<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<strings>
  <language name="English - Halloween" base="English" variant="Halloween" owner="ayylimao"/>
  <string key="NotInGame">
    <value>You don't appear to be in any games right now...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerStartedGame" isgif="true">
    <!-- 0 - Player name -->
    <value>{0} has started a game! Why don't you /join Halloween Town?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerStartedChaosGame" isgif="true">
    <!-- 0 - Player name -->
    <value>{0} has started some serious chaos in Halloween Town! Why don't you /join in in the confusion?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NoJoinGameRunning">
    <value>Halloween Town is being attacked! No new denizens are being accepted at the moment...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AlreadyJoined">
    <value>You've already joined!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MinuteLeftToJoin">
    <value>1 minute left to /join</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SecondsLeftToJoin">
    <!-- 0 - remaining seconds (number) -->
    <value>{0} seconds left to /join</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NotEnoughPlayers">
    <value>Not enough monsters, cancelling game!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="StartingGameWait">
    <value>Game is starting, please wait while I assign roles and update the database.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="BannedForExploit">
    <!-- 0 - Player name -->
    <value>{0} is banned for attempting an exploit (no names starting with /)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ChangeNameToJoin">
    <!-- 0 - Player name -->
    <value>{0}, please change your name to join</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerLimitReached">
    <value>Sorry, max player limit has been reached!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerJoined">
    <!-- 0 - Player name -->
    <!-- 1 - current players -->
    <!-- 2 - Minimum players -->
    <!-- 3 - Maximum players -->
    <value>Welcome {0} to Halloween Town! Population: {1}! There is no town without at least {2} monsters, and this one only has {3} dens!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PMTheBot">
    <!-- 0 - Player name -->
    <!-- 1 - bot username -->
    <value>{0} click this: {1}, then click start.  Until you do, I cannot tell you what your role is.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DeadFlee">
    <value>You can't run away! You're dead and there are no zombies in the game!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Flee">
    <!-- 0 - Player name -->
    <value>Was this town too monstrous? {0} must have thought that, because they fled in terror!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerRoleWas">
    <!-- 0 - Player name -->
    <!-- 1 - Player role -->
    <value>{0} was {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CountPlayersRemain">
    <!-- 0 - Number of players -->
    <value>{0} monsters remain.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DidntAsk">
    <value>I know you're bloodthirsty but wait, I didn't even ask you anything yet!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NotPlaying">
    <value>You aren't a monster...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NoPlayerName">
    <value>I can't find that monster, are you sure that's the right name?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AnswerNonValid">
    <value>You don't need to talk like a monster too, otherwise I won't understand!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolfVotedKill">
    <!-- 0 - wolf teammate name -->
    <!-- 1 - Victim name -->
    <value>{0} has voted to attack {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerVotedLynch">
    <!-- 0 - Voter name -->
    <!-- 1 - Target name -->
    <value>{0} has voted to burn {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="IdleKill">
    <!-- 0 - player name -->
    <!-- 1 - player role -->
    <value>{0} for some reason didn't want anyone burned twice in a row... The whole town thought this was fishy, and {0} probably noticed that too, because they suddenly ran away. {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="TraitorTurnWolf">
    <value>All of your brethren have been killed! Engulfed in rage, you decided to become one of them, ready to attack anyone in this hellhole...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ChoiceAccepted">
    <value>Choice accepted</value>
  </string>
  <string key="BeholderSeer">
    <!-- 0 - seer name -->
    <value>\nYour master is {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ApprenticeNowSeer">
    <!-- 0 - seer name -->
    <value>{0}, the former head of your coven, has died. As their successor, you have become the new head, and are now allowed to use soul-searching spells.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="BeholderNewSeer">
    <!-- 0 - apprentice name -->
    <!-- 1 - seer name -->
    <value>{0} was {1}'s apprentice, and is now the new head of the coven. As your master's successor, they are now your new master.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SeerSees">
    <!-- 0 - player name -->
    <!-- 1 - player role -->
    <value>After a long night of preparations, your spell finally works, revealing to you {0}'s soul, that of {1}!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskLynch">
    <value>Who do you want to burn?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskDetect">
    <value>Your former coven is asleep, and now you can use a soul-searching spell on someone, but who?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskShoot">
    <!-- 0 - bullet count -->
    <value>Whose death can you feel Halloween Town wishing for? The town has {0} wishes left!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskVisit">
    <value>Who do you want to feed off?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskSee">
    <value>Who should you use a soul-searching spell on?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskGuard">
    <value>What den do you want to guard?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskEat">
    <value>Who do you want to attack?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskHunt">
    <value>You ready your trusty blade for a visit... Who do you think might be a vampire?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskRoleModel">
    <value>Who is your master?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskConvert">
    <value>Whose blood do you want to drink?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DiscussWith">
    <!--Leave the leading spaces here please-->
    <!-- 0 - teammate names -->
    <value>  Make sure you discuss with {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="And">
    <!--this is paired with "DiscussWith".  again, leave the spaces!-->
    <value> and </value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoCursed">
    <value>You are the Half-Demon 😾! You look enough like your demonic counterparts to pass as one and live in Halloween Town. The only problem you have to contend with is your human blood making you more susceptible to curses... Both werewolves and vampires can try and make you one of their own!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoDetective">
    <value>You are the Warlock 🕵! You used to be a part of Halloween Town's only coven, but some disagreements made you be asked to leave... You can still use the soul-searching spells you learned with your former coven, just... not at the same time. The witches sleep during the day, so that's the time you can use your spells to find out exactly what kind of monster another person is! Be careful, though... When the sun is out, the walls have ears, and werewolves' heightened hearing may notice you preparing your spells!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoDrunk">
    <value>You are the Leprechaun 🍻! You spend the day... and night... drinking, which makes your blood have a very high alcohol content... While vampires might be (very!) fine with that, werewolves will get drunk if they kill you, rendering them unable to attack the next night!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoGuardianAngel">
    <value>You are the Gargoyle 👼! The church you lived in has been destroyed by the demons, and you honestly don't know where to live (and guard) now... Every night, you can choose one den to protect, but be careful: some monsters are quite territorial and might not like your presence...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoGunner">
    <value>You are the Genie 🔫! Long ago, you have promised three death wishes to Halloween Town. Only two are left, and you're planning to make them come true quickly, before the town is no more!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoHarlot">
    <value>You are the Succubus 💋! Every night, you go to someone's den and feed off them, which sounds wonderful but won't be if the monster you choose to feed off isn't very open to visitors. Still, a girl's gotta eat, right?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoTraitor">
    <value>You are the Wolf Demon 🖕! Nobody knows it - or maybe they suspect it - but you're actually the demon who started it all, creating the werewolves as a pastime. All went wonderfully until they started becoming violent... If all of your creations die, you will be so enraged you'll become one of them! Spells aren't that good with demon types, so a witch might see you as either a common demon or a werewolf...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoWolf">
    <value>You are a Werewolf 🐺! Back in the day you lived peacefully with the other monsters at Halloween Town, but some time ago werewolves have become violent and stronger... Strong enough that, each night, you can choose a den to attack and will probably be able to kill the monster living there!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoSeer" >
    <value >You are the Witch 👳! The head of Halloween Town's coven, you are the only one allowed to use soul-searching spells. Those spells take time, though, so you will only be able to search the soul of one monster each night to find out what they are!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoVillager" >
    <value >You are a Demon 👱! That sounds super awesome, but in Halloween Town you're actually another one in a crowd. Still, there's strength in numbers!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoTanner" >
    <value >You are the Phoenix 👺! Back in the time, you used to be very powerful, but now it's the end of your life and you can't even summon fire to be reborn... Luckily, it seems every evening Halloween Town's denizens are burning someone at the stake... If they choose you, the flames will let you be reborn, at the cost of the entire town!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoWildChild" >
    <value >You are Cerberus 👶! Choose one of Halloween Town's denizens to be your master, and you will be happy as long as they live... Once they die, though, your pain and rage will be so big you'll become a werewolf!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoBeholder" >
    <value >You are the Witch's Familiar 👁! Having sworn loyalty to the witch, the same way you've been sworn loyalty to, you are the witch's most trusted companion. Of course, as much as the witch treats you well, you are also a symbol of power: only the head of the coven has a familiar, so anyone who isn't your master and claims they're the witch is either lying or a fool.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoApprenticeSeer" >
    <value >You are the Witch's Apprentice 🙇! Having studied under the current head of the coven for years, you are the next in line if the current witch dies!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoCultist" >
    <value >You are a Vampire 👤! Every night, you and your clan can choose one person to attack... Not that you'll kill them! Your clan has a strict no-killing rule, so the most you ever do to your victims is drink their blood... And, well. If that turns them into vampires, who are you to complain? The more the merrier!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoCultistHunter" >
    <value >You are a Dhampir 💂! Child of a vampire and a human, you are accepted in Halloween Town as a monster, but don't plan to live peacefully there! You've got a bone to pick with vampires, and, every night, you go to a monster's den, trusting your blade to cut them down if they're actually a vampire!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="LynchTime" >
    <!-- 0 - number of seconds -->
    <value>
      The last remnants of light are finally going away, but now it's time to create a new source before embracing the darkness... A pyre has been prepared, and all monsters must now decide who will be burnt in it!
      Only {0} seconds before the flames die down!
    </value>
  </string>
  <string key="DayTime" >
    <!-- 0 - number of seconds -->
    <value >Sadly, all that's good must end, and the sun has come once more to cull Halloween Town's freedom... Few monsters can do anything at all during the day's {0} seconds other than talk.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NightTime" >
    <!-- 0 - number of seconds -->
    <value >All light has finally disappeared, and Halloween Town's denizens are free to do as they wish for {0} seconds!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="LynchKill" >
    <!-- 0 - player name -->
    <!-- 1 - player role -->
    <value >It took some time but now Halloween Town has decided on who to burn at the stake. {0} dies in a flurry of ashes and flames. {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="LynchTie" >
    <value >The town's denizens tried and tried to decide who to burn, but were unable to do that before the flames died...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NoLynchVotes" >
    <value >Looks like no one wants to burn their fellow neighbors! The pyre's flames died without taking any lives with them...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DetectiveEaten" >
    <!-- 0 - victim name -->
    <value >Strangely enough, no one could find {0} in the morning. Someone tried to search for them in their den, sidestepping cauldrons and magic tomes, but could only find blood and pieces of meat... Still, the contents of their den were enough to figure out it was the Warlock 🕵's!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardianEaten" >
    <!-- 0 - victim name -->
    <value >As soon as the first rays of light appear, everyone can see pieces of stone strewn around the town, obviously belonging to {0}, the Gargoyle 👼.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GunnerEaten" >
    <!-- 0 - victim name -->
    <value >{0} is nowhere to be seen, and there's nothing that could explain their disappearance, other than a broken lamp...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SeerEaten" >
    <!-- 0 - victim name -->
    <value >The coven is in mourning... Gossip quickly spreads to the whole town, and soon everyone knows {0}, the former head of the Witches' 👳 coven, was found almost unrecognisable in their den last night.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DrunkEaten" >
    <!-- 0 - victim name -->
    <value >A few gold coins strewn around are quickly pocketed by the first to see them, until a smart monster realizes they make a trail. Following them to find the source, they find a toppled beer mug, and a small green body covered in gold, blood and beer... Isn't that a wonderful mixture? {0} is dead, but a lucky monster got a very good meal!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="FoolEaten" >
    <!-- 0 - victim name -->
    <value >Surrounded by puppets and slumped above a magician's hat, the body of {0} is found by a demon who often brought them food. While mourning is completely natural for a demon, maybe that one should have paid attention to whose shoulder they were crying on... Thanks to an awful gossiper, the whole town now knows that recluse monster was delusional, thinking themselves the head of a big coven...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DefaultEaten" >
    <!-- 0 - victim name -->
    <!-- 1 - victim role -->
    <value>The instantly recognizable smell of blood permeates the entire town. Hungry demons search and search and finally find a good breakfast in {0}'s lifeless body. Greedier demons enter the late monster's den, stealing everything of value and in the process finding out {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterKilledCultist">
    <!-- 0 - victim name -->
    <value>WHAT is that thing surrounding {0}'s den? Holy water? Who would do such a thing... No one wants to try crossing that insurmountable barrier to find out exactly what happened, but whispers on the street mention a Dhampir going around, exterminating vampires in the exact same way...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NoAttack" >
    <value >Morning comes, and it sounds like the night is the only thing to be mourned... Curious as to who died this time, Halloween Town was disappointed to see no one did.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CursedBitten" >
    <value >You had little warning before being violently attacked last night by frenzied wolves... After they left you for dead, the pain you were feeling somehow only increased... You have no idea how long you were screaming in pain until you started howling, but at the end of all that, you realized you had become a werewolf yourself.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolfTeam">
    <!-- 0 - teammate names -->
    <value>Your pack is composed of {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CursedBittenToWolves" >
    <!-- 0 - victim name -->
    <value >You had a lot of fun attacking {0} last night... And, hours after that, you could hear another wolf's howl. Looks like you got a new packmate!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolvesEatYou" isgif="true" >
    <value >You fought valiantly after you were attacked in the dead of the night, but it was for naught.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolvesEatDrunk" >
    <!-- 0 - victim name -->
    <value >This was a great night! {0} was a fun prey, the meat was tasty, and even after returning home you're still feeling the buzz of victory... Or is it another buzz? Oops! Looks like that taste was the one of beer marinated meat...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardWolf" >
    <value >You spent centuries guarding your church from outside threats... So how would you know what to do when the threat came from within? The den you tried to guard belonged to a very territorial wolf...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardSaved" >
    <!-- 0 - saved player name -->
    <value >The battle you fought tonight was one you were born to fight, and you emerged victorious, happy in the knowledge your victory saved {0}'s life.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardNoAttack" >
    <!-- 0 - player name -->
    <value >It was a quiet night outside {0}'s den, the stillness soothing for your stone heart.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardEmptyHouse">
    <!-- 0 - player name -->
    <value>You spent the night outside {0}'s den, guarding it from anything and anyone... Why would it matter to you that the den was empty all night?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardSavedYou" >
    <value >You heard a sound outside your den, quickly taking a look to see a gargoyle fighting someone. Silently wishing the stone monster good luck, you go back inside, feeling safer than ever.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotEaten" >
    <!-- 0 - player name -->
    <value >Undoubtedly the Succubus was already full, and decided to stay home for the night... A terrible choice, since the werewolves also wanted to satisfy their own appetite, and became full with {0}'s flesh...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotNotHome" >
    <!-- 0 - player name -->
    <value >You went to great lengths to stealthily attack {0}'s den tonight, only to find out there was no one inside...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotFuckWolf" >
    <!-- 0 - player name -->
    <value >You decide to feed off {0} tonight, but, entering their den, you find out the meal today is going to be you...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotFuckedWolfPublic" >
    <!-- 0 - player name -->
    <value >{0} chose the wrong victim last night, and became one! Only the Succubus' 💋 wings are left, dropped like an afterthought in one of Halloween Town's many streets...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotFuckedVictimPublic" >
    <!-- 0 - harlot name -->
    <!-- 1 - victim name -->
    <value >Looks like {1} was just too appealing a victim, because two monsters chose that den to attack last night... But of course the werewolves won. {0}, the Succubus 💋, was killed along with their intended victim...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotVisitNonWolf" >
    <!-- 0 - target name -->
    <value >What a good meal you had tonight! {0} was full of energy when the night started, although now they're in a rather bad shape...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotVisitYou" >
    <value >What a wonderful night you had! Although you won't tell it to anyone, your dreams were very pleasurable, and you will remember them for a very long time... And if you're feeling worse for the wear once the morning comes, it's a small price to pay for that great night.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DetectiveCaught" >
    <!-- 0 - detective name -->
    <value >Your heightened hearing could catch some incantations being muttered in a den somewhere... Discreetly looking around, you realize the source of the sound is {0}'s den. Looks like you've caught the Warlock 🕵!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DetectiveSnoop" >
    <!-- 0 - target name -->
    <!-- 1 - target role -->
    <value >After lots of preparing and a very tiring enchantment, your spell finally reveals {0}'s soul, that of {1}!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotShot" >
    <!-- 0 - gunner's name -->
    <!-- 1 - Harlot's name -->
    <value >{0}'s voice resounds around. "Halloween Town's wish has been granted!" Suddenly, {1} falls death - obviously that was the wish the Genie talked about... {1} was the Succubus 💋</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DefaultShot" >
    <!-- 0 - Gunner's name -->
    <!-- 1 - target name -->
    <!-- 2 - Target's revealed name ( Target was a role) -->
    <value >{0}'s voice resounds around. "Halloween Town's wish has been granted!" Suddenly, {1} falls death - obviously that was the wish the Genie talked about... {2}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolfWins" isgif="true" >
    <value >A single werewolf has proven itself to be stronger than a whole village of monsters... The werewolf has won!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolvesWin" isgif="true" >
    <value >Monsters and demons did their best, but in the end, the werewolves prevailed!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="VillageWins" isgif="true" >
    <value >There's no match for a village full of monsters and demons! Halloween Town has endured all!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="TannerWins" isgif="true" >
    <value >As the pyre consumes a body, the flames grow higher and higher, until Halloween Town is consumed by them. The only thing remaning is a small phoenix chick...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RemainingPlayersEnd">
    <value>The bloodbath in Halloween City was awful, but we must congratulate the survivors:</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultistVotedConvert" >
    <!-- 0 - Voter's name -->
    <!-- 1 - target name -->
    <value >{0} wants to attack {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultConvertCultHunter">
    <!-- 0 - Yougest Cultist (killed)'s name' -->
    <!-- 1 - CultHunter's name -->
    <value>Your clan showed up in {1}'s den, ready to have a good snack... But they met a trained vampire hunter! {0} was killed in the fight with the Dhampir...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultHunterKilledCultVisit">
    <!-- 0 - Youngest Cultist's name -->
    <!-- 1 - Number of cultists left -->
    <value>You sensed vampires nearby, and, true to that, soon Hallowen Town's entire clan was upon you. But you've been ready for that fight ever since you were born... {0} fell by your blade, but the {1} other vampires who attacked you managed to escape...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultConvertYou">
    <value>The first thing you realized was a prickle in your neck, then another, then another... At the end of the night, you didn't even feel the blood loss anymore, and the vampire clan accepted you as one of their own.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultTeam">
    <!-- 0 - Number of cultists -->
    <value>The Vampire's clan is composed of {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultJoin">
    <!-- 0 - new cultist's name -->
    <value>{0} was a wonderful meal, and now is your fellow clanmate!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultVisitEmpty">
    <!-- 0 - Newest cultist's name -->
    <!-- 1 - target name -->
    <value>Your clan visited {1}'s den, but there was no one inside... You might be used to your new body by now, but {0}, the newest member of your clan, won't stop complaining about hunger...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultWins" isgif="true">
    <value >Halloween Town was full of good meals, but now the only denizens left are part of the vampire clan... Soon, they should leave town in search of more victims.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterVisitDead">
    <!-- 0 - target name -->
    <value>You entered {0}'s den with your blade ready to strike, only to find a dead body...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterFindCultist">
    <!-- 0 - target name -->
    <value>Stealthily and carefully, you get in {0}'s den, searching for any evidence they are a vampire... And you find it, in the shape of fangs going straight for your neck! The fight is a dance you know well, and at the end of it, you go home knowing there is one less vampire in Halloween Town.</value>
  </string>
  <!-- 0 - target name -->
  <string key="HunterFailedToFind">
    <value>Stealthily and carefully, you get in {0}'s den, searching for any evidence they are a vampire... But there is none.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WildChildToWolves">
    <!-- 0 - Werechild's name -->
    <value>{0}'s master died! Their rage is a sight for sore eyes, and at the end of it, you realize it left you with a new packmate.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WildChildTransform">
    <!-- 0 - role's name -->
    <!-- 0 - teamate's names -->
    <value>{0} has died! You are stricken by grief and an all-encompassing rage, only realizing after you've calmed down how feral you've gone... Enough to be considered a werewolf, that's for sure. You're accepted by the Town's pack, {1}</value>
  </string>
  <!-- Villager, Drunk, Harlot, Seer, Traitor, GuardianAngel, Detective, Wolf, Cursed, Gunner, Tanner, Fool, WildChild, Beholder, ApprenticeSeer, Cultist, CultistHunter-->
  <string key="Villager">
    <value>a Demon 👱</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Drunk">
    <value>the Leprechaun 🍻</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Harlot">
    <value>the Succubus 💋</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Seer">
    <value>the Witch 👳</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Traitor">
    <value>the Wolf Demon 🖕</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardianAngel">
    <value>the Gargoyle 👼</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Detective">
    <value>the Warlock 🕵</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Wolf">
    <value>a Werewolf 🐺</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Cursed">
    <value>the Half-Demon 😾</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Gunner">
    <value>the Genie 🔫</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Tanner">
    <value>the Phoenix 👺</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Fool">
    <value>the Magician 🃏</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WildChild">
    <value>Cerberus 👶</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Beholder">
    <value>the Witch's Familiar 👁</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ApprenticeSeer">
    <value>the Witch's Apprentice 🙇</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Cultist">
    <value>a Vampire 👤</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultistHunter">
    <value>the Dhampir 💂</value>
  </string>
  <!-- These are for the player list -->
  <string key="RanAway">
    <value>Ran away</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Dead">
    <value>💀 Dead</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Alive">
    <value>🙂 Alive</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayersAlive">
    <value>Monsters Alive</value>
  </string>
  <!-- New strings 4 MAY 2016-->
  <string key="Mason">
    <value>an Alien 👷</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoMason">
    <value>There is a big investigation going on about humans, and you're one of the unlucky ones who get to stay in the HQ and manage everything without taking part in the action. Usually, you would do that from the mothership, but humans are just too suspicious about space, so you had to set up a temporary base in Halloween Town, where even Aliens 👷 are accepted as denizens. Although you all live in different homes, you do know who your fellow planetmen are... After all, you need to work in a team to manage everything!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MasonEaten">
    <!-- 0 - dead man's name -->
    <value>Once again there is light, illuminating a really strange sight. {0} is obviously dead, with green blood splattered around... It seems aliens aren't a tasty meal for werewolves.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MasonTeam">
    <value>  The aliens are: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <!-- new strings May 6 2016-->
  <string key="CultTargetDead">
    <!-- 0 - Youngest cultists name -->
    <value>Your clan goes into {0}'s den ready for a nice snack, finding evidence of a fight there, and lots of blood in the ground... But you're not that hungry tonight, and return home without drinking a drop of blood from there.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardBlockedWolf">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>{0} sounded like a really good meal, but, when going to his den, your pack noticed a Gargoyle 👼 outside it. Sneaking around would have been useless, you were all rather hungry already, and the gargoyle was already looking at the pack, ready for a fight. And what a fight it was! One to be remembered, but maybe not by you, the losers... At least there were no casualties on your side (or any side, really).</value>
  </string>
  <!-- new strings May 9 2016-->
  <string key="CultUnableToConvert">
    <!-- 0 - newest  -->
    <!-- 1 - target's name -->
    <value>Your clan safely gets into {1}'s den to attack them, and even {0}, the hungriest out of all of you, went back home feeling full... Somehow, you even managed to leave your prey completely alive, and can surely visit them again for another late night snack!</value>
  </string>
  <!-- new string May 12 2016-->
  <string key="NameExists">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <!-- 1 - name -->
    <value>@{1}, a player with the name {0} has already joined.  Please change your name to join.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotDiscoverCult">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>Tonight's meal was slightly lacking... {0}'s energy wasn't as strong as most monsters', and while you fed, they tried to feed off you too! Your neck still hurts from the bite, even if you didn't let them take any blood...</value>
  </string>
  <!-- new string May 13 2016-->
  <string key="Was">
    <value>was</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GenericDeathNoReveal">
    <!-- 0 - Dead's name -->
    <value>Soon after morning comes, someone notices {0} isn't anywhere to be seen... But no one could find them, so they were assumed dead, and life went on.</value>
    <value>The sun didn't even rise completely and everyone already knows {0} is dead, because a friend of a friend of a friend saw their body... That's all anyone knows about it, though.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MasonConverted">
    <!-- 0 - mason's name -->
    <value>You waited the whole night for {0} to show up, even had to take care of a few of his investigators, but nothing. And yet, you know they're not dead because once morning came, you saw them outside!</value>
  </string>
  <!-- new string May 16 2016-->
  <string key="FleeDisabled">
    <value>Fleeing while the game is running has been disabled by the group admin!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="IsDead">
    <!-- used when gunner shoots a player -->
    <value>is dead</value>
  </string>

  <!-- MORE STRINGS May 16, 2016 -->
  <string key="AdminAdded">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>{0} added to admin list. Use /config to change group settings.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AlreadyInGame">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>You are already in a game! ({0})</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MultipleGames">
    <value>Your group has managed to start multiple games...  Killing extras.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GroupQueue">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <!-- 1 - target's name -->
    <value>Your group is currently in the queue.  Position: {0} / {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MaintBreak">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>Sorry, I'm about to start a short maintenance break, you can't start a game right now.\nWaiting on {0} games to end...\nGo to @werewolfdev for more information</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MaxGames">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <!-- 1 - target's name -->
    <value>Sorry, max concurrent games has been reached ({0}).  \nPosition in queue: {1} / {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SkipQueue">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>{0} is a preferred group, and has skipped the queue!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NoGame">
    <value>There is no game running.  Start a new game with /startgame or start a chaos game with /startchaos</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GroupAdminOnly">
    <value>Only a group admin can run this command.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShuttingDown">
    <value>After this game, I am shutting down for maintenance.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShuttingDownUpdate">
    <value>After this game, I am shutting down momentarily for an update (automated).</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NullIdAdmin">
    <value>UserId was null.  Are you sure you sent this as a reply?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AlreadyAdmin">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>{0} is already an admin!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NotAdmin">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>{0} is not an admin!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AdminRemoved">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>{0} removed from admin list.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="LanguageSet">
    <!-- 0 - language's name -->
    <value>Language set to {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NoSeer">
    <value>Sadly, the witches' coven is no more, and you have no master...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="TimesUp">
    <value>Time's up!</value>
  </string>
  <!-- new strings june 10 2016 -->
  <string key="RoleInfoCupid">
    <value>You are the Love Fairy 🏹! You're cute, you're romantic, and you're ready to do some mischief. Your powers are a bit limited, but you can still work with them! Once in every blue moon, you can make it so two people's souls are connected... They will feel happiness when the other is happy, and death when the other is killed.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoDoppelganger">
    <value>You are a Shapeshifter 🎭! Unfortunately, too many pranks have left you with a strict rule: no shifting into someone from the Town, and no shifting without telling someone responsible about it! Still, they didn't say anything about shifting into dead people... With all those attacks going around, today will be your last chance to choose someone to shift into once they die!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoHunter">
    <value>You are the Yeti 🎯! You don't particularly care about Halloween Town's affairs, and your den is even in a remote location... But you're extremely territorial, and anyone who decides to pay you a visit will surely regret it, just as they will if they try to kill you.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoSerialKiller">
    <value>You are the Chupacabra 🔪! While most monsters in Halloween Town only dare to eat corpses, you like your meals fresh, and they're only dead by the end of your dinner. You're so stealthy most of them don't even get the chance to fight, but if you choose the wrong victim, be careful, because there's no one watching your back...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CupidChosen">
    <value>Suddenly, you start to wonder what {0} is doing right now... You can't take them out of your head. You're hit by the great wish, almost a need, to see them happy, and can't even imagine what would happen should they die. Can it be... love?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterLynchedChoice">
    <value>Demons fasten ropes tying you to the pyre, and light the fire... As soon as you feel flames catching on your fur, a maddening despair gives you strength you've never felt before, and you break free of the pyre! You're still catching fire, though, and won't be able to survive much longer. Will you use your last breaths to take revenge, and on who?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterNoChoiceLynched">
    <value>{0} breaks free of the pyre, but only manages to stumble a little forward before falling dead, the fire's heat too much for their body.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterSkipChoiceLynched">
    <value>{0} breaks free of the pyre, roaring... and tries, in vain, to take the fire that catched on their fur out. Sadly, their last breaths are spent fruitless, and the Yeti falls dead soon after.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterKilledFinalLynched">
    <!-- 0 - hunter's name -->
    <!-- 1 - target's name -->
    <!-- 2 - target's role -->
    <value>{0} breaks free of the pyre, roaring and still catching fire! It's a terrifying sight, for {1} more than anyone, since that's who the Yeti decided to attack. What follows is a gory death, followed by the Yeti's own, finally consumed by the flames. {2}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterShotChoice">
    <value>You've been deadly wounded! Your strength is waning quickly, but you still have enough to at least try and get revenge... But on who?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterNoChoiceShot">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>The wounds were too much for {0}, and the Yeti didn't even growl before succumbing to them...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterSkipChoiceShot">
    <!-- 0 - hunter's name -->
    <value>{0} decided to spend their final moments trying to survive instead of taking revenge, a truly useless endeavour...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterKilledFinalShot">
    <!-- 0 - hunter -->
    <!-- 1 - target's name -->
    <!-- 2 - target's role -->
    <value>{0} is bleeding out, but not quickly enough to be unable to fight! The Yeti attacks {1} with all the strength of a dying monster, and the result of their struggle is... both of their deaths. {2}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultConvertSerialKiller">
    <value>Your clan goes to {1}'s den, slipping inside carefully ready to suck their blood... But looks like the monster inside wanted to do the same to you! All vampires struggle and struggle, but finally manage to run from that treacherous den... Except for {0}, who sadly was killed in the fight.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterShotWolfMulti">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>The werewolves chose the wrong den to attack, because that one was home to an Yeti! The fight was long and arduous, leaving both the Yeti and the werewolf {0} dead.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterShotWolf">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>The werewolf {0} tried to attack an Yeti's den, a mistake they paid for with their life!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SerialKillerKilledWolf">
    <value>The werewolves attacked someone who also wanted to attack people... {0} has been killed by the Chupacabra!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DefaultKilled">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <!-- 1 - target's role -->
    <value>Noticing {0}'s absence, someone goes to their den see what happened, only to find a corpse sucked dry, left there to rot... Halloween Town's vampires never kill, so this is obviously the work of the Chupacabra! {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardBlockedKiller">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>Incredibly hungry, you go to {0}'s den for a good meal, only to find a Gargoyle outside it! You try going in anyway, but the stone guardian fights you off.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultConvertHunter">
    <!-- 0 - Youngest Cultist's name -->
    <!-- 1 - target's name -->
    <value>The clan goes to {1}'s den, only to find a very angry Yeti! You all know better, and flee home, but sadly {0} wasn't fast enough... Their screams will haunt you for weeks.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultConvertSerialKiller">
    <!-- 0 - Youngest Cultist's name -->
    <!-- 1 - target's name -->
    <value>The clan goes into {1}'s den, ready to drink some blood, but looks like {1} also wants a nice meal... You fight valiantly to escape and drink for another day, but sadly {0} falls in the fight, and seeing no other choice, all of you flee while your clanmate is sucked dry by the Chupacabra...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardKiller">
    <value>You spent centuries guarding your church from outside threats... So how would you know what to do when the threat came from within? Your back was turned to the Chupacabra, a terrible mistake.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotFuckKiller">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>You slip into {0}'s den, ready for a good meal, but trying to feed off the Chupacabra is never a good idea, and you became tonight's dinner instead...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotFuckKillerPublic">
    <value>don't worry about this string for now! - {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGToMason">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>There's no reason to mourn today, because the shapeshifter {0} shifted into an alien, and will now work just as your late colleague did!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGTransformToMason">
    <!-- 0 - dead mason's name -->
    <!-- 1 - mason collegues's name -->
    <value>{0} is dead, and you can finally shift into someone! Now you're an alien, which would be great, if you didn't have to work every single night now... Your colleagues are: {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGToCult">
    <!-- 0 - new cultist's name -->
    <value>Your clan has mourned its lost member, but now there's a reason to rejoice! The shapeshifter {0} has shifted into them, and is now part of your clan!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGTransformToCult">
    <!-- 0 - role's name -->
    <!-- 1 - teammates's name -->
    <value>{0} is dead, and you can finally shift into someone! As you shift, you can feel your fangs growing, and a thirst for blood... You have been accepted by the vampire clan: {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGToWolf">
    <!-- 0 - DG's name -->
    <value>The loss of a packmate is always sad, but at least now you've got a new one, {0}!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGTransformToWolf">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <!-- 1 - teammates's name -->
    <value>{0} is dead, and you can finally shift into someone! After the transformation is complete, you feel an overwhelming urge to howl at the moon... You have been accepted by the werewolf pack: {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SerialKillerWins" isgif="true">
    <value>No more meals for the Chupacabra, because all denizens of Halloween Town are dead... Looks like migrating again is in order!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskKill">
    <value>Who do you want to eat?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="LoverDied">
    <!-- 0 - dead's name -->
    <!-- 1 - lover's name -->
    <!-- 2 - roles -->
    <value>{0} dies by a very obvious cause, but left unexplained is the death of {1}, who died at the exact same time... {2}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskDoppelganger">
    <value>Who do you want to shift into once they die?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskCupid1">
    <value>Who should you connect someone's soul to?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskCupid2">
    <value>And who should that soul be connected to?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Hunter">
    <value>the Yeti 🎯</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Cupid">
    <value>the Love Fairy 🏹</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SerialKiller">
    <value>the Chupacabra 🔪</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Doppelgänger">
    <value>the Shapeshifter 🎭</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CupidChosen">
    <!-- 0 - lover's name -->
    <value>Suddenly, you start to wonder what {0} is doing right now... You can't take them out of your head. You're hit by the great wish, almost a need, to see them happy, and can't even imagine what would happen should they die. Can it be... love?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NewWCRoleModel">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>You have shifted into the Cerberus, taking with their features their love for their master, {0}!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="LoversWin">
    <value>Not even the Love Fairy could have seen that coming... The only ones left alive are the lovers - and what an odd couple they make!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterKilledVisiter">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <!-- 1 - role -->
    <value>The only thing remaining from {0} are pieces of flesh and a lot of blood... Looks like an Yeti attack! {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultAttempt">
    <value>Suddenly, you feel a sharp pain in your neck, quickly realizing you've been attacked by vampires... There's nothing to do but hold on to your consciousness, which you do, sighing with relief when they go away. Somehow, you didn't even became a vampire like them! Your blood must be truly strong.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AlreadyOnWaitList">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>You are already on the wait list for {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AddedToWaitList">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>You have been added to the wait list for {0}.  I will PM you when the next game is starting. </value>
  </string>
  <string key="NotifyNewGame">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>A new game is starting in {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SerialKillerWinsOverpower">
    <!-- 0 - SK's name -->
    <!-- 1 - target's name -->
    <value>There are only two monsters left alive... No, wait... {0} plunges into {1}'s neck, quickly killing them. Only the Chupacabra is left, with a stomach full and energy to spare.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NoWinner" isgif="true">
    <value>Halloween Town has become a ghost town... No monsters were left alive after the terrible Halloween Bloodbath.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SKHunterEnd">
    <!-- 0 - SK's name -->
    <!-- 1 - Hunter's name -->
    <value>Monsters in a town... What's a town to a werewolf? What's a werewolf to a chupacabra? What's a chupacabra to an yeti? The fight between {0} and {1} was one to be remembered, but there was no one left to watch it, and there was no one left to tell the story, either.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleModelChosen">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>You failed to make a choice, so the moderator has chosen for you: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Won">
    <value>Won</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Lost">
    <value>Lost</value>
  </string>
  <string key="IdleCount">
    <!-- 0 - player's name -->
    <!-- 1 - idle count -->
    <value>Player {0} has been killed for not voting {1} times in the past 24 hours.</value>
  </string>
  <!--New strings 7th of July-->
  <string key="AboutVG">
    <value>Your role is simple - try to survive. Each day, you will have a chance to lynch the werewolf.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutSeer">
    <value>You are the Seer. In this role, each night, you may choose a player, and have their role revealed to you. Admit to your role wisely: If you reveal you are the seer, the wolves will try to kill you!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutWw">
    <value>You get to have fun! Each day, you will attempt to decieve your fellow players. However, each night, you will get to pick a player to kill! Note:if you attack the drunk, you yourself will become drunk, and will be unable to attack the next night as you sleep off your hangover! If you attack the cursed, they will become a wolf like yourself! Hooray friends!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutHarlot">
    <value>As the harlot (you slut...) you will be given the chance to 'visit' another player each night. If they are not the wolf, you will be told so (because you live!). If you visit a wolf, you will be killed. If you visit the player the wolves have chosen to kill, you will be killed as well. However - If you are visiting a player, and the wolves choose to kill you, you will survive (you weren't home)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutDrunk">
    <value>You drunken bastard! As the drunk, you are still just a villager. BUT! If the wolves kill you, they will become disabled for the next night, as they are drunk off your insanely high BAC.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutCursed">
    <value>As the cursed, you are a normal villager... until the wolves kill you. Once they do, you will become a wolf as well! Free to hunt in the night..... XD</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutTraitor">
    <value>You are a traitorous bastard. If you survive long enough for all the wolves to die, you will become a werewolf, ready to kill your former teammates in the night!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutGA">
    <value>You are the Guardian Angel! Each night, you may choose a player to watch over. Be careful however - if you choose to watch over a wolf, there is a 50% chance you will be killed.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutDetective">
    <value>You old sleuth.. Each day, you will have the chance to investigate another player. Use this carefully however, for these is a 40% chance the werewolves will detect you!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutGunner">
    <value>A bit trigger happy are we? As the gunner, you are given 2 silver bullets at the beginning of the game. Each day, you will have the chance to shoot another player. Once you do, everyone will know you are the gunner! Be careful though, you only have 2 bullets!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutTanner">
    <value>The Tanners goal is simple: Get Lynched. If the Tanner gets lynched, he wins, period. Everyone else loses.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutFool">
    <value>he fool is told they are the seer.... when they choose to see someone's role at night, they are told a random role.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutCult">
    <value>As a cultist, it is your goal to convert all other players (except wolves) to your cult. If at the end of the game, all living players are cultist - the cult wins</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutCH">
    <value>Your job is to hunt the Cult. If the cult attacks you, their newest member will die. Each night you may pick a player to 'hunt' - if they are a cultist, they will die.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutWC">
    <value>At the beginning of the game, you will choose someone to be your 'role model'. If they die, you become a werewolf.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutAppS">
    <value>For now, you are a normal villager. However, if the seer dies, you will become the new seer</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutBH">
    <value>You will be told who the seer is (the real one, not the fool)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutMason">
    <value>A masons job is simple - they automatically know who the other masons are. Otherwise, they are a simple villager.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutDG">
    <value>
      Your ancestors had the ability to metamorph into others... while you don't have their full abilities, you can pick a player at the start of the game. If that player dies, you will become what they were.
      Note: If the player was converted to cult, you will take on their original role. All other normal rules apply: If they were Wild Child and their role model died, you will become a wolf. Otherwise, you will inherit their role model.
      The cult cannot convert the Doppelgänger (but can after the doppelganger switches roles). Also - the Doppelgänger can NOT win unless they have transformed. If at the end of the game, the Doppelgänger is still the same, they lose (exception: lover)
    </value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutCupid">
    <value>
      Love is in the air. As Cupid, you will choose two players at the start of the game. These two players will become madly in love! If one of them dies, the other will die of sorrow :(
      Note: Lovers will know who each other are, but not be told their roles. If the lovers are the last two alive, they win, regardless of teams. If the lovers are on different teams (villager + wolf), and one team wins (wolf), the lover (villager) wins as well. TL;DR if both lovers are alive at the end, and at least one of them was on the winning team, they both win together
    </value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutHunter">
    <value>
      A trigger happy, vindictive player. As the hunter, you try to keep to yourself. However, when others come to visit you, they may find themselves dead, as your paranoia takes hold and you shoot. If the wolves attack you, you have a chance to take one of them with you. Otherwise, if you die, you will get a chance to shoot someone as you die.
      Note: For wolf attacks, the chance starts at 30%. If there is one wolf, the hunter has a 30% chance to kill the wolf (and survive). For each additional wolf, add 20% (2 wolves = 50%, 3 = 70%, etc). However - if there are multiple wolves, while you may kill one of them, you will still be outnumbered and killed.
      If the cult tries to convert you, they have a 50% chance to fail. If they fail, you have a 50% chance to kill one of them!
    </value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutSK">
    <value>That asylum was silly anyways. What a joke. You are free now however, back to business as usual - killing! The serial killer is a lone player, on their own team. They can win only if they are the last player alive (exception: lovers). As the serial killer, you can kill ANYONE - wolves, hunters, gunners, guardian angels, whatever. If the wolves try to attack you, you will kill one of them (random), and live.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutPara">
    <value>Para is a silly developer that likes to bark at people.  Maybe he's been messing with werewolves too long....Messing with werewolves is a very bad idea.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="EndTime">
    <value>Game Length: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <!--New strings, July the 8th -->

  <string key="Day">
    <!--0 - Day -->
    <value>Day {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NodeShutsDown">
    <value>An error has occured, and this node has shut down :/</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SentPrivate">
    <value>I have sent you a PM</value>
  </string>
  <string key="StartPM">
    <value>Please send me a pm so I can PM you: @werewolfbot</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PMTrue">
    <value>Thanks for starting me! I can PM you now.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MustReplySmite">
    <value>You must reply to the user you want to smite</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WhatToDo">
    <value>What would you like to do?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="JoinFromGroup">
    <value>You must join a game from within a group chat!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="StartFromGroup">
    <value>You must start a game from within a group chat!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PingInfo">
    <value>Time for Telegram to send message to me: {0}\nCurrent CPU Usage: {1}%\nMessages per second: {2}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WhatLang">
    <value>What Language?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WhatVariant">
    <value>What Variant?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="LangSet">
    <value>Language set to {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GetLang">
    <value>Get which language file?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NoNodes">
    <value>There are no nodes online right now, please try again in a few seconds</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GroupCommandOnly">
    <value>You must run this command in a group</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NotGlobalAdmin">
    <value>You aren't a global admin...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NotPara">
    <value>You aren't Para!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Yes">
    <value>Yes</value>
  </string>
  <string key="No">
    <value>No</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Allow">
    <value>Allow</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Disallow">
    <value>Disallow</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Show">
    <value>Show</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Hide">
    <value>Hide</value>
  </string>
  <!-- Game Mode Choices-->
  <string key="NormalOnly">
    <value>Normal Only</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ChaosOnly">
    <value>Chaos Only</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerChoice">
    <value>Player Choice</value>
  </string>

  <!-- Show Roles on End Game -->
  <string key="ShowNone">
    <value>Don't show any</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShowLiving">
    <value>Show only living players</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShowAll">
    <value>Show all players</value>
  </string>

  <string key="Cancel">
    <value>Cancel</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowFleeQ">
    <!-- note, there is NO space after {0}.  This is on purpose -->
    <value>Do you want to allow fleeing once the game has started?\nNote: players can still flee during join phase\nCurrent: Players can {0}flee</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowFleeA">
    <!-- note, there is NO space after {0}.  This is on purpose -->
    <value>Players will {0}be allowed to flee after game start</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MaxPlayersQ">
    <value>How many players would like to set as the maximum?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MaxPlayersA">
    <value>Max players set to {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShowRolesDeathQ">
    <value>Show or Hide roles on death?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShowRolesDeathA">
    <value>Roles will be {0} on death.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GameModeQ">
    <value>What game mode will the group be?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GameModeA">
    <value>Game mode set to {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShowRolesEndQ">
    <value>How do you want roles to be shown at the end?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShowRolesEndA">
    <value>Roles shown at end set to: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SetDayTimeQ">
    <value>Choose the base time (in seconds) for day time.   This will still be modified based on number of players.\nMinimum time added based on players is 60 seconds.  Default setting: {0}\nCurrent: {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SetDayTimeA">
    <value>Base day time set to {0} seconds</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SetNightTimeQ">
    <value>Choose the time (in seconds) for night time. Default setting: {0}\nCurrent:{1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SetNightTimeA">
    <value>Night time set to {0} seconds</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SetLynchTimeQ">
    <value>Choose the time (in seconds) for lynch voting. Default setting: {0}\nCurrent:{1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SetLynchTimeA">
    <value>Lynch voting time set to {0} seconds</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowFoolQ">
    <value>Allow fool as a role option?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowFoolA">
    <value>Fool as a role set to: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowTannerQ">
    <value>Allow tanner as a role option?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowTannerA">
    <value>Tanner as a role set to: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowCultQ">
    <value>Allow cult as a role option?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowCultA">
    <value>Cult as a role set to: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThankYou">
    <value>Thank you, have a good day :)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WhatLangGroup">
    <value>What language do you want to look for a group to play in?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HereIsList">
    <value>Here are the groups for {0}:</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Members">
    <value>Members</value>
  </string>
  <string key="StartMe">
    <value>Please start me so I can PM you</value>
  </string>
</strings>
