<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<strings>
  <language name="Harry Potter English" base="English" variant="Harry Potter" owner="Benjy(Bumper)" code="en"/>
  <string key="PlayerStartedGame" isgif="true">
    <!-- 0 - Player name -->
    <value>{0} has started a new school year! Quickly get your tickets for the Hogwarts Express!!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerStartedChaosGame" isgif="true">
    <!-- 0 - Player name -->
    <value>Someone randomly threw an Avada Kedavra curse! {0} sighs about yet another chaotic Wizarding War.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MinuteLeftToJoin">
    <value>You have 1 minute left before the Hogwarts Express leaves!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SecondsLeftToJoin">
    <!-- 0 - remaining seconds (number) -->
    <value>You have {0} seconds left before the Hogwarts Express leaves!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NotEnoughPlayers">
    <value>Too few wizards went to Hogwarts, and the year was filled with boring classes. Booooo, no fun for the wizards!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="StartingGameWait">
    <value>The school year at Hogwarts is beginning, please wait while I, the Sorting Hat, distribute your assignments.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ChangeNameToJoin">
    <!-- 0 - Player name -->
    <value>{0}, the Sorting Hat does not recognize you, please change your name to participate in the selection.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerLimitReached">
    <value>I'm so sorry, the classes are now full of wizards and Hogwarts can no longer accept anymore students!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerJoined">
    <!-- 0 - Player name -->
    <!-- 1 - current players -->
    <!-- 2 - Minimum players -->
    <!-- 3 - Maximum players -->
    <value>{0} has boarded the Hogwarts Express. There are currently {1} students, and there's a minimum of {2} students and a maximum of {3}.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PMTheBot">
    <!-- 0 - Player name -->
    <!-- 1 - bot username -->
    <value>{0} Please, send an owl for private ({1}) saying start, as it is not yet enrolled in Hogwarts. So that I can send you private owls, you must send me an owl you first.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DeadFlee">
    <value>How does a corpse flee when it's already a corpse? YOU ARE NOW A GHOST! Your only job is to roam around the halls of the castle.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Flee">
    <!-- 0 - Player name -->
    <value>{0} decided that Hogwarts was not worth it!</value>
	<value>{0} has ripped out the acceptance letter from Hogwarts!</value>
	<value>{0} has returned home!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerRoleWas">
    <!-- 0 - Player name -->
    <!-- 1 - Player role -->
    <value>{0} was {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CountPlayersRemain">
    <!-- 0 - Number of players -->
    <value>{0} remaining wizards in Hogwarts.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NotPlaying">
    <value>It seems you have not bought a ticket for the Hogwarts Express ...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NoPlayerName">
    <value>The Sorting Hat couldn't seem to find out who you are.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolfVotedKill">
    <!-- 0 - wolf teammate name -->
    <!-- 1 - Victim name -->
    <value>{0} has voted to cast an Avada Kedavra to {1}.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerVotedLynch">
    <!-- 0 - Voter name -->
    <!-- 1 - Target name -->
    <value>{0} has pointed their wand to {1} to vote for them to be sent to Azkaban.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="IdleKill">
    <!-- 0 - player name -->
    <!-- 1 - player role -->
    <value>{0} has not voted for 2 nights in a row.  The forces of good judged this as a deed of a tenebrous wizard and they suddenly fall, dead. {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="TraitorTurnWolf">
    <value>Realizing that all the Death Eaters are gone, fear rises into you and you decided to avenge the Dark Lord. You are now a Death Eater!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ChoiceAccepted">
    <value>Choice accepted.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="BeholderSeer">
    <!-- 0 - seer name -->
    <value>\nYou peeked through the Divination Class, only to see {0} as Sybill Trelawney 👳.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ApprenticeNowSeer">
    <!-- 0 - seer name -->
    <value>{0} was Sybill Trelawney 👳. As Ginny Weasley 🙇, you take the crystal ball and you become the substitute teacher for Divination class.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="BeholderNewSeer">
    <!-- 0 - apprentice name -->
    <!-- 1 - seer name -->
    <value>{0} was Ginny Weasley 🙇, and has taken the crystal ball to fill {1}'s place to substitute Professor Sybill Trelawney 👳! </value>
  </string>
  <string key="SeerSees">
    <!-- 0 - player name -->
    <!-- 1 - player role -->
    <value>The crystal ball reveals {0} as {1}!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskLynch">
    <value>Who do you want to banish to Azkaban?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskDetect">
    <value>Whose Invisibility Cloak shall you unveil?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskShoot">
    <!-- 0 - bullet count -->
    <value>Who do you want to cast a Sectumsempra on? {0} spell (s) remain.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskVisit">
    <value>Whose bedroom would you like to pay a visit to?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskSee">
    <value>Who shall you use the crystal ball on?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskGuard">
    <value>Who do you want to cast Protego on?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskEat">
    <value>Who do you want to cast Avada Kedavra on?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskHunt">
    <value>Who would you like to investigate with your Patronus?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskRoleModel">
    <value>Who is your example to follow?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskConvert">
    <value>Who would you like to kiss to death and substitute for a Dementor?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DiscussWith">
    <!--Leave the leading spaces here please-->
    <!-- 0 - teammate names -->
    <value>  Make sure you discuss with {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="And">
    <!--this is paired with "DiscussWith".  again, leave the spaces!-->
    <value> and </value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoCursed">
    <value>You are Dolores Umbridge 😾, the most annoying teacher to walk the school grounds, and you are greatly disliked by the students. Due to the lack of favors, you cursed yourself with a hidden spell! If the Death Eaters make physical contact with you, a dark mark appears and you will become one of them.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoDetective">
    <value>You are Hermione Granger 🕵️, the fighter and the smartest student of Hogwarts. During the day, you may choose a Wizard to follow through the school and unveil their Invisibility cloak. However, be wary of the Death Eaters, they could find out what you're doing! (40% chance)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoDrunk">
    <value>Congrats! You are Horace Slughorn 🍻! You put potions in the wrong bottles and end up drinking them. If the Death Eaters attack you, they will feel the effects of your potions and they will not be able to attack anyone the next night.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoGuardianAngel">
    <value>You are Lily J. Potter 👼, the defender of Hogwarts. Each night, you may choose a wizard to protect with Protego. However, if you choose a Death Eater, there is a 50% chance you will die.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoGunner">
    <value>You are Sirius Black 🔫. You have only two spells that are your strongest. During the day, you may choose to cast a Sectumsempra to another wizard. Everyone will hear the screams of agony and will know you are Sirius Black (not a Death Eater).</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoHarlot">
    <value>You are Cho Chang 💋. You are one of the most courted witches. With all these wizards waiting for your reply, you wonder what it was about you that strikes them to fall onto their knees for you (literally too). Therefore, you would prepare a Veritaserum potion, a powerful truth serum, and visit their chambers one by one, unaware that you may or may not be killed if you visit a Death Eater or Grindelwald.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoTraitor">
    <value>You are Peter Pettigrew 🖕, the great traitor! For now, you are an animagus living clandestinely like a mouse, but once all the Death Eaters are dead, you will reveal yourself as one of them. If Sybill Trelawney or Ginny Weasley looks at you, you may or may not be identified by them as a Death Eater.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoWolf">
    <value>With the mark on your arm, you are a DEATH EATER 🐺! Fantastic! During the night you can choose a Wizard to torture and kill, along with your fellow Death Eaters.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoSeer" >
    <value>You are Sybill Trelawney 👳, the Professor of Divination. With your crystal ball, you are able to see the life of a Wizard. Be very wary, however, the Death Eaters will show no mercy when they find you!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoVillager" >
    <value>You are a simple Wizard 👱, condemned to spend your days studying spells and waiting to be killed by the Death Eaters. Once a day you can vote for someone to send to Azkaban, use your vote wisely.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoTanner" >
    <value>You are Mykew Gregorovitch 👺! Already fearing the Dark Lord and Grindelwald, you tried your best to commit suicide, only to fail several times. The only way to succeed now? Being banished to Azkaban.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoWildChild" >
    <value>You are Draco Malfoy 👶! Pick a wizard to be your example in life. - if they die, or they are sent to Azkaban, hate will dominate you and you will join the Death Eaters.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoBeholder" >
    <value>You are Ron Weasley 👁. You will know who your Professor for Divination Class is (and not some wannabe Professor like Argus Filch)- that is your only function. Use this to help your team, Hogwarts!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoApprenticeSeer" >
    <value>You are Ginny Weasley 🙇, the apprentice Divination Professor and a fighter of Hogwarts. If Professor Sybill Trelawney dies, you will take the crystal ball and substitute the Divination class. </value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoCultist" >
    <value>You are one of the terrifying Dementors 👤. During the night, you can choose someone to kiss, sucking away all their life force for them to become one of you. If all the remaining players at the end of the game are Dementors, they will rule all over Hogwarts!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoCultistHunter" >
    <value>The Dementors are at Hogwarts trying to inhale all souls and spread fear and sadness. You are Remus Lupin 💂, a powerful wizard! During the night you can use the Patronus spell to investigate a Wizard. If they are a Dementor, they will no longer dare to come close to Hogwarts. If the dementors attack you, the weaker Dementor will run away in fear.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="LynchTime" >
    <!-- 0 - number of seconds -->
    <value>The night approaches and the wizards at Hogwarts meet to decide who will go to Azkaban today ... Everyone now has {0} seconds to point their wands!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DayTime" >
    <!-- 0 - number of seconds -->
    <value>Dawn arrives at Hogwarts. You now have {0} seconds to make your accusations / defenses / discuss.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NightTime" >
    <!-- 0 - number of seconds -->
    <value>Night has fallen. Everyone falls into a trance, wearied by the happenings of a stressful day. Wizards, you have {0} seconds to cast your spells!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="LynchKill" >
    <!-- 0 - player name -->
    <!-- 1 - player role -->
    <value>Amid doubts and suspicions, the wizards point their wands to one sole being! {0}, {1}, has been sent to Azkaban.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="LynchTie" >
    <value>Unable to reach a final decision on who to banish, the restless wizards return to their bedrooms, frustrated ...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NoLynchVotes" >
    <value>Seems everyone was more focused on practicing their spells or doing homework, so no one voted. That stinks.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DetectiveEaten" >
    <!-- 0 - victim name -->
    <value>A shriek echoes through the halls! Teachers rushed to see what was the commotion, only to cry as one of their brightest pupils lay on the floor with their pool of blood in the middle of an empty classroom. Hermione Granger 🕵, {0}, is now in the afterlife.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardianEaten" >
    <!-- 0 - victim name -->
    <value>A few students entered the Astronomy Tower, hoping to meet their professor. However, they were met with a ghost with broken wings and missing arms. Lily J. Potter 👼, {0}, smiled bleakly, before fading away, leaving the students confused.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GunnerEaten" >
    <!-- 0 - victim name -->
    <value>The Killing Curse was thrown, squarely on the chest of a man with great magic abilities. He lost his balance, and sends himself through the Veil, and to his death. Sirius Black 🔫, {0}, may no longer return from the land of the dead.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SeerEaten" >
    <!-- 0 - victim name -->
    <value>Students and teachers wake up to the news of Sybill Trelawney 👳, {0}, dead on top of a spell table, tarot cards scattered on the floor and the crystal ball lying in a corner of the room. Goodbye Professor Trelawney, may you rest in peace (and not the thought of the Grim surrounding your head).</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DrunkEaten" >
    <!-- 0 - victim name -->
    <value>So many potions in the house, only to have them get mixed and ended up burning the entire house, along with Horace Slughorn 🍻, {0}, in it. This is what happens when you make too many potions and not use them for good. Refrain from drinking potions kids!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="FoolEaten" >
    <!-- 0 - victim name -->
    <value>As the sun rises over Hogwarts, students find {0} lying on top of a used table, WITH A SNOW SPHERE AND A MOP ????? HAHAHAHA, THAT WANNABE PROFESSOR. {0} was Argus Filch 🃏!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DefaultEaten" >
    <!-- 0 - victim name -->
    <!-- 1 - victim role -->
    <value>As everyone gets up to do their daily tasks, they smell something horrible. They follow the smell to find {0} quartered in the forest, killed by a terrible forbidden spell. AVADA KEDAVRA. {1}.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterKilledCultist">
    <!-- 0 - victim name -->
    <value>Teachers were wondering why {0} did not attend their classes today, so they sent a student to check on their chambers. Upon entering their chambers, nothing seems out of the ordinary, except for the room to be lighter and the presence of {0}. It's clear that Remus Lupin has conjured his Patronus, sending a Dementor 👤 back to Azkaban.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NoAttack" >
    <value>Morning rises. Students and teachers gather in the Great Hall and breathe a sigh of relief - no deadly curses were thrown to anyone last night.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CursedBitten" >
    <value>You were attacked by the Death Eaters 🐺. Thanks to your self-inflicted curse, you have become a Death Eater!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolfTeam">
    <!-- 0 - teammate names -->
    <value>Your fellow Death Eaters 🐺 are: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CursedBittenToWolves" >
    <!-- 0 - victim name -->
    <value>{0} has been attacked ... but she was Dolores Umbridge 😾 and she became a Death Eater! Congratulations on your new partner! (I guess..)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolvesEatYou" isgif="true" >
    <value>Oh no! The Death Eaters 🐺 threw you the forbidden spell ... AVADA KEDAVRA!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolvesEatDrunk" >
    <!-- 0 - victim name -->
    <value>Oh no! {0} was Horace Slughorn 🍻! Now you are under the effects of his potions, and can't attack tomorrow night...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardWolf" >
    <value>You tried to protect a Death Eater 🐺, but they handed you an Avada Kedavra in return!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardSaved" >
    <!-- 0 - saved player name -->
    <value>Your Protego charm has saved {0}'s life!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardNoAttack" >
    <!-- 0 - player name -->
    <value>Sadly, there wasn't any effect with the Protego casted on {0}. Whoops.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardEmptyHouse">
    <!-- 0 - player name -->
    <value>You cast Protego on {0}, but wondered why they're not in their chambers. Hmm...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardSavedYou" >
    <value>Lily J. Potter 👼 was taking care of you last night and her Protego charm worked! What a blessing!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotEaten" >
    <!-- 0 - player name -->
    <value>Cho Chang 💋 was tired of visiting her courters every night, but choosing to stay in her chambers did no good either. {0} was attacked by the Death Eaters 🐺!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotNotHome" >
    <!-- 0 - player name -->
    <value>Strange ... {0} was not in the bedroom! No victim for you today ...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotFuckWolf" >
    <!-- 0 - player name -->
    <value>You visited {0}'s chambers and gave them the Veritaserum potion, only to be revealed that they are a Death Eater 🐺! You were about to run away, but sadly the Killing Curse was casted to you. Too bad, you're dead.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotFuckedWolfPublic" >
    <!-- 0 - player name -->
    <value>Whispers and gossips were spread to the halls, as they stared at the body of Cho Chang 💋, {0}, on the floor of the Main Hall and an empty bottle right next to her. Perhaps it was an unlucky night for her to visit a Death Eater 🐺.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotFuckedVictimPublic" >
    <!-- 0 - harlot name -->
    <!-- 1 - victim name -->
    <value>Cho Chang 💋, {0}, was about to enter {1}'s chambers, but only to realize that a Killing Curse was casted on {1}, and a Death Eater 🐺 was in their chambers! Before she could run, the figure turned to her and she was blinded by a bright flash of green ... Well, {0}'s dead too.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotVisitNonWolf" >
    <!-- 0 - target name -->
    <value>You perceive that {0} is not a Death Eater 🐺, since your kisses convinced them to drink the potion and reveal the truth!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotVisitYou" >
    <value>In the middle of the night, a Witch entered your bedroom and gave you something to drink in exchange for a kiss. You were too sleepy to recognise who it was, but her voice was so sweet that you couldn't resist answering some of her questions. After the kiss, the witch went back to where she came from.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DetectiveCaught" >
    <!-- 0 - detective name -->
    <value>As you were in the middle of discussion, you saw a figure retreating. It's {0}, Hermione Granger 🕵️!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DetectiveSnoop" >
    <!-- 0 - target name -->
    <!-- 1 - target role -->
    <value>Your research proved that {0} is {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotShot" >
    <!-- 0 - gunner's name -->
    <!-- 1 - Harlot's name -->
    <value>Feeling disgusted, Sirius Black 🔫, {0}, decided to cast Sectumsempra on Cho Chang 💋! It seems that {0} didn't quite enjoy her visit! {1} is dead.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DefaultShot" >
    <!-- 0 - Gunner's name -->
    <!-- 1 - target name -->
    <!-- 2 - Target's revealed name ( Target was a role) -->
    <value>Suddenly, a spell is triggered. The students looked to see {0}, who is Sirius Black 🔫, standing by the body of {1}, wand still pointed towards their head. {2}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolfWins" isgif="true" >
    <value>The Death Eater 🐺 has won!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolvesWin" isgif="true" >
    <value>The Death Eaters 🐺 have won!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="VillageWins" isgif="true" >
    <value>The wizards won! All the Death Eaters have perished ...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="TannerWins" isgif="true" >
    <value>Oh no! You have sent Mykew Gregorovitch 👺 to Azkaban! He has won the game.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RemainingPlayersEnd">
    <value>Remaining players, roles and faction:</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultistVotedConvert" >
    <!-- 0 - Voter's name -->
    <!-- 1 - target name -->
    <value>{0} has voted to replace {1} with a Dementor.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultConvertCultHunter">
    <!-- 0 - Youngest Cultist (killed)'s name' -->
    <!-- 1 - CultHunter's name -->
    <value>{0} was sent to give the kiss of death and replace {1} with a Dementor ... However, he was Remus Lupin 💂, and had a great way to ward off the Dementors! {0} has returned to Azkaban.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultHunterKilledCultVisit">
    <!-- 0 - Youngest Cultist's name -->
    <!-- 1 - Number of cultists left -->
    <value>{0} went to your office last night, ready to administer the kiss of death and replace you ... But you had a great way to protect yourself. One of the Dementors 👤 returned to Azkaban ... {1} Dementor(s) remaining!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultConvertYou">
    <value>You received the kiss of death of a Dementor 👤 and was replaced by one of them. During the night, you can try to kiss them to death with your fellow Dementors and replace other wizards ...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultTeam">
    <!-- 0 - Number of cultists -->
    <value>Dementors: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultJoin">
    <!-- 0 - new cultist's name -->
    <value>{0} received the kiss of death and was replaced by a Dementor!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultVisitEmpty">
    <!-- 0 - Newest cultist's name -->
    <!-- 1 - target name -->
    <value>{0} was sent to give {1} the kiss of death ... But no one was in the chambers.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultWins" isgif="true">
    <value>All the Wizards have died and the only survivors are the Dementors 👤 ... The Dementors have won!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterVisitDead">
    <!-- 0 - target name -->
    <value>You went to investigate {0}, but when you got there you found only the feelings of sadness and ... is that candy? You returned to your chambers, candy in hand.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterFindCultist">
    <!-- 0 - target name -->
    <value>You invade {0}'s room and feel an air of sadness and depression. You know very well what to do on these occasions: invoke the Patronus enchantment.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterFailedToFind">
    <!-- 0 - target name -->
    <value>You enter the bedroom of {0} but do not feel empty and unhappy. {0} is not part of the Dementors ... Still ...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WildChildToWolves">
    <!-- 0 - Werechild's name -->
    <value>The amazing life example of {0} has just died. In rage, he has become a Death Eater 🐺!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WildChildTransform">
    <!-- 0 - role's name -->
    <!-- 0 - teammates' names -->
    <value>You saw your role model, {0}, die before you. Alas, hatred seeps their way in and you turned to the Death Eater's side. Your new teammates are: {1}</value>
  </string>
  <!-- Villager, Drunk, Harlot, Seer, Traitor, GuardianAngel, Detective, Wolf, Cursed, Gunner, Tanner, Fool, WildChild, Beholder, ApprenticeSeer, Cultist, CultistHunter-->
  <!-- Do NOT change the emoji's, even if you are translating werewolf in a non-standard mode! -->
  <string key="Villager">
    <value>a Wizard 👱</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Drunk">
    <value> Horace Slughorn 🍻</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Harlot">
    <value>Cho Chang 💋</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Seer">
    <value>Sybill Trelawney 👳</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Traitor">
    <value>Peter Pettigrew 🖕</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardianAngel">
    <value>Lily J. Potter 👼</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Detective">
    <value>Hermione Granger 🕵</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Wolf">
    <value>a Death Eater 🐺</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Cursed">
    <value>Dolores Umbridge 😾</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Gunner">
    <value>Sirius Black 🔫</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Tanner">
    <value>Mykew Gregorovitch 👺</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Fool">
    <value>Argus Filch 🃏</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WildChild">
    <value>Draco Malfoy 👶</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Beholder">
    <value>Ron Weasley 👁</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ApprenticeSeer">
    <value>Ginny Weasley 🙇</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Cultist">
    <value>a Dementor 👤</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultistHunter">
    <value>Remus Lupin 💂</value>
  </string>
  <!-- These are for the player list -->
  <string key="RanAway">
    <value>Ran away</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Dead">
    <value>💀 Dead</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Alive">
    <value>🙂 Alive</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayersAlive">
    <value>Wizards Alive</value>
  </string>
  <!-- New strings 4 MAY 2016-->
  <string key="Mason">
    <value>Dumbledore's Army 👷</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoMason">
    <value>You are a member of the Dumbledore Army 👷, a secret society of Wizards who came together to help Hogwarts against Death Eater attacks. If there are others from the Army, you will know their name. Otherwise, you will be a simple wizard.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MasonEaten">
    <!-- 0 - dead man's name -->
    <value>As everyone gets up during the morning, {0}'s body is found near the Room of Requirements, with their wand on their chest, broken in the middle and a notebook with some spells. One of the members of Dumbledore's Army 👷 has died.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MasonTeam">
    <value> Dumbledore's Army is formed by: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <!-- new strings May 6 2016-->
  <string key="CultTargetDead">
    <!-- 0 - Youngest cultists name -->
    <value>The most recent member of the Dementors runs to the room of {0} to give the kiss of death and replace them with a Dementor, but it finds instead disorder, blood and pieces ... The objective has been assassinated!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardBlockedWolf">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>The Death Eaters go to the quarter of {0} for the attack, but they are found with a high creature, elevated and surrounded by light, armed with a sword and a wand. Lily J. Potter 👼 comes out in defense of the target and, after a fight full of light effects, they return to their bedrooms defeated.</value>
  </string>
  <!-- new strings May 9 2016-->
  <string key="CultUnableToConvert">
    <!-- 0 - newest  -->
    <!-- 1 - target's name -->
    <value>{0} has been sent to give the coup de grace and replace {1} with a Dementor, but their Patronus was too strong. :(</value>
  </string>
  <!-- new string May 12 2016-->
  <string key="NameExists">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <!-- 1 - name -->
    <value>{1}, a wizard / witch with the name {0} has already joined the battle. Please change your name to enter Hogwarts.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotDiscoverCult">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>You went to the bedroom of {0} to kiss a little, but when you arrived you felt a feeling of emptiness, as if your soul left your body. On the return to the Room of Requirements you decide to eat a chocolate toad ...</value>
  </string>
  <!-- new string May 13 2016-->
  <string key="Was">
    <value>was</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GenericDeathNoReveal">
    <!-- 0 - Dead's name -->
    <value>As everyone gets up and leaves their rooms in the morning, they sense the absence of {0} ... When they check their bedroom, they find their body lifeless.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MasonConverted">
    <!-- 0 - mason's name -->
    <value>How strange ... {0} did not appear in the Room of Requirements this morning...</value>
  </string>
  <!-- new string May 16 2016-->
  <string key="FleeDisabled">
    <value>You try to escape, but you should know that this is not possible at Hogwarts. With the Death Eaters here, the exits are closed so NO ONE can run! Good luck with that!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="IsDead">
    <!-- used when gunner shoots a player -->
    <value>is dead</value>
  </string>

  <!-- MORE STRINGS May 16, 2016 -->
  <string key="AlreadyInGame">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>You are already in a game! ({0})</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NoGame">
    <value>There is no school year at Hogwarts at the moment. Start a new one with /startgame or start a chaos one with /startchaos</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GroupAdminOnly">
    <value>Only a Director can use this command.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NoSeer">
    <value>The Divination Professor is not in Hogwarts!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="TimesUp">
    <value>Time's up!</value>
  </string>
  <!-- new strings june 10 2016 -->
  <string key="RoleInfoCupid">
    <value>You are Luna Lovegood 🏹. Sent to Hogwarts with your Spectrespecs and the love potion of Amortentia, on the first night, you can chose two wizards to fall in love with each other for the entire school year. If one of them dies, the other will die of sorrow. After deciding the two lovebirds, you can go back to following your life as a simple Wizard, still watching and fawning over the romance of two wizards.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoDoppelganger">
    <value>You are Nymphadora Tonks 🎭, a Metamorphmagus capable of modifying your own appearance without the use of spells or potions. Choose a wizard and when he dies you assume their role at Hogwarts.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoHunter">
    <value>You are Harry Potter 🎯! Your wand is your lover and you are with her all the time - you even sleep with her. If you die, you can choose a wizard to kill. And if the Death Eaters visit you at night, you are not someone who would accept to die without a fight, but in the darkness, you can not choose who to kill and there is a chance you will miss.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoSerialKiller">
    <value>You are Gellert Grindelwald 🔪. You are alone and the other wizards are nothing but your toys. With fear instilled in your psychotic mind, you sent yourself out to start a collection of wizards, dead wizards. Prepare your Killing Curse~!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CupidChosen">
    <value>Whenever you have the chance, you would glance at {0} and swoon over their abilities. You two would always stick together, alive or dead. If your partner is killed or sent to Azkaban, you will accompany them, to be together, forever.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterLynchedChoice">
    <value>Hogwarts decided to send you to Azkaban! It's your last chance to use your beloved wand!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterNoChoiceLynched">
    <value>{0} tries to reach his wand while he is judged, but his fingers are tired and before reaching it, he is sent to Azkabán ...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterSkipChoiceLynched">
    <value>{0} pulls out his wand, and points to the crowd ... His shooter's eyes try to decide who he will take with him. But he accepts his end, alone ...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterKilledFinalLynched">
    <!-- 0 - hunter's name -->
    <!-- 1 - target's name -->
    <!-- 2 - target's role -->
    <value>Upon arrival in Azkaban, {0} pulls out his wand and, quick as a cobra, casts a spell on {1}! Harry Potter 🎯 yells the Disarming Charm to {1}, who is {2}, and they fall lifeless onto the ground.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterShotChoice">
    <value>You were mortally wounded! With your last breath, you can take a wizard with you ... Choose fast!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterNoChoiceShot">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>{0} was dealt a heavy blow, so much so that he could not even get his wand out, falling dead onto the floor ...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterSkipChoiceShot">
    <!-- 0 - hunter's name -->
    <value>{0}, as if the blood coming out of his belly was nothing, decides not to give his last spell, accepting his destiny ...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterKilledFinalShot">
    <!-- 0 - hunter -->
    <!-- 1 - target's name -->
    <!-- 2 - target's role -->
    <value>{0} falls to the ground, mortally wounded ... But before dying, he pulls out his wand and casts a precise spell on {1}, falling hard on the ground, with a mark on his forehead. {2}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterShotWolfMulti">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>AAAAH! AAAH! Hogwarts trembled with the sounds of agony last night! The Death Eaters 🐺 have attacked the wrong person. Harry Potter 🎯 did not leave alone, he took a Death Eater {0} with him.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterShotWolf">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>The Death Eater 🐺 tried to attack the wrong person last night! Harry Potter knows how to protect himself very well, and has left a small gift for Hogwarts, the body of {0}!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SerialKillerKilledWolf">
    <value>The Death Eaters 🐺 tried to attack the wrong person last night! {0} is without his clothes hanging on the wall ... You can almost feel sorry for that Death Eater! It is as if Gellert Grindelwald 🔪 is giggling ...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DefaultKilled">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <!-- 1 - target's role -->
    <value>It seemed like a normal night, but where is {0}? Students gather in {0}'s room, and find their body floating in the bathtub full of blood ... It seems Gellert Grindelwald 🔪 had fun tonight ... {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardBlockedKiller">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>You went to have a little fun with {0}. But upon getting there, Lily J. Potter 👼 ended your fun! No jokes for the night ...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultConvertHunter">
    <!-- 0 - Youngest Cultist's name -->
    <!-- 1 - target's name -->
    <value>The Dementors command {0} to kiss {1} till their death and replace them with a Dementor. Arriving there, {0} was greeted with an Expelliarmus followed by a Sectumsempra that was shot right into their chest! {0} is dead...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultConvertSerialKiller">
    <!-- 0 - Youngest Cultist's name -->
    <!-- 1 - target's name -->
    <value>{0} sneaks over to {1}'s room, pops open the door, and is immediately greeted by a crazed maniac with a knife!!! {1} attempts to plunge the knife deep into {0}'s organs in alphabetical order, cackling the entire time! {0}, being a Dementor 👤, is unscathed, but being frightened by Grindelwald 🔪, they have decided to return to Azkaban.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardKiller">
    <value>You tried to protect the wrong wizard. Gellert Grindelwald 🔪 invites you to be the guinea pig of a terrible experiment. The kind of experiment that you die in the end ...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotFuckKiller">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>You visited the bedroom of {0} to have a little fun. But that night, only {0} is going to have fun with you, while he was throwing a Crucio on his body. You died, but if it's any consolation, you probably had a lot of fun!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotFuckKillerPublic">
    <value>{0} visited the wrong bedroom, what was to be a night of kisses and fun turned into a terrifying ordeal, but at least Gellert Grindelwald 🔪 had a lot of fun.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGToMason">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>{0}, Nymphadora Tonks 🎭, has become a member of Dumbledore's Army, just like you!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGTransformToMason">
    <!-- 0 - dead mason's name -->
    <!-- 1 - mason colleagues' names -->
    <value>{0} has died, and you become a member of Dumbledore's Army 👷.  Your teammates (if any) are: {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGToCult">
    <!-- 0 - new cultist's name -->
    <value>{0}, Nymphadora Tonks 🎭, was replaced by a Dementor.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGTransformToCult">
    <!-- 0 - role's name -->
    <!-- 1 - teammates' names -->
    <value>With {0} dead, you accept your fate, and join the Dementors 👤. Your new partners (if any) are: {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGToWolf">
    <!-- 0 - DG's name -->
    <value>{0}, Nymphadora Tonks 🎭, became a Death Eater. One more for the clan!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGTransformToWolf">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <!-- 1 - teammates' names -->
    <value>{0} has died, and you transform into a Death Eater 🐺! Your teammates (if any) are: {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SerialKillerWins" isgif="true">
    <value>The only survivor was Gellert Grindelwald 🔪! He certainly has had a lot of fun with his jokes, especially when they involved killing all of you!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskKill">
    <value>Who do you want to kill tonight?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="LoverDied">
    <!-- 0 - dead's name -->
    <!-- 1 - lover's name -->
    <!-- 2 - roles -->
    <value>{0} gives their last breath, looking into their beloved's eyes, {1}, who holds their body on their knees. {1} can not stand the pain, and, with a wand, casts an Avada Kedavra on themselves... They will be together, even in the world of the dead. {2}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskDoppelganger">
    <value>Who do you want to become if they get sent to Azkaban?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskCupid1">
    <value>Who do you want the lovebirds to be? Choose the first wizard.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskCupid2">
    <value>Who do you want the lovebirds to be? Choose the second wizard.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Hunter">
    <value>Harry Potter 🎯</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Cupid">
    <value>Luna Lovegood 🏹</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SerialKiller">
    <value>Gellert Grindelwald 🔪</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Doppelgänger">
    <value>Nymphadora Tonks 🎭</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NewWCRoleModel">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>You have become the Draco Malfoy. Your awesome life example is: {0}.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="LoversWin">
    <value>True love endures! That's what you wanted, right? Love always wins!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterKilledVisiter">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <!-- 1 - role -->
    <value>When everyone wakes up, they find {0} dead in the middle of the Great Hall, totally emaciated due to the Sectumsempra. It seems that someone visited Harry Potter 🎯 and it went wrong! {1}.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultAttempt">
    <value>In the middle of the night you feel a sadness, a void, as if your happiness was unburdening. You use your patronus, and the feeling subsides.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AlreadyOnWaitList">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>You are already on the wait list for {0}.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AddedToWaitList">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>We're glad to announce that your application for the Hogwarts school has been sent. We will let you know when a new school year begins! You will depart for Hogwarts in {0}. \nYours Sincerely, Professor McGonagall.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NotifyNewGame">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>A new year at Hogwarts is starting in {0}.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SerialKillerWinsOverpower">
    <!-- 0 - SK's name -->
    <!-- 1 - target's name -->
    <value>Morning arrives at Hogwarts and only two wizards remain at the school. {0} looks at {1}, a sinister smile on his face. He removes his wand and throws a Crucio, playing with {1} until he decides to use the third unforgivable curse on them. They are as good as dead.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NoWinner" isgif="true">
    <value>Everyone at Hogwarts has been sent to Azkaban ... No one won that battle.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SKHunterEnd">
    <!-- 0 - SK's name -->
    <!-- 1 - Hunter's name -->
    <value>The sun rises on the horizon, {0} and {1} are the only survivors. {0} approaches {1} smiling, and invites him to a joke. {1}, fast as thunder, pulls out his wand and casts a deadly spell on {0}. {0}, with his last breath, uses an Avada Kedavra on {1}. They both die, the day is over. No winner prevails to tell the tale ...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleModelChosen">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>You failed to make a choice, so the Gods have chosen your awesome life example for you: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Won">
    <value>Won</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Lost">
    <value>Lost</value>
  </string>
  <string key="IdleCount">
    <!-- 0 - player's name -->
    <!-- 1 - idle count -->
    <value>The wizard {0} has been sent to Azkaban for not voting {1} times in the past 24 hours.</value>
  </string>
  <!--New strings 7th of July-->
  <!--If you are translating werewolf in a non-standard mode (eg. Mafia, Pokémon and similar) please put the role and the emoji in front of the string.
  For example in Mafia, AboutMason would be:
  Caporegime 👷\nYou are a caporegime blah blah
  -->
  <string key="AboutVG">
    <value>You are a simple wizard 👱, condemned to spend his days studying / teaching at Hogwarts waiting to be killed by the Death Eaters, his enemies. Once a day you can vote for someone to send to Azkaban, use your vote wisely.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutSeer">
    <value>You are Sybill Trelawney 👳, the Professor of Divination. With your crystal ball, you are able to see the life of a Wizard. Be very wary, however, the Death Eaters will show no mercy when they find you!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutWw">
    <value>YOU ARE A DEATH EATER 🐺!! Great! During the night you can choose a wizard to torture and kill, along with your clan, the Death Eaters.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutHarlot">
    <value>You are Cho Chang 💋. You are one of the most courted witches. With all these wizards waiting for your reply, you wonder what it was about you that strikes them to fall onto their knees for you (literally too). Therefore, you would prepare a Veritaserum potion, a powerful truth serum, and visit their chambers one by one, unaware that you may or may not be killed if you visit a Death Eater or Grindelwald.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutDrunk">
    <value>You drunken bastard! Congratulations, you're Horace Slughorn 🍻! You put potions in the wrong bottles and end up drinking them. If the Death Eaters attack you, they will feel the effects of your potions and they will not be able to attack anyone the next night.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutCursed">
    <value>You are Dolores Umbridge 😾, you have been cursed. For now you are a simple teacher of Hogwarts, but if you are tortured by the Death Eaters, you will receive the dark mark and become a Death Eater yourself.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutTraitor">
    <value>You are Peter Pettigrew 🖕, the great traitor! For now, you are an animagus living clandestinely like a mouse, but once all the Death Eaters are dead, you will reveal yourself as one of them. If the Divination Professor or Ginny Weasley looks at you, you may or may not be identified by them as a Death Eater.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutGA">
    <value>You are Lily J. Potter 👼, and your role is to protect Hogwarts. During the night, you can choose a wizard to protect, even if it means losing your life.
However, if you protect a Death Eater, you may have a fate worse than death.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutDetective">
    <value>You are Hermione Granger 🕵️, the fighter and the smartest student of Hogwarts. During the day, you may choose a Wizard to follow through the school and unveil their Invisibility cloak. However, be wary of the Death Eaters, they could find out what you're doing! (40% chance)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutGunner">
    <value>You are Sirius Black 🔫. You have 2 spells to help Hogwarts. During the day, you can throw a Sectumsempra to someone. Everyone will hear the cries of agony from the victim and they will know you are Sirius Black.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutTanner">
    <value>You are Mykew Gregorovitch 👺! Already fearing the Dark Lord and Grindelwald, you tried your best to commit suicide, only to fail several times. The only way to succeed now? Being banished to Azkaban</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutFool">
    <value>Argus Filch 🃏 says he is a wizard ... But when he casts a spell, nothing happens. Argus Filch says he's a teacher, but what he does is mop the floors of Hogwarts... He's just a wannabe.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutCult">
    <value>You are one of the Dementors 👤. During the night, you can choose someone to kiss, sucking away all their life force for them to become one of you. If all the remaining players at the end of the game are Dementors, they will rule all over Hogwarts!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutCH">
    <value>The Dementors are at Hogwarts trying to inhale all happiness and spread fear and sadness, and you, Remus Lupin 💂, must defend the school! During the night you can use the patronus spell to investigate a Wizard. If he (it) is a Dementor, he / she dies. If the dementors attack you, the weaker Dementor will die.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutWC">
    <value>You are Draco Malfoy 👶! Choose someone to be your awesome life example - if he / she dies or is sent to Azkaban, hatred will dominate you and you will join the Death Eaters.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutAppS">
    <value>You are Ginny Weasley 🙇, the Apprentice of Divination, and fight for Hogwarts. If Sybill Trelawney is no longer, she will take her place as Professor.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutBH">
    <value>You are Ron Weasley 👁. You will know who is the true Professor of Divination (and not Argus Filch). Use this to help your team, Hogwarts!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutMason">
    <value>You are a member of the Dumbledore's Army 👷, a secret society of wizards that came together to defend Hogwarts from Death Eater attacks. If there are others from the Army, you will know their names. Otherwise, you will be a simple wizard.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutDG">
    <value>You are Nymphadora Tonks 🎭, a metamorphmagus capable of modifying your own appearance without the use of spells or potions. Choose a wizard and when they die, you assume their role at Hogwarts.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutCupid">
    <value>
      Oh, how you love romance! You are Luna Lovegood 🏹, you will choose two players at the start of the game. These two players will become madly in love! If one of them dies, the other will die of sorrow :(
      Note: Lovers will know who each other are, but not be told their roles. If the lovers are the last two alive, they win, regardless of teams. If the lovers are on different teams (Hogwarts + Death Eater), and one team wins (Death Eater), the lover (Hogwarts) wins as well. TL;DR if at least one of the lovers was on the winning team, they both win together.
      </value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutHunter">
    <value>
      YOU'RE A WIZARD, HARRY! You are Harry Potter 🎯, a strong Half-Blood Wizard who, for some odd reason, has an obsession with his wand. In your head, you tend to think that everyone is after your wand, so you would cast a spell  to prevent them from getting your wand. If the Death Eaters come after you, you may or may not be able to reverse their Killing Curse, so you may or may not be dead. If you die though, you are allowed to cast your last spell onto someone. Note: For wolf attacks, the chance starts at 30%. If there is one wolf, the hunter has a 30% chance to kill the wolf (and survive). For each additional wolf, add 20% (2 wolves = 50%, 3 = 70%, etc). However - if there are multiple wolves, while you may kill one of them, you will still be outnumbered and killed. If the cult tries to convert you, they have a 50% chance to fail. If they fail, you have a 50% chance to kill one of them!
    </value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutSK">
    <value>Having escaped Nurmengard, Gellert Grindelwald 🔪 has decided that the world is too boring... Why jail people when you can torture them? To remedy this, he's going to make the world a little more "fun"... And don't talk to him about working together with someone, because the last time he did, well, let's just say his friend ended up jailing him...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutPara">
    <value>Para is a silly developer that likes to bark at people.  Maybe he's been messing with werewolves too long....Messing with werewolves is a very bad idea.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="EndTime">
    <value>Game Length: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <!--New strings, July the 8th -->

  <string key="Day">
    <!--0 - Day -->
    <value>Day {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NodeShutsDown">
    <value>An error has occurred, and this node has shut down :/</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SentPrivate">
    <value>I have sent you a PM</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WhatToDo">
    <value>What would you like to do?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="JoinFromGroup">
    <value>You must join a game from within a group chat!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="StartFromGroup">
    <value>You must start a game from within a group chat!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PingInfo">
    <value>Time to receive ping message: {0}\nMessages per second: {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WhatLang">
    <value>What Language?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WhatVariant">
    <value>What Variant?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="LangSet">
    <value>Language set to {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GetLang">
    <value>Get which language file?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NoNodes">
    <value>There are no nodes online right now, please try again in a few seconds</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GroupCommandOnly">
    <value>You must run this command in a group</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NotGlobalAdmin">
    <value>You aren't a global admin...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NotPara">
    <value>You aren't Para!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Yes">
    <value>Yes</value>
  </string>
  <string key="No">
    <value>No</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Allow">
    <value>Allow</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Disallow">
    <value>Disallow</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Show">
    <value>Show</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Hide">
    <value>Hide</value>
  </string>
  <!-- Game Mode Choices-->
  <string key="NormalOnly">
    <value>Normal Only</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ChaosOnly">
    <value>Chaos Only</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerChoice">
    <value>Player Choice</value>
  </string>

  <!-- Show Roles on End Game -->
  <string key="ShowNone">
    <value>Don't show any</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShowLiving">
    <value>Show only living players</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShowAll">
    <value>Show all players</value>
  </string>

  <string key="Cancel">
    <value>Cancel</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowFleeQ">
    <value>Do you want to allow fleeing once the game has started?\nNote: players can still flee during join phase\nCurrent: {0} fleeing</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowFleeA">
    <value>{0} fleeing after game start</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MaxPlayersQ">
    <value>How many players would like to set as the maximum?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MaxPlayersA">
    <value>Max players set to {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShowRolesDeathQ">
    <value>Show or Hide roles on death?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShowRolesDeathA">
    <value>Roles will be {0} on death.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GameModeQ">
    <value>What game mode will the group be?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GameModeA">
    <value>Game mode set to {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShowRolesEndQ">
    <value>How do you want roles to be shown at the end?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShowRolesEndA">
    <value>Roles shown at end set to: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SetDayTimeQ">
    <value>Choose the base time (in seconds) for day time. This will still be modified based on number of players.\nDefault setting: {0}\nCurrent: {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SetDayTimeA">
    <value>Base day time set to {0} seconds</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SetNightTimeQ">
    <value>Choose the time (in seconds) for night time. Default setting: {0}\nCurrent:{1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SetNightTimeA">
    <value>Night time set to {0} seconds</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SetLynchTimeQ">
    <value>Choose the time (in seconds) for lynch voting. Default setting: {0}\nCurrent:{1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SetLynchTimeA">
    <value>Lynch voting time set to {0} seconds</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowFoolQ">
    <value>Allow fool as a role option?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowFoolA">
    <value>Fool as a role set to: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowTannerQ">
    <value>Allow tanner as a role option?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowTannerA">
    <value>Tanner as a role set to: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowCultQ">
    <value>Allow cult as a role option?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowCultA">
    <value>Cult as a role set to: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="EnableSecretLynchQ">
    <value>Enable Secret Lynch?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="EnableSecretLynchA">
    <value>Enabling of secret Lynch set to: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThankYou">
    <value>Thank you, have a good day :)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WhatLangGroup">
    <value>What language do you want to look for a group to play in?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HereIsList">
    <value>Here are the groups for {0}:</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Members">
    <value>Members</value>
  </string>
  <string key="StartMe">
    <value>Please start me so I can PM you</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerNoPM">
    <value>{0} failed to start the bot, and has been removed from the game!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="LatestList">
    <value>Here is the latest list</value>
  </string>
  <string key="UnableToGetList">
    <value>Unable to get latest list</value>
  </string>
  <string key="YouJoined">
    <!-- 0 - Group Name -->
    <value>You have successfully joined the game in {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Ping2">
    <value>Time to send ping message: {0}</value>
  </string>

  <!-- Update 4.0-->
  <string key="RoleInfoMayor">
    <value>You are Minister Cornelius Oswald Fudge 🎖, the Most Stylish Wizard of the Year. You have such powerful words to make sure someone is going to Azkaban, because your words are worth twice as normal! But that's after you grab your shiny Silver Pocket Watch and make an announcement.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoPrince">
    <value>All teachers are very wary of your presence, every students fear you, probably except for the Slytherin house, for you are none other than the Half-Blood Prince, Severus Snape 👑. If the wizards start speculating you for murder, you will not be banished to Azkaban because they will be threatened to have their house points deducted (especially Gryffindor's).</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoClumsyGuy">
    <value>You are Neville Longbottom 🤕, the wizard with immense amount of clumsiness! You tend to trip on your feet, fiddle around with your wand, and fall asleep on your breakfast. When you vote to send someone to Azkaban, you have a 50% chance that your wand will point to a different wizard!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoSorcerer">
    <value>Sneaking from behind, you are Antonin Dolohov 🔮, the one who tortured countless Muggles and non-supporters of the Dark Lord! After escaping from Azkaban, every night you will use your Dark Mark to find the Death Eaters or Professor Sybill Trelawney to give her to the Dark Lord. You win along with the Death Eaters, so just play hide and seek before someone sent you to Azkaban again.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoBlacksmith">
    <value>You are the famous Wandmaker, Garrick Ollivander ⚒. You have a small wandshop in the village, but who knows, some are powerful enough to prevent the Death Eaters from attacking for one night. During the day, you can choose to raise your wand and cast Protective Enchantments around the village. Other than that, you are just a common wizard.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoAlphaWolf">
    <value>You are Lord Voldemort ⚡️, also known as the Dark Lord, He-Who-Shall-Not-Be-Named, a very menacing Wizard that will cast Avada Kedavra to those who stands in his way. However, you have 20% chance to take a liking towards a PUREBLOOD Wizard WITH exceptional magic abilities.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoWolfCub">
    <value>You are Lucius Malfoy 🐶, the youngest Death Eater (and very favored by the Dark Lord too). You have unaccountable power, and without that the Death Eaters would be nothing. If you die, Voldemort and his army would rage and cast the Killing Curse to two Wizards.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PrinceLynched">
     <value>The wizards pointed their wands at one person, but then trembled in fear. {0} claimed that he is the Half-Blood Prince 👑. Instantly, everyone started to pack their things and rush their way to their next class, knowing that there will be dire consequences for them if they don't.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SorcererOther">
    <value>Raising your wand to look at {0}, you conjure ropes from your wand, but they hit you with a Silencing Charm! You can't do nothing but escape, with no information... But they aren't Death Eaters or Sybill for sure!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MayorReveal">
    <value>{0} steps forward, grabs his shiny Silver Pocket Watch and points his wand at his neck while muttering Sonorus. "He's back!", {0} declares, fiddling a little with his bowler hat, signalling that danger is coming. From now on, {0}' s votes for sending an Accused to Azkaban will count twice.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskMayor">
    <value>Click Reveal whenever you are ready to grab your pocket watch and announce your words as Minister Fudge.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Reveal">
    <value>Reveal</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SpreadDust">
    <value>Would you like to cast Protective Enchantments today, disabling the Death Eaters tonight?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="BlacksmithSpreadSilver">
    <value>As Hogwarts debates over the events, they suddenly notice {0} wandering around casting Protective Enchantments around the village nearby. For now, at least, Hogwarts and Hogsmead will be safe from Death Eaters attacks. (Death Eaters are disabled tonight.)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Mayor">
    <value>Minister Cornelius Fudge 🎖</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Prince">
    <value>Severus Snape 👑</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Sorcerer">
    <value>Antonin Dolohov 🔮</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ClumsyGuy">
    <value>Neville Longbottom 🤕</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Blacksmith">
    <value>Garrick Ollivander ⚒</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AlphaWolf">
    <value>Lord Voldemort ⚡️</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolfCub">
    <value>Lucius Malfoy 🐶</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerBittenWolves">
    <value>As the Death Eaters raise their wands to cast Avada Kedavra on {0}, {1} stops everyone, being Lord Voldemort ⚡️. {1} tells the Death Eaters that {0} should join them instead, since they seem like a worthy pureblood, so the Death Eaters leave them alone.  Under Voldemort's really-threat-free coaxing (ahem), they will join the Death Eaters tomorrow night.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerBitten">
    <value>You were attacked by the Death Eaters, but Voldemort ⚡️ deemed you worthy to be one of them. Instead of being killed, you will join the Death Eaters tomorrow night ... or have your loved ones get killed off ...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="BittenTurned">
    <value>As night falls, you sigh, resigned to your fate. There's no way out of this. You get out of bed to join your fellow Death Eaters.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutMayor">
    <value>Good day, Minister Cornelius Fudge 🎖. As the Minister for Magic, you have great power to control every wizard. You only need to grab your pocket watch and raise your wand to make an announcement, so everyone will know who you are! Once you do this, you will be given twice the vote count for sending an Accused to Azkaban (meaning that your vote is twice as powerful as everyone else's). Use that power wisely to save everyone, and yourself too. Remember your slogan? A Fair Deal for Wizards Who Deal Fair with Muggles.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutPrince">
   <value>You are Severus Snape 👑, the Half-Blood Prince. If the wizards start speculating you for murder, you will not be banished to Azkaban because they will be threatened to have their house points deducted (especially Gryffindor's).</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutSorcerer">
    <value>Pale skin with dark hair, you are Antonin Dolohov 🔮, the Original Death Eater of Lord Voldemort. After fighting in the First Wizarding War, torturing so many Muggles, wizards and witches who were not supporters of the Dark Lord, you were caught and sent to Azkaban. However, after escaping and bearing the Dark Mark as a sign of your loyalty to the Dark Lord, you try to seek for the other Death Eaters or to find Professor Sybill Trelawney and give her to Dark Lord! </value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutClumsy">
    <value>You are Neville Longbottom 🤕, the wizard with an immense amount of clumsiness! You tend to trip on your feet, fiddle around with your wand, and fall asleep on your breakfast. To send someone to Azkaban, you only have a 50% chance that your wand will point to a different wizard!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutBlacksmith">
    <value>
      You are the famous Wandmaker, Garrick Ollivander ⚒. You know every single ingredient to make wands, from a hornbeam to a phoenix feather. Some of your ingredients are very special, and you can use these once to stop Death Eaters from killing any innocent Wizards for one night. (or just use a Protection Enchantments Charm too)
    </value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutAlphaWolf">
    <value>
      You are Lord Voldemort ⚡️, also known as the Dark Lord, He-Who-Shall-Not-Be-Named, a very menacing Wizard that will cast Avada Kedavra to those who stands in his way. However, you have 20% chance to take a liking towards a PUREBLOOD Wizard WITH exceptional magic abilities.
    </value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutWolfCub">
    <value>You are Lucius Malfoy 🐶, the youngest Death Eater (and very favored by the Dark Lord too). You have unaccountable power, and without that the Death Eaters would be nothing. If you die, Voldemort and his army would rage and cast the Killing Curse to two Wizards. </value>
  </string>

  <!-- new strings 06 nov-->
  <string key="DGTransformToAlpha">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <!-- 1 - teammates' names -->
    <value>{0} has died, and you transform into Voldemort ⚡️. Your teammates (if any) are: {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGTransformToWolfCub">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <!-- 1 - teammates' names -->
    <value>{0} has died, and you transform into Lucius Malfoy 🐶. Your teammates (if any) are: {1}</value>
  </string>

  <string key="VillageTeamEnd">
    <value>Village Team</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NeutralTeamEnd">
    <value>Neutral Team</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolfTeamEnd">
    <value>Wolf Team</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SerialKillerTeamEnd">
    <value>SK Team</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultTeamEnd">
    <value>Cult Team</value>
  </string>
  <string key="TannerTeamEnd">
    <value>Tanner Team</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultConvertWolf">
    <value>The Dementors send {0} to administer the Kiss on {1}, but instead, {0} disappears, seemingly sent back to Azkaban by the Death Eaters.</value> </string>

  <string key="HarlotFuckedKilledPublic">
    <!-- used when Harlot visit's SK's victim, and dies -->
    <!--{0} = Harlot name, {1} = SK's victim name-->
    <value>{0} slips into {1}'s room, her bottle of Veritaserum clutched in her hand, only to find Gellert Grindelwald 🔪 levitating {1} and making them hit the wall repeatedly! Grindelwald gives {0}, Cho Chang 💋, a grin, before forcing her to join his little "party"!</value>
  </string>


  <!--New Death Strings 05 DEC-->
  <string key="ApprenticeSeerEaten">
    <value>Hogwarts awakens to find {0} slumped lifelessly against the wall near the Divination classroom, clearly a victim to the Death Eaters' Killing Curse. Seems like the Death Eaters find Ginny Weasley 🙇 as much of a threat to them as Sybill Trelawney.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="BlacksmithKilled">
    <value>Seems like {0}, the resident wandmaker Garrick Ollivander ⚒, must have been extremely unlucky. {0}'s frail body looks as though it has been injured by spells, freshly casted from {0}'s wands, with some knives found plunged into his hands, feet and head, and pinned to the craftsman's table last night. Oh, look at his head! Maybe Gellert Grindelwald 🔪 did cast Crucio till his neck broke like that...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultistKilled">
    <value>Everyone seems to feel a little happier. {0} the Dementor 👤 seems to have ran back to Azkaban. Gellert Grindelwald 🔪 must have scared this poor Dementor out of their (non-existent) mind!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CupidKilled">
    <value>The next morning, Hogwarts was in shock to find {0} dead, her Spectrespecs smashed to smithereens, twinkling on the floor like ominous glitter. Luna Lovegood 🏹 may not have been the most popular person, but she definitely didn't deserve the death Gellert Grindelwald 🔪 gave her...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DrunkKilled">
    <value>A few Hogwarts students had hoped to meet {0} to request to join his Slug Club, but all they found in {0}'s room was his head in a glass bottle. Seems as if putting Horace Slughorn's 🍻 head in a glass bottle is Gellert Grindelwald's 🔪 idea of a good joke.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardianAngelKilled">
    <value>{0} would normally have managed to fight off Gellert Grindelwald 🔪, but Lily J. Potter's 👼 continued existence was only due to her ability to protect others, and not herself. {0} has finally left this world for good.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GunnerKilled">
    <value>Sirius Black 🔫 must have tired himself out after patrolling the Hogwarts corridors so much. It seems as if Gellert Grindelwald 🔪 has caught him sleeping soundly. {0}, usually an alert wizard, now lies dead, his blood pooling around him. Strangely, some areas within the pool are not covered by blood, forming a sinister smiley face...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MayorKilled">
    <value>Assassination! {0} the Minister of Magic 🎖 was found crushed, and neck broken... Someone must have entered the room and casted Avada Kedavra on him! Clearly it's Gellert Grindelwald 🔪 who missed out on the top spot only because You-Know-Who arrived! He demands a duel with the Dark Lord...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PrinceKilled">
     <value>A maniacal laugh echoed through the halls, announcing the death of the Half-Blood Prince. The wizards mourn, for they have lost their best professor, a great wizard, and friend. Severus Snape 👑, {0}, is gone.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SeerKilled">
    <value>Everyone thought Sybill Trelawney 👳 couldn't be killed by anyone, seeing how she could probably foresee their assassination attempts. However, Gellert Grindelwald 🔪 seems to have bypassed this, catching her off-guard. {0}'s lifeless body is found in a hog-tie, her crystal ball stuffed into her mouth.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SorcererEaten">
    <value>The sky suddenly turns into dark, the Dark Mark appears...Bloody hell, a mistake has been made. The Death Eaters took out soul from one of their own. {0}, alias Dolohov 🔮, is dead with empty soul.</value>
    <value>A scream were heard last night, Impediment Jinx mirrored and attacked his caster. They could see an exhumed body with a Dark Mark on his hand, belonging to {0}, alias Antonin Dolohov 🔮. The life of the Original Death Eater has ended...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WildChildEaten">
    <value>Shrieks were heard this morning, echoing throughout the corridors of Hogwarts. Seems like the Death Eaters have made a grave mistake by killing off one of their member's son, Draco Malfoy 👶, and are now receiving punishment for it! Alas, no amount of punishment can undo their mistake and bring {0} back...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SerialKillerKilledCH">
    <!--used when CH visits SK-->
    <value>Remus Lupin 💂 may have been a smart man, but even the intelligent can fall prey to Gellert Grindelwald's 🔪 "antics". {0}'s bedroom was broken into and spray-painted with his house colours, using - you guessed it - his own blood.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultConvertWolfPublic">
    <!--used when Cultists convert the wolves, only if wolves stayed home-->
    <value>Voldemort seems to have trained his followers well! Despite taking a day off from killing people, the Death Eaters 🐺 remained alert. {0}, a poor Dementor 👤, thought that they could catch a Death Eater off-guard, but no - they've been sent back to Azkaban.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultConvertKillerPublic">
    <!--used when Cultists convert the SK-->
    <value>The Dementors 👤 tried to give Gellert Grindelwald 🔪 the Kiss, but {0}, the newest member, was too spooked out by Grindelwald's so-called pranks and decided to return to Azkaban!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GAGuardedKiller">
    <!-- used when GA guards SK -->
    <value>Lily J. Potter 👼 tried to protect Gellert Grindelwald 🔪, hoping that this shot at life will let him change. After all, he was a friend of Dumbledore, was he not? Unfortunately, a leopard cannot change its spots. {0}'s attempt was futile and Grindelwald has erased her existence completely.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GAGuardedWolf">
    <!-- used when GA guards a wolf -->
    <value>Death Eaters 🐺 do not like being disturbed, even if the intruder means well. {0}, who is Lily J. Potter 👼, wanted to protect one of the Death Eaters from harm last night, but ended up leaving this world forever, thanks to a well-casted Dark spell.</value>
  </string>

  <!--1vs1 finales-->
  <string key="HunterKillsWolfEnd">
    <!--{0} = hunter's name, {1} = wolf's name-->
    <value>A Death Eater 🐺 thought that they could finally give their master what he wanted, but they were wrong. Harry Potter 🎯 proves to be very resistant against getting captured and {1} lies dead, {0} standing victoriously over him.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolfKillsHunterEnd">
    <!--{0} = hunter's name, {1} = wolf's name-->
    <value>The last Death Eater 🐺 has gotten tired of trying to capture Harry Potter 🎯 alive, knowing that their efforts will be futile. {1} casts a Killing Curse on {0}, knowing that his signature Expelliarmus can't save him. All hail Lord Voldemort.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CHKillsCultistEnd">
    <!--{0} = last cultist's name, {1} = CH's name -->
    <value>A feeling of sadness and dread envelopes {1}, undoubtedly the work of a Dementor 👤. Knowing only {0} was left in Hogwarts, Remus Lupin 💂 casts a Patronus charm, sending his Patronus towards {0}'s bedroom. A feeling of happiness and relief signals that his job here is done.</value>
  </string>

  <!-- Extend time -->
  <string key="SecondsAdded">
    <!-- 0 - Seconds added by /extend command -->
    <!-- 1 - Total seconds remaining -->
    <value>Join time extended by {0} seconds!\n{1} left to Join</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SecondsRemoved">
    <!-- 0 - Seconds removed by /extend command -->
    <!-- 1 - Total seconds remaining -->
    <value>Join time decreased by {0} seconds!\n{1} left to Join</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CantExtend">
    <value>Only group admins can extend the time more than once!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowExtendQ">
    <!--{0} = "Allow" / "Disallow" string-->
    <value>Allow players to extend join time?\nCurrent: {0} extending\nNote: Admins will always be able to extend</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowExtendA">
    <!--{0} = "Allow" / "Disallow" string-->
    <value>{0} players to extend join time</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MaxExtendQ">
    <value>Choose maximum number of seconds which can be added to joining timer by a single /extend command.\nDefault setting: {0}\nCurrent:{1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MaxExtendA">
    <value>Maximum extending time set to {0} seconds</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolvesEatDrunkBlockSecondKill">
    <value>{0}'s potions are a little too potent! Instead of attacking {1}, you and your teammates head back to bed to sleep off the effects of the potion.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="JoinButton">
    <value>Join</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NotMember">
    <value>You can't join this game because you don't seem to be a member of {0}.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="JoinByButton">
    <value>Please don't use the commands to join. Use this button instead.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerVoteCounts">
    <value>{0} players have voted, {1} total.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NoAutoJoin">
    <value>{0}, please remember that you will have to join with the button as well.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GroupNotFound">
    <!--This string might need rewording from some native speaker-->
    <value>Couldn't find the group. Please run this command in the group you want to stop waiting for, or add link, id, or username next to the command.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DeletedFromWaitList">
    <value>You have been deleted from the wait list for {0}.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HaveJoined">
    <!-- {0} = list of people who have joined -->
    <!-- NOTE: No space between {0} and joined. It will be added in the code if necessary-->
    <value>{0}joined the game in the last 30 seconds.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowCult">
    <value>Allow Cult</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowTanner">
    <value>Allow Tanner</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowFool">
    <value>Allow Fool</value>
  </string>
  <string key="EnableSecretLynch">
    <value>Enable Secret Lynch</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RandomMode">
    <value>Enable Random Mode</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowExtend">
    <value>Allow Extending Timer</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShowRolesDeath">
    <value>Show Roles on Death</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowFlee">
    <value>Allow Fleeing</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShowIDs">
    <value>Show IDs on joining</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShowIDsQ">
    <value>Show IDs of players while they join the game?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShowIDsA">
    <value>{0} IDs</value>
  </string>

  <string key="All">
    <!-- used when searching for groups in all the variants -->
    <value>All</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RandomModeQ">
    <value>Enable random mode?\nWhen random mode is enabled, Chaos, Secret Lynch, Show Roles on Death, and Allow Cult / Fool / Tanner will be randomly determined every time someone starts a game.\nCurrent:{0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RandomModeA">
    <value>Enabling of random mode set to: {0}</value>
  </string>

  <string key="AllowNSFW">
    <value>Allow NSFW Gif Packs</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowNSFWQ">
    <value>Allow players to have NSFW gif packs?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowNSFWA">
    <value>{0} NSFW Gifs</value>
  </string>

  <string key="TannerEnd">
    <!-- 0 - Tanner name -->
    <value>Gregorovitch 👺, free from Hogwarts at last! It was a waste of time staying here instead of doing research on properties of wand cores... {0} didn't even manage to see how Azkaban was like! How disappointing.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SorcererEnd">
    <!-- 0 - Sorcerer name -->
    <value>{0} showed out of the blue, but... strange, he saw none of the wizards or witches! Everyone must be dead, Antonin Dolohov 🔮 thought. Strange, his Dark Mark on his hand has gone. He walked through dirty path and saw... everyone was dead. Curious, {0} ran while holding his wand, mumbling to himself about the end of the Dark Era, he reached the end of a cliff. {0} points his wand on his left inner forearm, sticked the wand to it trying to summon the Dark Mark on the sky, nothing happened. He then slipped into the darkness of the forest, away from the quiet village.</value>
    <value>{0} saw Death Eaters lay motionless and lifeless. He told himself repeatedly that Harry Potter isn't coming, his voice rising in anguish with each repetition. Antonin Dolohov 🔮 then looked up to the sky and saw.......nothing but emptiness. {0} breaks his wand, and silently disappears, in a cloud of fog, in search of another Death Eaters that might be still alive... "He-Who-Shall-Not-Be-Named must be there..." murmured him, walking into the dark...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WhatVariantVets">
    <value>What Variant?\nCurrent: {0}\nAs you have played over 500 games you can also join: </value>
  </string>
  <string key="Skip">
    <value>Skip</value>
  </string>
  <!-- New Roles, April 2018 -->
  <string key="DGTransformToLycan">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <!-- 1 - teammates' names -->
    <value>{0}'s wand is thrown to you, and once you grab it, you suddenly transform into the Bellatrix Lestrange 🐺🌝! Your Death Eater teammates (if any) are: {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NegSeerSees">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <!-- 1 - role that they are not -->
    <value>You see that {0} is NOT {1}!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskSandman">
    <value>Would you like to put all players to sleep tonight?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SandmanSleepAll">
    <value>As the wizards and witches at town talks, {0} goes back to their house to get a harp and enchants it with a spell to put everyone to sleep.  Just tonight, everyone will sleep very deeply, and none of the night wizards will be able to use their night actions~</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SandmanNight">
    <value>The wizards wondered about a beautiful melody that plays and plays... but they barely make it to their beds from exhaustion.  They all fall asleep so suddenly, they don't even remember closing their eyes...</value>
  </string>

  <string key="AllowThiefQ">
    <value>Allow thief as a role option?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowThiefA">
    <value>Thief as a role set to: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThiefFullQ">
    <value>Thief can be used every night?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThiefFullA">
    <value>Thief will play every night: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowThief">
    <value>Allow Thief</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThiefFull">
    <value>Thief Full Game</value>
  </string>

  <string key="RoleInfoWolfMan">
    <value>Ha, I thought you were someone else, but turns out you're Mundungus Fletcher 👱🌚! Since you spend most of your time dealing in illegal activities, Professor Sybill Trelawney will get confused and mistake you for a Death Eater...W-wait, don't run, you coward!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolfMan">
    <value>Mundungus Fletcher 👱🌚</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutWolfMan">
    <value>Mundungus Fletcher 👱🌚, a half-blood wizard with a notoriously shady reputation. You are surprisingly very loyal to Albus Dumbledore, but be careful! Because you spend most of your time dealing with illegal activities, Professor Sybill Trelawney tends to get confused and mistake you for a Death Eater!</value>
  </string>

  <string key="RoleInfoLycan">
    <value>You are Bellatrix Lestrange 🐺🌝, the Dark Lord's most loyal servant. You learned the Dark Arts from him, that's why Professor Sybill can't detect your identity as a Death Eater!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Lycan">
    <value>Bellatrix Lestrange 🐺🌝</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutLycan">
    <value>The most loyal servant of He-Who-Shall-Not-Be-Named, pure-blood witch, Bellatrix Lestrange 🐺🌝! You are the most dangerous and sadistic of all Dark Lord's followers, a powerful Death Eater. Your identity can't be detected even by Professor Sybill.</value>
  </string>

  <string key="RoleInfoOracle">
    <value>You are the strong and courageous centaur Firenze 🌀. You can sense danger by choosing to look at someone every night... but you will only be able to see what they are NOT.  The night stars will tell you a role of someone else who is still alive in the school, so pay attention to what role is said!.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Oracle">
    <value>Firenze the Centaur 🌀</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutOracle">
    <value>Firenze 🌀 predicts future with stars, and will be told what role someone is NOT, choosing from roles that are still alive in the current round.</value>
  </string>

  <string key="RoleInfoSandman">
    <value>You are Kingsley Shacklebolt 💤! What's that inside your house, a harp? You can use your magic to put everyone into such a deep sleep with that stringy thing that they won't be able to use their role at night, but only once per game.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Sandman">
    <value>Kingsley Shacklebolt 💤</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutSandman">
    <value> Once per game, you, Kingsley Shacklebolt 💤, can make all players sleep so deeply with an enchanted harp, that nobody can use their night actions!</value>
  </string>

<!-- NOT IMPLEMENTED YET -->
  <string key="RoleInfoPacifist">
    <value>You are Dobby ☮️, the loyal, kind, and compassionate house elf. You don't like having the wizards around you argue. To stop them from arguing, you can pull out a stinky sock that has the scent of mouldy cheese, Stinksap, and other items that has that foul stench. Ugh disgusting, but hey at least they stop arguing!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Pacifist">
    <value>Dobby ☮️</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutPacifist">
    <value>You are Dobby ☮️, the loyal, kind, and compassionate house elf. You don't like having the wizards around you argue. Your greatest strength? The foul stench from the stinky sock you pull out to stop people from arguing.</value>
  </string>

  <string key="AskPacifist">
    <value>Hit this button to take out your stinky sock to distract everyone from arguing and sending anyone to Azkaban.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PacifistNoLynch">
  <!-- {0} - Pacifist's name -->
    <value>Dobby ☮️, {0}, pulls out his stinky sock. Everyone covers their nose and runs back into their rooms to get a breath of fresh air! Seems like no one will be sent to Azkaban tonight.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PacifistNoLynchNow">
    <value>Dobby's ☮️ stinky sock strikes! The area is filled with a foul stench and no one dares to leave their rooms to vote to send anyone to Azkaban!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoWiseElder">
    <value>You are the great and wise Albus Dumbledore 📚. With your wand, you can survive an attack from a Death Eater because of your Protection Charm - but be warned, they can kill you the second time! If somehow you're in battle along with Sirius Black or Harry Potter against the Dark Lord, and killed by their spell, they will lose their powers out of sorrow and immediately end their lives as a pitiful wizard 👱!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WiseElder">
    <value>Albus Dumbledore 📚</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutWiseElder">
    <value>You are Professor Albus Percival Wulfric Brian Dumbledore  📚, the Great Headmaster of Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry.  With your wand, you can survive from Death Eater because of your Protection Charm - but once you're not aware, the second time they can kill you! If somehow you're in battle along with Sirius Black or Harry Potter against Dark Lord, and killed by their spell, they will lose their powers out of sorrow and immediately end their lives as a pitiful wizard 👱!</value>
  </string>

  <string key="WolvesTriedToEatWiseElder">
  <!-- 0 - Wise Elder's name -->
    <value>Quietly, you tried to enter {0}'s room, but unfortunately they were Albus Dumbledore 📚! {0} successfully thwart the spells, but luckily, they didn't recognise any of you. Defeated for now, you slip back to the dark...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolvesAteWiseElderPM">
    <value>You saw Death Eaters flying around you, casting spells, but you managed to avoid the spells! You, the great Dumbledore 📚 successfully thwart the attacks, but unfortunately you didn't get to recognise any attackers...However you know that they must come from the Dark Lord's order...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterKilledWiseElder">
  <!-- {0} - Hunter's Name -->
  <!-- {1} - Wise Elder's Name -->
    <value>Harry Potter 🎯, {0} raised his wand and casted an Avada Kedavra...without realising that it was Dumbledore 📚, {1}! As Dumbledore fell from the Astronomy Tower to reach his death, {0} sobbed mournfully, regretting his mistake, and used the Killing Curse to end his life and die as a pitiful wizard 👱!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GunnerShotWiseElder">
  <!-- {0} - Gunner's Name -->
  <!-- {1} - Wise Elder's Name -->
    <value>Sirius Black 🔫, {0} raised his wand in a battle with Dark Lord, but the spells mirrored and hit Albus Dumbledore 📚, {1}! {0} sobbed mournfully, regretting his mistake, and used the Apparition Spell, vanishing... Now he lives somewhere in town as a pitiful wizard 👱!</value>
  </string>

  <string key="RoleInfoThief">
    <value>Aha, Rita Skeeter 😈, our famous Daily Prophet journalist! You can steal someone's role with your spell every night and turn them into a common wizard!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoThiefFull">
    <value>Aha, Rita Skeeter 😈, our famous Daily Prophet journalist! Since the [Full Thief] mode is turned on, you will only have a 50% chance of stealing a player's role every night. If successful, that player will become the new Daily Prophet journalist and continue with the theft!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Thief">
    <value>Rita Skeeter 😈</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutThief">
    <value>Rita Skeeter 😈, a witch journalist who specialises in writing poison-pen stories based on false information and misreported interviews! You can steal someone's role with your spell every night and turn them into a common wizard!\nLets see...If the [Full Thief] mode is turned on, you will only have a 50% chance to steal a player's role every night. If successful, that player will become the new Daily Prophet journalist and continue with the theft!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThiefStealFailed">
  <!-- {0} - The name of the thief's target -->
    <value>Ouch Rita, you tried to steal the information from {0}, but unfortunately you failed...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThiefStealDead">
  <!-- {0} - The name of the thief's target -->
    <value>Ouch Rita, you tried to steal the role from {0}, but {0} is already died, but, by who? Hmm...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThiefStoleYourRole" deprecated="true">
  <!-- {0} - The new role -->
    <value>Your role got stolen! You are now {0}.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThiefStoleRole">
  <!-- {0} - The name of the thief's target -->
    <value>You successfully stole {0}'s role!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThiefToMason">
    <!-- 0 - old mason's name -->
    <!-- 1 - new mason's name -->
    <value>Strange, {0} has left the house and {1} has joined Dumbledore's Army!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThiefTransformToMason">
    <!-- 0 - mason colleagues' names -->
    <value>Wanting to properly learn Defence Against the Dark Arts, you joined Dumbledore's Army 👷. Your teammates (if any) are: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThiefToCult">
    <!-- 0 - old cultist's name -->
    <!-- 1 - new cultist's name -->
    <value>Strange, {0} is no longer your teammate and {1} has now become a being without spirit, that nonetheless seek life, just like you!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThiefToWolf">
    <!-- 0 - old wolf's name -->
    <!-- 1 - new wolf's name -->
    <value>Strange, {0} is no longer your teammate and {1} has now become a Death Eater with a mark on his arm, just like you!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThiefTransformNewTeammates">
    <!-- 0 - teammates' names -->
    <value>Your teammates (if any) are: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThiefEnd">
  <!-- 0 - Thief's name -->
    <value>As {0} wanders around the village, they find out that there is no more fun information available for them to steal. They quickly leave the Daily Prophet and search for another place to restart their journalist career.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThiefStealChosen">
  <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>Your theft target is now {0}.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskThief">
    <value>Whose information do you want to write on news from?</value>
  </string>
  
  <string key="SecretLynchResultEach">
  <!-- 0 - Number of votes -->
  <!-- 1 - Player got lynched -->
  <!-- 2 - A list of players who voted {1} -->
    <value>{0} votes went to {1}: {2}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SecretLynchResultFull">
  <!-- 0 - A list of "SecretLynchResultEach" or "SecretLynchResultNumber" -->
    <value>The lynch result for today:\n{0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SecretLynchResultNumber">
  <!-- 0 - Number of votes -->
  <!-- 1 - Player got lynched -->
    <value>{0} votes went to {1}.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SecretLynchShowVotes">
    <value>Secret: Votes Count</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SecretLynchShowVotesQ">
    <value>When secret lynch is turned on, show the vote count at the end of the lynch?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SecretLynchShowVotesA">
    <value>When secret lynch is turned on, the vote count at the end of the lynch will: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SecretLynchShowVoters">
    <value>Secret: Voters</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SecretLynchShowVotersQ">
    <value>When secret lynch is turned on and the vote count is showing, show the voter's name for every voted player?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SecretLynchShowVotersA">
    <value>When secret lynch is turned on and the vote count is showing, the voter's name for every voted player will: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultistBitten">
  <!-- {0} - Cultist that was bitten by the Alpha Wolf -->
	<value>Strange... The second you start discussing on whom to convert tonight, you realize that {0} isn't here! What has happened to them??</value>
  </string>
  
  <string key="Peace">
  <!-- Used for Pacifist's button -->
	<value>Sock!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="LynchPeaceTimeout">
  <!-- Used in PM if the pacifist uses his ability during lynch phase -->
	<value>Today's lynching got skipped because Dobby ☮️ took out his stinky sock!</value>
  </string>
  
  <string key="ThiefStoleYourRoleThief"> 
    <value>Your information got stolen! You are now the new journalist of Daily Prophet 😈 and can steal an information the next night!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThiefStoleYourRoleVillager">
    <value>Your information got stolen! You are now a common wizard 👱, just about to start a day flying with your broom.</value>
  </string>
  
  <string key="SerialKillerKilledYou" isgif="true">
    <value>HA! Bloody hell, he only came to take your life away~ You've been visited by Gellert Grindelwald 🔪! Your life ends here...</value>
    <value>Gellert Grindelwald 🔪 disarmed you using his spell, and casted Avada Kedavra on you! You're now dead...</value>
  </string>
  
  <string key="ThiefTeamEnd">
    <value>Thief Team</value>
  </string>
  
  <string key="StealKiller">
    <value>You tried to steal information... without knowing that your target was Gellert Grindelwald 🔪! They let you inside their house, and not a minute later, you were killed by his Killing Curse...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThiefStoleKiller">
    <!-- used when Thief steals SK -->
    <value>The Daily Prophet journalist 😈, {0}, tried to steal the information from Gellert Grindelwald 🔪! This didn't work out so well: {0} got casted with Avada Kedavra too! What a bad day...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="BeholderSeerStolen">
 <value>Oops! Rita Skeeter 😈 has stolen the Sybill's information and tried to impersonate her! {0} is now Sybill, and {1} no longer has seeing abilities!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Spumpkin">
    <value>the Spumpkin 🎃</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoSpumpkin">
    <value>You are the Spumpkin! Known in the village to grow the biggest, ripest, most delicious pumpkins, you carry your prized possession wherever you go. One pumpkin grows too big, and might explode at any moment! In your panic, you may run to someone else just as it explodes, killing both of you.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Detonation" >
    <!-- 0 - Spumpkin's name -->
    <!-- 1 - target name -->
    <!-- 2 - Target's revealed name ( Target was a role) -->
    <value>{0}'s pumpkin detonated! {1} was in the way and they were impaled by pumpkin bits! {1} is dead. {2}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DetonatedWiseElder">
    <!-- {0} - Spumpkin's Name -->
    <!-- {1} - Wise Elder's Name -->
    <value>{0}'s pumpkin detonated at an unfortunate time! The all-knowing {1} is dead!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskDetonate">
    <value>The pumpkin is growing too big and might detonate! In a panic, who do you run to?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutSpumpkin">
    <value>The Spumpkin 🎃 is a pumpkin grower known for his plump pumpkins, which can grow large enough to explode! When detonated, the Spumpkin and another player of their choice die from the impact. The Spumpkin wins with the rest of the villagers.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Nexus">
    <value>the Golden Snitch 💫</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoNexus">
    <value>You are the Golden Snitch 💫, a key item in making Hogwarts succeed in defeating Voldemort! Being a small, fluttery ball, you are difficult to catch. This makes it impossible for anyone to carry out any actions on you, and they will miss and hit someone random instead. However, this isn't the case for actions that will kill you (e.g. getting killed by Death Eaters).</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutNexus">
    <value>The Golden Snitch 💫 was the first Snitch that Harry Potter caught. Currently, it contains something invaluable to Hogwarts. As a Golden Snitch, non-killing actions will miss you and hit a random person instead. However, your little wings can only get you so far... If you are chosen to be killed or sent to Azkaban, your enchantments will break, allowing yourself to be captured.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NexusWin" isgif="true">
    <value>The Golden Snitch flutters in and out of sight, twinkling like an unreachable star. This Quidditch match ends with none of the Quidditch players as winners.</value>
    <value>Left, right, up, down, all across the Quidditch field. Alas, it was just too much for the Seekers to succeed in catching the Golden Snitch. Times up! The Quidditch Match ends up as a tie.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SerialKillerSoloSurvive">
    <value>The remaining pair of serial killers gather in the town square. They draw their knives in unison. A few minutes later, {0} wipes their knife clean. Looks like they're the last remaining survivor of this bloodbath! Having proven themselves to be the most skilled killer, they pack up their liver collection to visit another village....</value>
  </string>
</strings>