<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<strings>
  <language name="English uwu" base="English" variant="uwu" code="en" isDefault="false"/>
  <string key="PlayerStartedGame" isgif="true">
    <value>{0} hawas stawartewed awa gawamewe! Jowoiwin towo gewet iwin owon thewe fuwun... awand prowobawablywy diwiewe :P</value>
    <value>AwA newew gawamewe hawas beweewen stawartewed bywy {0}! Jowoiwin towo gewet eweawatewen!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerStartedChaosGame" isgif="true">
    <value>{0} hawas stawartewed awa chawaowos gawamewe! Jowoiwin towo gewet iwin owon thewe fuwun... awand prowobawablywy diwiewe :P</value>
    <value>AwA newew chawaowos gawamewe hawas beweewen stawartewed bywy {0}! Jowoiwin towo gewet eweawatewen!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MinuteLeftToJoin">
    <value>1 miwinuwutewe leweft towo Jowoiwin</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SecondsLeftToJoin">
    <value>{0} sewecowonds leweft towo Jowoiwin</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NotEnoughPlayers">
    <value>Nowot ewenowouwugh plawaywyewers, cawancewelliwing gawamewe!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="StartingGameWait">
    <value>Gawamewe iwis stawartiwing, pleweawasewe wawaiwit whiwilewe IwI awassiwign rowolewes awand uwupdawatewe thewe dawatawabawasewe.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ChangeNameToJoin">
    <value>{0}, pleweawasewe chawangewe ywyowouwur nawamewe towo jowoiwin</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerLimitReached">
    <value>Soworrywy, mawax plawaywyewer liwimiwit hawas beweewen reweawachewed!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerJoined">
    <value>{0} hawas jowoiwinewed thewe gawamewe. {1} plawaywyewers, {2} miwiniwimuwum, {3} mawax</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PMTheBot">
    <value>{0} Pleweawasewe cliwick thewe stawart buwuttowon bewelowow owor {1} awand stawart mewe, sowo IwI cawan PM ywyowouwu ywyowouwur rowolewe. YwYowouwu mawaywy nowot jowoiwin thewe gawamewe uwuntiwil ywyowouwu dowo.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DeadFlee">
    <value>YwYowouwu cawan't ruwun awawawaywy! YwYOwOUwU'REwE DEwEAwAD! Gewet bawack iwin thewe growouwund... jeweewez!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Flee">
    <value>{0} hawas flewed iwin tewerrowor!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerRoleWas">
    <value>{0} wawas {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CountPlayersRemain">
    <value>{0} plawaywyewers rewemawaiwin.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NotPlaying">
    <value>YwYowouwu dowon't seweewem towo bewe plawaywyiwing....</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NoPlayerName">
    <value>IwI cawan't fiwind awa plawaywyewer bywy thawat nawamewe!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolfVotedKill">
    <value>{0} hawas vowotewed towo eweawat {1}.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerVotedLynch">
    <value>{0} hawas vowotewed towo lywynch {1}.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="IdleKill">
    <value>{0} hawas nowot vowotewed fowor 2 niwights iwin awa rowow. Thewe foworcewes owof gowoowod hawavewe seweewen thiwis awas awa tewerriwiblewe criwimewe, awand {0} suwuddewenlywy fawalls, deweawad. {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="TraitorTurnWolf">
    <value>YwYowouwu trawaiwitowor!!! YwYowouwu awarewe nowow thewe wowolf...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ChoiceAccepted">
    <value>Chowoiwicewe awacceweptewed.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="BeholderSeer">
    <value>\nThewe seweewer iwis {0}.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ApprenticeNowSeer">
    <value>{0} wawas thewe seweewer. AwAs thewe awapprewentiwicewe, ywyowouwu stewep uwup towo bewecowomewe thewe newew seweewer.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="BeholderNewSeer">
    <value>{0} wawas awan awapprewentiwicewe, awand hawas nowow steweppewed uwup towo fiwill {1}'s plawacewe awas thewe newew Seweewer.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SeerSees">
    <value>YwYowouwu seweewe {0} iwis {1}!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskLynch">
    <value>Whowo dowo ywyowouwu wawant towo lywynch?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskDetect">
    <value>Whowo dowo ywyowouwu wawant towo dewetewect?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskShoot">
    <value>Whowo dowo ywyowouwu wawant towo showoowot? {0} buwullewet(s) rewemawaiwin.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskVisit">
    <value>Whowo dowo ywyowouwu wawant towo viwisiwit?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskSee">
    <value>Whowo dowo ywyowouwu wawant towo seweewe?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskGuard">
    <value>Whowo dowo ywyowouwu wawant towo guwuaward?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskEat">
    <value>Whowo dowo ywyowouwu wawant towo eweawat?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskHunt">
    <value>Whowo dowo ywyowouwu wawant towo huwunt?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskRoleModel">
    <value>Whowo iwis ywyowouwur rowolewe mowodewel?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskConvert">
    <value>Whowo dowo ywyowouwu wawant towo cowonvewert towo ywyowouwur owordewer?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DiscussWith">
    <value>  Mawakewe suwurewe ywyowouwu diwiscuwuss wiwith {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="And">
    <value> awand </value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoCursed">
    <value>YwYowouwu awarewe cuwursewed. YwYowouwu awarewe awa viwillawagewer awat thiwis tiwimewe, buwut iwif thewe wowolvewes chowoowosewe towo kiwill ywyowouwu, ywyowouwu wiwill bewecowomewe awa wewerewewowolf ywyowouwursewelf.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoDetective">
    <value>YwYowouwu awarewe thewe dewetewectiwivewe. Duwuriwing thewe dawaywy, ywyowouwu mawaywy chowoowosewe awa plawaywyewer towo reweveweawal theweiwir rowolewe. Howowewevewer - iwin dowoiwing sowo, ywyowouwur rowolewe cowouwuld bewe reweveweawalewed towo thewe wowolvewes! (40% chawancewe)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoDrunk">
    <value>Cowongrawats! YwYowouwu'rewe thewe viwillawagewe druwunk! (awand reweawallywy, ewevewerywyowonewe knowows iwit...)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoGuardianAngel">
    <value>YwYowouwu awarewe thewe Guwuawardiwiawan AwAngewel. EwEawach niwight, ywyowouwu mawaywy chowoowosewe awa plawaywyewer towo sawavewe. Howowewevewer, iwif ywyowouwu chowoowosewe awa wowolf, thewerewe iwis awa 50% chawancewe ywyowouwu wiwill diwiewe.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoGunner">
    <value>YwYowouwu awarewe thewe guwunnewer. YwYowouwu hawavewe twowo buwullewets. Duwuriwing thewe dawaywy, ywyowouwu mawaywy chowoowosewe towo showoowot awanowothewer plawaywyewer. EwEvewerywyowonewe wiwill heweawar thewe showots, awand knowow ywyowouwu awarewe thewe guwunnewer (nowot awa wowolf).</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoHarlot">
    <value>YwYowouwu sluwut! YwYowouwu awarewe thewe Hawarlowot. Duwuriwing thewe niwight, ywyowouwu mawaywy chowoowosewe towo viwisiwit awanowothewer plawaywyewer, towo veweriwifywy thawat theweywy awarewe nowot awa wowolf. Howowewevewer--iwif ywyowouwu viwisiwit awa wowolf, owor viwisiwit sowomeweowonewe kiwillewed bywy thewe wowolf, ywyowouwu wiwill diwiewe. IwIf ywyowouwu dowo gowo towo viwisiwit thowouwugh, awand thewe wowolf triwiewes towo kiwill ywyowouwu awat ywyowouwur howomewe, ywyowouwu wiwill suwurviwivewe.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoTraitor">
    <value>Trawaiwitowor! Fowor nowow, ywyowouwu awarewe awa viwillawagewer, buwut owoncewe awall thewe wowolvewes diwiewe, ywyowouwu wiwill bewecowomewe awa wewerewewowolf. IwIf thewe seweewer lowoowoks towo ywyowouwu, ywyowouwu mawaywy owor mawaywy nowot bewe iwidewentiwifiwiewed awas awa wowolf.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoWolf">
    <value>YwYOwOUwU AwAREwE AwA WOwOLF!! XD (gowoowod owon ywyawa) EwEawach niwight ywyowouwu cawan chowoowosewe towo kiwill sowomeweowonewe.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoSeer" >
    <value >YwYowouwu awarewe thewe seweewer. EwEawach niwight, ywyowouwu mawaywy chowoowosewe awa plawaywyewer towo 'seweewe', awand reweveweawal theweiwir rowolewe towo ywyowouwu.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoVillager" >
    <value >YwYowouwu awarewe awa lowowlywy viwillawagewer, dowoowomewed towo spewend ywyowouwur dawaywys plowowiwing awa fiwieweld awand gewet eweawatewed.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoTanner" >
    <value >YwYowouwu awarewe thewe tawannewer. IwIf ywyowouwu gewet lywynchewed, ywyowouwu wiwin awauwutowomawatiwicawallywy!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoWildChild" >
    <value >YwYowouwu awarewe awa wiwild chiwild! Piwick awa plawaywyewer towo bewe ywyowouwur 'rowolewe mowodewel' - iwif theweywy diwiewe, ywyowouwu bewecowomewe awa wewerewewowolf.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoBeholder" >
    <value >YwYowouwu awarewe thewe bewehowoldewer, ywyowouwu wiwill bewe towold whowo thewe (reweawal) seweewer iwis - thawat iwis ywyowouwur owonlywy fuwunctiwiowon.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoApprenticeSeer" >
    <value >YwYowouwu awarewe thewe awapprewentiwicewe seweewer. IwIf thewe (reweawal) seweewer diwiewes, ywyowouwu wiwill tawakewe theweiwir plawacewe awas thewe seweewer.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoCultist" >
    <value >YwYowouwu awarewe awa cuwultiwist. EwEvewerywy niwight, ywyowouwu mawaywy chowoowosewe awa plawaywyewer towo cowonvewert towo awa cuwultiwist. IwIf awall rewemawaiwiniwing liwiviwing plawaywyewers awat thewe ewend awarewe cuwultiwists, theweywy wiwin.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoCultistHunter" >
    <value >YwYowouwu awarewe thewe Cuwultiwist Huwuntewer, trywyiwing towo stowop thewe cuwult iwin towown frowom cowonvewertiwing ewevewerywyowonewe! EwEawach niwight, chowoowosewe awa plawaywyewer. IwIf theweywy awarewe awa cuwultiwist, theweywy diwiewe. IwIf thewe cuwult triwiewes towo cowonvewert ywyowouwu, thewe cuwult's newewewest mewembewer diwiewes.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="LynchTime" >
    <value>
      Duwusk drawaws neweawar, awand thewe viwillawagewers gawathewer towo deweciwidewe whowo theweywy awarewe lywynchiwing thiwis eweveweniwing...
      EwEvewerywyowonewe nowow hawas {0} sewecowonds towo vowotewe!
    </value>
  </string>
  <string key="DayTime" >
    <value >IwIt iwis nowow dawaywy tiwimewe. AwAll owof ywyowouwu hawavewe {0} sewecowonds towo mawakewe ywyowouwur awaccuwusawatiwiowons, dewefewensewes, owor juwust tawalk.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NightTime" >
    <value >Niwight hawas fawallewen. EwEvewerywyowonewe heweawads towo bewed, weweawarywy awaftewer awanowothewer strewessfuwul dawaywy. Niwight plawaywyewers: ywyowouwu hawavewe {0} sewecowonds uwusewe ywyowouwur awactiwiowons!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="LynchKill" >
    <value >Thewe viwillawagewers hawavewe cawast theweiwir vowotewes, awamiwid dowouwubts awand suwuspiwiciwiowons. {0} iwis deweawad. {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="LynchTie" >
    <value >UwUnawablewe towo cowomewe uwup wiwith awa prowopewer deweciwisiwiowon owon whowo towo lywynch, thewe mowob rewetuwurns towo theweiwir howomewes fowor thewe niwight, fruwustrawatewed...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NoLynchVotes" >
    <value >Sowomewethiwing iwis fiwishywy, fowor nowo owonewe vowotewed! Nowo lywynch mowob towoniwight...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DetectiveEaten" >
    <value >Thewe viwillawagewers gawathewer iwin thewe moworniwing, buwut dowo nowot seweewe {0}. Theweywy wawandewer owovewer towo thewe howouwusewe, towo fiwind {0} diwisewembowowewelewed, awan owold bawadgewe showovewed dowown theweiwir throwoawat.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardianEaten" >
    <value >Moworniwing cowomewes, awand towo ewevewerywyowonewe's diwismawaywy, iwimpawalewed owon towop owof thewe chuwurch's crowoss iwis {0}, thewe Guwuawardiwiawan AwAngewel.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GunnerEaten" >
    <value >AwAs ewevewerywyowonewe cowomewes owouwut owof theweiwir howouwusewes, theweywy fiwind piwiewecewes owof awa showotguwun strewewn awabowouwut... thewen lewegs... thewen fiwingewers... thewen thewe bowodywy owof {0}, flowoawatiwing iwin thewe fowouwuntawaiwin iwin thewe towown squwuawarewe, deweawad frowom awa wewerewewowolf awattawack. YwYowouwu hawavewe lowost ywyowouwur guwunnewer.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SeerEaten" >
    <value >Thewe viwillawagewers awawawakewe iwin thewe moworniwing, towo fiwind thewe diwisewembowowewelewed rewemawaiwins owof {0} huwunchewed owovewer awa OwOuwuiwijawa bowoaward awand tawarowot cawards. Thewe Seweewer iwis deweawad.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DrunkEaten" >
    <value >EwEvewerywyowonewe wawakewes towo thewe smewell owof awalcowohowol awand blowoowod... thewe puwub iwis dewestrowoywyewed! AwAftewer cleweawaniwing thewe blowoowod owouwut, thewe rewemawaiwins owof {0} awarewe fowouwund, toworn awapawart.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="FoolEaten" >
    <value >AwAs thewe suwun riwisewes awabowovewe thewe viwillawagewe, thewe viwillawagewers fiwind thewe coworpsewe owof {0} siwittiwing owovewer awa OwOuwuiwijawa bowoaward, buwut wiwith awa deweck owof... Biwicywyclewe plawaywyiwing cawards? WHAwAT AwA FOwOOwOL!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DefaultEaten" >
    <value>AwAs ewevewerywyowonewe riwisewes iwin thewe moworniwing, theweywy smewell awa tewerriwiblewe stiwink. Theweywy fowollowow thewe smewell towo fiwind {0} shreweddewed awapawart iwin thewe piwig pewen, heweawad miwissiwing. NOwOMNOwOMNOwOMNOwOM\n{1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterKilledCultist">
    <value>AwA nowotiwiceweawablewe stewench iwis cowomiwing frowom {0}'s howouwusewe... thewe viwillawagewe iwinspewects iwit towo fiwind awa bowodywy lywyiwing iwin frowont owof awa dawark awaltawar. AwA cuwultiwist hawas beweewen kiwillewed bywy thewe cuwult huwuntewer!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NoAttack" >
    <value >Thewe viwillawagewers gawathewer thewe newext moworniwing iwin thewe viwillawagewe cewentewer, towo siwighs owof reweliwiewef - iwit awappeweawars thewerewe wawas nowo awattawack thewe preweviwiowouwus niwight.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CursedBitten" >
    <value >YwYowouwu hawavewe beweewen kiwillewed bywy thewe wowolvewes. AwAs ywyowouwu wewerewe cuwursewed, ywyowouwu hawavewe nowow bewecowomewe awa wowolf!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CursedBittenToWolves" >
    <!-- 0 - victim name -->
    <value >{0} wawas biwittewen... buwut wawas cuwursewed, awand bewecawamewe awa wewerewewowolf! Cowongrawats owon ywyowouwur newew teweawammawatewe!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolvesEatYou" isgif="true" >
    <value >OwOh nowo! Thewe wowolvewes eweawatewed ywyowouwu. NOwOMNOwOMNOwOMNOwOM</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolvesEatDrunk" >
    <value >OwOh nowo! {0} wawas awa druwunk! Nowow ywyowouwu awarewe druwunk, awand cawan't awattawack towomoworrowow niwight...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardWolf" >
    <value >YwYowouwu triwiewed towo guwuaward awa wowolf! Thewe wowolf hawas eweawatewen ywyowouwu.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardSaved" >
    <value >YwYowouwu hawavewe sawavewed {0}'s liwifewe!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardNoAttack" >
    <value >{0} wawas nowot awattawackewed, sowo ywyowouwu diwidn't dowo muwuch owof awanywythiwing.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardEmptyHouse">
    <value>YwYowouwu wewent towo guwuaward {0}, buwut theweywy wewerewen't howomewe!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardSavedYou" >
    <value >AwA guwuawardiwiawan awangewel wawas wawatchiwing owovewer ywyowouwu lawast niwight awand fowouwught owoff awan awattawackewer!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotEaten" >
    <value >Thewe hawarlowot chowosewe thewe wrowong niwight towo stawaywy howomewe. {0} hawas beweewen eweawatewen bywy thewe wowolvewes!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotNotHome" >
    <value >OwOdd... {0} wawas nowot howomewe! Nowo diwinnewer fowor ywyowouwu...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotFuckWolf" >
    <value >YwYowouwu sliwip iwintowo {0}'s howouwusewe fowor awa liwittlewe fuwun, owonlywy towo bewe cowonfrowontewed bywy awa wowolf. YwYowouwu awarewe deweawad.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotFuckedWolfPublic" >
    <value >{0} sliwippewed iwintowo thewe wrowong howouwusewe lawast niwight! {0}'s sluwuttywy rewemawaiwins awarewe fowouwund piwinnewed towo thewe chuwurch dowoowors wiwith awan iwirowon rowod...  howow sawad :(</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotFuckedVictimPublic" >
    <value >{0} sliwips iwintowo {1}'s howouwusewe, reweawadywy towo hawavewe awa liwittlewe fuwun towo eweawasewe owoff thewe strewess. IwInsteweawad, {0} fiwinds awa wewerewewowolf eweawatiwing {1}! Thewe wewerewewowolf quwuiwicklywy tuwurns owon {0} awand juwumps... {0} iwis deweawad.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotVisitNonWolf" >
    <value >YwYowouwu seweewe {0} iwis nowot awa wowolf, awas ywyowouwu gowot fuwuckewed gowoowod awand haward awall niwight lowong!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotVisitYou" >
    <value >IwIt wawas awa biwit dawark, sowo ywyowouwu cowouwuldn't seweewe wewell ewenowouwugh, buwut iwin thewe miwiddlewe owof thewe niwight ywyowouwu wawakewe uwup towo thewe hawarlowot riwidiwing ywyowouwu. Bowoth owof ywyowouwu fiwiniwish uwup, thewen theweywy sliwip bawack owouwut siwilewentlywy...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DetectiveCaught" >
    <value >YwYowouwu cawauwught {0} snowoowopiwing awabowouwut! Thawat muwust bewe thewe dewetewectiwivewe!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DetectiveSnoop" >
    <value >YwYowouwur snowoowopiwing hawas showown ywyowouwu thawat {0} iwis {1}.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotShot" >
    <value >Lowoowoks liwikewe {0} cawamewe bawack powosiwitiwivewe awaftewer awa niwight wiwith thewe Hawarlowot! Thewe guwunnewer gowot rewevewengewe. {1} iwis deweawad.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DefaultShot" >
    <value >Suwuddewenlywy, awa showot riwings owouwut. Thewe viwillawagewe tuwurns towo seweewe {0} stawandiwing owovewer {1}'s bowodywy, awa guwun stiwill awaiwimewed awat thewe heweawad. {2}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolfWins" isgif="true" >
    <value >Thewe wewerewewowolf hawas wowon!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolvesWin" isgif="true" >
    <value >Thewe wewerewewowolvewes hawavewe wowon!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="VillageWins" isgif="true" >
    <value >Thewe viwillawagewers hawavewe wowon!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="TannerWins" isgif="true" >
    <value >OwOh nowo! YwYowouwu lywynchewed thewe Tawannewer! Thewe Tawannewer wiwins thewe gawamewe, siwillywy.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RemainingPlayersEnd">
    <value>Rewemawaiwiniwing liwiviwing plawaywyewers, rowolewes, awand teweawam:</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultistVotedConvert" >
    <value >{0} hawas vowotewed towo cowonvewert {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultConvertCultHunter">
    <value>{0} wawas sewent towo dowo ywyowouwur diwirtywy wowork, awand cowonvewert {1}... howowewevewer, theweywy wewerewe thewe cuwult huwuntewer! {0} iwis deweawad!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultHunterKilledCultVisit">
    <value>{0} cawamewe towo ywyowouwur howouwusewe lawast niwight, reweawadywy towo cowonvewert ywyowouwu.... buwut ywyowouwu showovewed ywyowouwur swoword riwight throwouwugh thewem. AwA cuwultiwist iwis deweawad... {1} rewemawaiwin!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultConvertYou">
    <value>Thewe cuwult hawas cowonvewertewed ywyowouwu towo theweiwir owordewer! YwYowouwu awarewe nowow awa cuwultiwist. EwEvewerywy owothewer niwight, ywyowouwu wiwill hawavewe awa chawancewe towo cowonvewert awanowothewer plawaywyewer.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultTeam">
    <value>Cuwultiwists: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultJoin">
    <value>{0} hawas jowoiwinewed thewe cuwult!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultVisitEmpty">
    <value>{0} wawas sewent towo dowo ywyowouwur diwirtywy wowork, awand cowonvewert {1}... buwut nowo owonewe wawas howomewe!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultWins" isgif="true">
    <value >AwAll thewe wowolvewes hawavewe diwiewed, awand thewe owonlywy peweowoplewe leweft stawandiwing hawavewe awall beweewen cowonvewertewed towo cuwultiwists.. Thewe cuwult hawas wowon!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterVisitDead">
    <value>YwYowouwu wewent towo huwunt {0}, buwut theweywy awarewe awalreweawadywy deweawad!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterFindCultist">
    <value>YwYowouwu gowo iwintowo {0}'s howouwusewe awand fiwind thewem prawaywyiwing bewefoworewe awan awaltawar towo sowomewe uwunknowown gowod. YwYowouwu quwuiwicklywy ruwun ywyowouwur swoword riwight throwouwugh thewe eweviwil cuwultiwist.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterFailedToFind">
    <value>YwYowouwu gowo towo {0}'s howouwusewe, buwut thewerewe iwis nowo mywysteweriwiowouwus chawantiwing. YwYowouwu rewetuwurn howomewe, cowonviwincewed thawat {0} iwis nowot awa cuwultiwist.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WildChildToWolves">
    <value>{0}'s rowolewe mowodewel juwust diwiewed! IwIn theweiwir rawagewe, theweywy hawavewe bewecowomewe awa wewerewewowolf!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WildChildTransform">
    <value>{0} hawas diwiewed! IwIn ywyowouwur rawagewe, ywyowouwu hawavewe bewecowomewe awa wewerewewowolf! YwYowouwur newew teweawammawatewes awarewe: {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Villager">
    <value>awa Viwillawagewer 👱</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Drunk">
    <value>thewe Druwunk 🍻</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Harlot">
    <value>thewe Hawarlowot 💋</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Seer">
    <value>thewe Seweewer 👳</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Traitor">
    <value>thewe Trawaiwitowor 🖕</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardianAngel">
    <value>thewe Guwuawardiwiawan AwAngewel 👼</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Detective">
    <value>thewe Dewetewectiwivewe 🕵</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Wolf">
    <value>awa Wewerewewowolf 🐺</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Cursed">
    <value>thewe Cuwursewed 😾</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Gunner">
    <value>thewe Guwunnewer 🔫</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Tanner">
    <value>thewe Tawannewer 👺</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Fool">
    <value>thewe Fowoowol 🃏</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WildChild">
    <value>thewe Wiwild Chiwild 👶</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Beholder">
    <value>thewe Bewehowoldewer 👁</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ApprenticeSeer">
    <value>thewe AwApprewentiwicewe Seweewer 🙇</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Cultist">
    <value>awa Cuwultiwist 👤</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultistHunter">
    <value>thewe Cuwultiwist Huwuntewer 💂</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RanAway">
    <value>Rawan awawawaywy</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Dead">
    <value>💀 Deweawad</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Alive">
    <value>🙂 AwAliwivewe</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayersAlive">
    <value>Plawaywyewers AwAliwivewe</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Mason">
    <value>awa Mawasowon 👷</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoMason">
    <value>YwYowouwu awarewe awa Mawasowon. IwIf thewerewe awarewe awanywy owothewer mawasowons, ywyowouwu wiwill knowow whowo theweywy awarewe.  OwOthewerwiwisewe, ywyowouwu awarewe awa viwillawagewer.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MasonEaten">
    <value>AwAs ewevewerywyowonewe riwisewes, theweywy fiwind thewe bowodywy owof {0} showovewed iwintowo awa piwilewe owof stowonewe, blowoowod splawattewerewed ewevewerywywhewerewe. OwOnewe owof ywyowouwur mawasowons hawas diwiewed!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MasonTeam">
    <value>  Thewe mawasowons awarewe: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultTargetDead">
    <value>YwYowouwur newewewest mewembewer heweawads owovewer towo {0}'s howouwusewe towo cowonvewert thewem, buwut iwinsteweawad fiwinds thewe howouwusewe awa cowomplewetewe wreweck, blowoowod ewevewerywywhewerewe, awand biwits owof wowolf fuwur snawaggewed owon thewe dowooworwawaywy...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardBlockedWolf">
    <value>Thewe pawack heweawads towo {0}'s howouwusewe towo eweawat thewem, buwut theweywy awarewe mewet bywy awa tawall dawark fiwiguwurewe, awarmewed towo thewe teweeweth. Thewe Guwuawardiwiawan AwAngewel fiwights ewevewerywyowonewe owoff, awand ywyowouwu heweawad bawack dewefeweawatewed.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultUnableToConvert">
    <value>YwYowouwu sewend {0} towo trywy towo cowonvewert {1}, howowewevewer theweiwir beweliwiewef wawas towoowo strowong, awand ywyowouwu wewerewe uwunawablewe towo cowonvewert thewem :(</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NameExists">
    <value>@{1}, awa plawaywyewer wiwith thewe nawamewe {0} hawas awalreweawadywy jowoiwinewed. Pleweawasewe chawangewe ywyowouwur nawamewe towo jowoiwin.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotDiscoverCult">
    <value>YwYowouwu sliwippewed iwintowo {0}'s howouwusewe fowor awa biwit owof fuwun... buwut awas ywyowouwu awarewe leweawaviwing, ywyowouwu hawappewen towo nowotiwicewe awa strawangewe awaltawar, powooworlywy hiwiddewen owoff iwin awa siwidewe rowoowom, wiwith awa strawangewe glowowiwing cowomiwing frowom iwit...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Was">
    <value>wawas</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GenericDeathNoReveal">
    <value>EwEvewerywyowonewe wawakewes uwup iwin thewe moworniwing, awand nowotiwicewes thawat {0} iwis nowot awarowouwund... Theweywy cheweck thewe howouwusewe towo fiwind thewe rewemawaiwins owof {0}.</value>
    <value>AwAs thewe viwillawagewers gawathewer awas thewe suwun riwisewes, thewe fiwind thewe rewemawaiwins owof {0}, whowo diwiewed sowomewehowow lawast niwight...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MasonConverted">
    <value>OwOdd.... {0} diwidn't showow uwup fowor thewe mawasowons meweewetiwing thiwis moworniwing... OwO.owo</value>
  </string>
  <!-- new string May 16 2016-->
  <string key="FleeDisabled">
    <value>Fleweeweiwing whiwilewe thewe gawamewe iwis ruwunniwing hawas beweewen diwisawablewed bywy thewe growouwup awadmiwin!!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="IsDead">
    <!-- used when gunner shoots a player -->
    <value>iwis deweawad</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AlreadyInGame">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>YwYowouwu awarewe awalreweawadywy iwin awa gawamewe! ({0})</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NoGame">
    <value>Thewerewe iwis nowo gawamewe ruwunniwing. Stawart awa newew gawamewe wiwith /startgame owor stawart awa chawaowos gawamewe wiwith /startchaos</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GroupAdminOnly">
    <value>OwOnlywy awa growouwup awadmiwin cawan ruwun thiwis cowommawand.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NoSeer">
    <value>Nowo seweewer!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="TimesUp">
    <value>Tiwimewe's uwup!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoCupid">
    <value>YwYowouwu awarewe Cuwupiwid. Sewent towo EwEawarth wiwith owonlywy uwundewerpawants, awa bowow awand twowo awarrowows, ywyowouwu gewet towo chowoowosewe twowo plawaywyewers towo lowovewe eweawach owothewer fowor ewetewerniwitywy. IwIf owonewe owof thewem diwiewes, thewe owothewer owonewe diwiewes owof soworrowow.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoDoppelganger">
    <value>YwYowouwu awarewe awa Dowoppewelgängewer. Lewegewend hawas iwit thawat ywyowouwur awancewestowors wewerewe mewetawamoworphs, awand cowouwuld chowoowosewe awanywy foworm theweywy wawantewed. YwYowouwu hawavewe iwinheweriwitewed sowomewe owof theweiwir cawapawaciwitiwiewes. Chowoowosewe awa plawaywyewer, whewen thawat plawaywyewer diwiewes, ywyowouwu wiwill tawakewe owon theweiwir rowolewe.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoHunter">
    <value>YwYowouwu awarewe thewe towown Huwuntewer. YwYowouwu dowo nowot sleweewep wewell, awand ywyowouwu wowouwuld newevewer gowo towo bewed wiwithowouwut ywyowouwur riwiflewe. IwIf ywyowouwu diwiewe, ywyowouwu cawan chowoowosewe sowomeweowonewe ewelsewe towo kiwill. IwIf ywyowouwu awarewe eweawatewen, ywyowouwu hawavewe awa chawancewe towo tawakewe awa wewerewewowolf dowown, buwut wiwill nowot bewe awablewe towo chowoowosewe awa plawaywyewer towo kiwill.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoSerialKiller">
    <value>YwYowouwu awarewe thewe seweriwiawal kiwillewer. Rewecewentlywy ewescawapewed frowom thewe lowocawal awasywyluwum, ywyowouwur gowoawal iwis fowor ewevewerywyowonewe ewelsewe towo diwiewe. EwEvewerywy niwight, ywyowouwu cawan awadd awa plawaywyewer's bowodywy towo ywyowouwur cowollewectiwiowon.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CupidChosen">
    <value>YwYowouwu hawavewe beweewen struwuck bywy lowovewe. {0}'s mewemoworywy wiwill newevewer fawadewe iwin ywyowouwur heweawart. IwIf owonewe owof ywyowouwu diwiewes, thewe owothewer owonewe wiwill diwiewe owouwut owof soworrowow. IwIf owonewe owof ywyowouwu wiwins, thewe owothewer owonewe wiwins towoowo.</value>
    <value>Cuwupiwid's awarrowow hawas struwuck ywyowouwu! YwYowouwu awarewe mawadlywy iwin lowovewe wiwith {0}! IwIf theweywy diwiewe, ywyowouwu wiwill diwiewe towoowo. IwIf owonewe owof ywyowouwu twowo wiwins, ywyowouwu wiwill bowoth wiwin.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterLynchedChoice">
    <value>Thewe viwillawagewe hawas chowosewen towo hawang ywyowouwu! Thiwis iwis ywyowouwur lawast chawancewe, chowoowosewe towo showoowot sowomeweowonewe awas ywyowouwu gowo dowown!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterNoChoiceLynched">
    <value>{0} fuwumblewes fowor theweiwir piwistowol awas thewe nowoowosewe tiwightewens, buwut cawannowot gewet iwit iwin tiwimewe, awand fawalls towo theweiwir deweawath wiwith awa lowouwud snawap owof theweiwir neweck...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterSkipChoiceLynched">
    <value>{{0} whiwips owouwut theweiwir piwistowol awand lowoowoks awat thewe crowowd... awand cawannowot mawakewe awa deweciwisiwiowon owon whowo towo showoowot. Theweywy fawall towo theweiwir deweawath, awacceweptiwing theweiwir fawatewe...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterKilledFinalLynched">
    <value>AwAs thewe nowoowosewe tiwightewens, {0} whiwips owouwut awa piwistowol, tawakewes awaiwim, awand showoowots {1} awas thewe flowoowor drowops owouwut! {1} fawalls owovewer, deweawad.  {2}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterShotChoice">
    <value>YwYowouwu'vewe beweewen muwurdewerewed! IwIn ywyowouwur lawast mowomewents, ywyowouwu hawavewe thewe chawancewe towo showoowot sowomeweowonewe... mawakewe iwit quwuiwick!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterNoChoiceShot">
    <value>Thewe blowow towo {0} wawas towoowo muwuch, sowo muwuch thawat theweywy cowouwuldn't ewevewen reweawach fowor theweiwir siwideweawarm, awas theweywy lawaywy iwin awa powoowol owof blowoowod...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterSkipChoiceShot">
    <!-- 0 - hunter's name -->
    <value>AwAs {0} lawaywys thewerewe, gawaspiwing fowor theweiwir fiwinawal breweawaths, theweywy cawan't deweciwidewe whowo towo showoowot... awand awaccewept theweiwir fawatewe.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterKilledFinalShot">
    <value>Dywyiwing, {0} fawalls towo thewe growouwund.... buwut nowot wiwithowouwut grawaspiwing theweiwir piwistowol, awand fiwiriwing uwupowon {1}, whowo tawakewes awa buwullewet riwight bewetweweewen thewe eweywyewes. {2}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterShotWolfMulti">
    <value>Thewe wowolvewes triwiewed towo awattawack thewe huwuntewer lawast niwight, buwut thewe huwuntewer wawas awablewe towo tawakewe owonewe dowown wiwith thewem awas theweywy diwiewed! {0} hawas diwiewed.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterShotWolf">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>Thewe wowolf triwiewed towo awattawack thewe huwuntewer lawast niwight, buwut thewe huwuntewer wawas awablewe towo tawakewe thewe wowolf {0} dowown wiwith theweiwir riwiflewe!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SerialKillerKilledWolf">
    <value>Thewe wowolvewes awattewemptewed towo hawavewe awa niwicewe lawatewe niwight snawack, buwut wewerewe iwinsteweawad greweewetewed bywy awa crawazewed muwurdewerewer! {0} wawas kiwillewed iwin thewe fiwight!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DefaultKilled">
    <value>IwIt seweewemewed awa quwuiwiewet ewenowouwugh niwight fowor {0}, buwut theweywy wewerewe wrowong. Thewe viwillawagewers gawathewer iwin thewe moworniwing towo fiwind {0} spliwit frowom heweawad towo towoewe, buwut owoddlywy thewe liwivewer wawas miwissiwing... Thewe seweriwiawal kiwillewer hawas struwuck awagawaiwin! {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardBlockedKiller">
    <value>YwYowouwu triwiewed towo cowollewect {0}'s bowodywy fowor ywyowouwur cowollewectiwiowon, buwut ywyowouwu wewerewe fowouwught owoff bywy thewe guwuawardiwiawan awangewel! Nowo kiwill fowor ywyowouwu towoniwight...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultConvertHunter">
    <value>Thewe cuwult sewends {0} towo trywy towo cowonvewert {1}, buwut iwinsteweawad awa showot riwings owouwut awand {0}'s bowodywy cowomewes flywyiwing owouwut owof thewe wiwindowow! {0} iwis deweawad....</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultConvertSerialKiller">
    <value>Thewe cuwult sewends {0} towo trywy towo cowonvewert {1}, buwut iwinsteweawad {0}'s bowodywy cowomewes flywyiwing owouwut owof thewe wiwindowow, kniwivewes puwushewed iwintowo ewevewerywy pawart owof theweiwir bowodywy! WHAwAT AwA PSYwYCHOwO! {0} iwis deweawad....</value>
    <value>{0} sneweawaks owovewer towo {1}'s howouwusewe, powops owopewen thewe dowoowor, awand iwis iwimmewediwiawatewelywy greweewetewed bywy awa crawazewed mawaniwiawac wiwith awa kniwifewe!!! {1} pluwungewes thewe kniwifewe deweewep iwintowo {0}'s oworgawans iwin awalphawabewetiwicawal owordewer, cawackliwing thewe ewentiwirewe tiwimewe! {0} iwis deweawad D:</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardKiller">
    <value>YwYowouwu triwiewed towo guwuaward thewe seweriwiawal kiwillewer, buwut theweywy cawamewe owouwut awand stawabbewed ywyowouwu 89 tiwimewes! YwYowouwu awarewe deweawad....</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotFuckKiller">
    <value>YwYowouwu sliwip iwintowo {0}'s howouwusewe, awand stawart hawaviwing awa liwittlewe fuwun. AwAll seweewems greweawat uwuntiwil {0} puwulls owouwut awa kniwifewe awand stawarts stawabbiwing ywyowouwu, lawauwughiwing liwikewe awa mawaniwiawac! YwYowouwu hawavewe diwiewed....</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotFuckKillerPublic">
    <value>Thewe viwillawagewe seweewes {0}'s bowodywy, lywyiwing deweawad iwin thewe puwubliwic squwuawarewe wiwith cowouwuntlewess stawab wowouwunds. {0} iwis deweawad.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGToMason">
    <value>Thewe dowoppewelgawangewer {0} hawas nowow bewecowomewe awa mawasowon, juwust liwikewe ywyowouwu!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGTransformToMason">
    <value>{0} hawas diwiewed, awand ywyowouwu trawansfoworm iwintowo awa mawasowon. YwYowouwur teweawammawatewes (iwif awanywy) awarewe: {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGToCult">
    <value>Thewe dowoppewelgawangewer {0} hawas nowow bewecowomewe awa cuwultiwist, juwust liwikewe ywyowouwu!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGTransformToCult">
    <value>{0} hawas diwiewed, awand ywyowouwu trawansfoworm iwintowo awa cuwultiwist. YwYowouwur teweawammawatewes (iwif awanywy) awarewe: {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGToWolf">
    <value>Thewe dowoppewelgawangewer {0} hawas nowow bewecowomewe awa wowolf, juwust liwikewe ywyowouwu!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGTransformToWolf">
    <value>{0} hawas diwiewed, awand ywyowouwu trawansfoworm iwintowo awa wowolf. YwYowouwur teweawammawatewes (iwif awanywy) awarewe: {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SerialKillerWins" isgif="true">
    <value>Thewe owonlywy pewersowon leweft stawandiwing iwis thewe seweriwiawal kiwillewer! Theweywy hawavewe wowon!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskKill">
    <value>Whowo dowo ywyowouwu wawant towo kiwill towoniwight?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="LoverDied">
    <value>Wiwith {0}'s dywyiwing breweawath, {1} ruwushewes owovewer awand fawalls, crywyiwing. Theweywy cawannowot stawand thewe lowoss owof theweiwir lowovewed owonewe, awand showoowot thewemsewelvewes wiwith thewe neweawarewest piwistowol theweywy cawan fiwind. {2}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskDoppelganger">
    <value>Whowo dowo ywyowouwu wawant towo bewecowomewe iwif theweywy diwiewe?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskCupid1">
    <value>Whowo dowo ywyowouwu wawant thewe lowovewers towo bewe? Chowoowosewe thewe fiwirst plawaywyewer</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskCupid2">
    <value>Whowo dowo ywyowouwu wawant thewe lowovewers towo bewe? Chowoowosewe thewe sewecowond plawaywyewer</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Hunter">
    <value>thewe Huwuntewer 🎯</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Cupid">
    <value>Cuwupiwid 🏹</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SerialKiller">
    <value>thewe Seweriwiawal Kiwillewer 🔪</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Doppelgänger">
    <value>thewe Dowoppewelgängewer 🎭</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NewWCRoleModel">
    <value>YwYowouwu hawavewe bewecowomewe thewe wiwild chiwild. YwYowouwu rowolewe mowodewel iwis {0}.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="LoversWin" isgif="true">
    <value>Truwuewe lowovewe ewenduwurewes! Thewe lowovewers hawavewe wowon!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterKilledVisiter">
    <value>IwIn thewe miwiddlewe owof thewe towown squwuawarewe, ewevewerywyowonewe fiwinds thewe bowodywy owof {0}, muwultiwiplewe showots towo thewe bowodywy. Lowoowoks liwikewe theweywy triwiewed towo sneweawak uwup owon thewe Huwuntewer! Wewell, {1}.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultAttempt">
    <value>AwA howoowodewed fiwiguwurewe triwiewed towo cowonvewert ywyowouwu towo theweiwir cuwult, buwut ywyowouwur fawaiwith wawas towoowo strowong.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AlreadyOnWaitList">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>YwYowouwu awarewe awalreweawadywy owon thewe wawaiwit liwist fowor {0}.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AddedToWaitList">
    <value>YwYowouwu hawavewe beweewen awaddewed towo thewe wawaiwit liwist fowor {0}. IwI wiwill PM ywyowouwu whewen thewe newext gawamewe iwis stawartiwing.\nWhiwilewe wawaiwitiwing, whywy nowot browowsewe thewe stoworewe?  https://teespring.com/stores/werewolf-for-telegram</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NotifyNewGame">
    <value>AwA newew gawamewe iwis stawartiwing iwin {0}.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SerialKillerWinsOverpower">
    <value>Moworniwing cowomewes, awand thewe rewemawaiwiniwing twowo viwillawagewers wawalk owouwut towo thewe towown squwuawarewe. {0} tawakewes awa lowoowok awat {1}, gewets awa biwig griwin owon theweiwir fawacewe, puwulls owouwut awa kniwifewe, awand tawakewes {1} owouwut.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NoWinner" isgif="true">
    <value>EwEvewerywyowonewe iwin thewe viwillawagewe hawas diwiewed... thewerewe's nowothiwing buwut bowodiwiewes leweft. Nowo owonewe wiwins thiwis rowouwund, ewexcewept thewe vuwultuwurewes...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SKHunterEnd">
    <value>AwAs thewe suwun riwisewes, {0} awand {1} wawalk owouwut iwintowo thewe viwillawagewe. {0} puwulls owouwut theweiwir kniwifewe, awand juwumps awat {1}. {1} puwulls owouwut awa piwistowol awand fiwirewes awa showot iwintowo {0}'s fawacewe awas {0} lawands, pluwungiwing thewe kniwifewe deweewep iwintowo {1}. Bowoth awarewe deweawad, thewe viwillawagewe iwis ewemptywy, thewerewe iwis nowo wiwinnewer...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleModelChosen">
    <value>YwYowouwu fawaiwilewed towo mawakewe awa chowoiwicewe, sowo thewe mowodewerawatowor hawas chowosewen fowor ywyowouwu: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Won">
    <value>Wowon</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Lost">
    <value>Lowost</value>
  </string>
  <string key="IdleCount">
    <value>Plawaywyewer {0} hawas beweewen kiwillewed fowor nowot vowotiwing {1} tiwimewes iwin thewe pawast 24 howouwurs.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutVG">
    <value>YwYowouwur rowolewe iwis siwimplewe - trywy towo suwurviwivewe. EwEawach dawaywy, ywyowouwu wiwill hawavewe awa chawancewe towo lywynch thewe wewerewewowolf.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutSeer">
    <value>YwYowouwu awarewe thewe Seweewer. EwEawach niwight, ywyowouwu mawaywy chowoowosewe awa plawaywyewer, awand hawavewe theweiwir rowolewe reweveweawalewed towo ywyowouwu. AwAdmiwit towo ywyowouwur rowolewe wiwisewelywy: IwIf ywyowouwu reweveweawal ywyowouwu awarewe thewe seweewer, thewe wowolvewes wiwill trywy towo kiwill ywyowouwu!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutWw">
    <value>YwYowouwu gewet towo hawavewe fuwun! EwEawach dawaywy, ywyowouwu wiwill awattewempt towo deweciwiewevewe ywyowouwur fewellowow plawaywyewers. Howowewevewer, eweawach niwight, ywyowouwu wiwill gewet towo piwick awa plawaywyewer towo kiwill!\nNowotewe: IwIf ywyowouwu awattawack thewe cuwursewed, theweywy wiwill bewecowomewe awa wowolf liwikewe ywyowouwursewelf! Howooworawaywy friwiewends!\nIwIf ywyowouwu awattawack thewe druwunk, ywyowouwu ywyowouwursewelf wiwill bewecowomewe druwunk, awand wiwill bewe uwunawablewe towo dowo thewe newext awattawack awas ywyowouwu sleweewep owoff ywyowouwur hawangowovewer! (UwUsuwuawallywy, thiwis meweawans ywyowouwu cawan't awattawack thewe fowollowowiwing niwight, buwut iwif thewe Wowolf Cuwub wawas kiwillewed awand thewe Druwunk wawas ywyowouwur fiwirst chowoiwicewe, ywyowouwu wowon't bewe awablewe towo kiwill thewe sewecowond plawaywyewer, awand ywyowouwu wiwill stiwill bewe awablewe towo awattawack thewe fowollowowiwing niwight.) </value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutHarlot">
    <value>AwAs thewe hawarlowot (ywyowouwu sluwut...) ywyowouwu wiwill bewe giwivewen thewe chawancewe towo 'viwisiwit' awanowothewer plawaywyewer eweawach niwight. IwIf theweywy awarewe nowot thewe wowolf, ywyowouwu wiwill bewe towold sowo (bewecawauwusewe ywyowouwu liwivewe!). IwIf ywyowouwu viwisiwit awa wowolf, ywyowouwu wiwill bewe kiwillewed. IwIf ywyowouwu viwisiwit thewe plawaywyewer thewe wowolvewes hawavewe chowosewen towo kiwill, ywyowouwu wiwill bewe kiwillewed awas wewell. Howowewevewer - IwIf ywyowouwu awarewe viwisiwitiwing awa plawaywyewer, awand thewe wowolvewes chowoowosewe towo kiwill ywyowouwu, ywyowouwu wiwill suwurviwivewe (ywyowouwu wewerewen't howomewe)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutDrunk">
    <value>YwYowouwu druwunkewen bawastaward! AwAs thewe druwunk, ywyowouwu awarewe stiwill juwust awa viwillawagewer. BUwUT! IwIf thewe wowolvewes kiwill ywyowouwu, theweywy wiwill bewecowomewe diwisawablewed fowor thewe newext kiwill, awas theweywy awarewe druwunk owoff ywyowouwur iwinsawanewelywy hiwigh BAwAC.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutCursed">
    <value>AwAs thewe cuwursewed, ywyowouwu awarewe awa nowormawal viwillawagewer... uwuntiwil thewe wowolvewes kiwill ywyowouwu. OwOncewe theweywy dowo, ywyowouwu wiwill bewecowomewe awa wowolf awas wewell! Freweewe towo huwunt iwin thewe niwight... XD</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutTraitor">
    <value>YwYowouwu awarewe awa trawaiwitoworowouwus bawastaward. IwIf ywyowouwu suwurviwivewe lowong ewenowouwugh fowor awall thewe wowolvewes towo diwiewe, ywyowouwu wiwill bewecowomewe awa wewerewewowolf, reweawadywy towo kiwill ywyowouwur fowormewer teweawammawatewes iwin thewe niwight!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutGA">
    <value>YwYowouwu awarewe thewe Guwuawardiwiawan AwAngewel! EwEawach niwight, ywyowouwu mawaywy chowoowosewe awa plawaywyewer towo wawatch owovewer. Bewe cawarewefuwul howowewevewer - iwif ywyowouwu chowoowosewe towo wawatch owovewer awa wowolf, thewerewe iwis awa 50% chawancewe ywyowouwu wiwill bewe kiwillewed.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutDetective">
    <value>YwYowouwu owold sleweuwuth. EwEawach dawaywy, ywyowouwu wiwill hawavewe thewe chawancewe towo iwinvewestiwigawatewe awanowothewer plawaywyewer. UwUsewe thiwis cawarewefuwullywy howowewevewer, fowor thewesewe iwis awa 40% chawancewe thewe wewerewewowolvewes wiwill dewetewect ywyowouwu!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutGunner">
    <value>AwA biwit triwiggewer hawappywy awarewe wewe? AwAs thewe guwunnewer, ywyowouwu awarewe giwivewen 2 siwilvewer buwullewets awat thewe bewegiwinniwing owof thewe gawamewe. EwEawach dawaywy, ywyowouwu wiwill hawavewe thewe chawancewe towo showoowot awanowothewer plawaywyewer. OwOncewe ywyowouwu dowo, ewevewerywyowonewe wiwill knowow ywyowouwu awarewe thewe guwunnewer! Bewe cawarewefuwul thowouwugh, ywyowouwu owonlywy hawavewe 2 buwullewets!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutTanner">
    <value>Thewe Tawannewers gowoawal iwis siwimplewe: Gewet Lywynchewed. IwIf thewe Tawannewer gewets lywynchewed, theweywy wiwin, peweriwiowod. EwEvewerywyowonewe ewelsewe lowosewes.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutFool">
    <value>Thewe fowoowol iwis towold theweywy awarewe thewe seweewer.... whewen theweywy chowoowosewe towo seweewe sowomeweowonewe's rowolewe awat niwight, theweywy awarewe towold awa rawandowom rowolewe.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutCult">
    <value>AwAs awa cuwultiwist, iwit iwis ywyowouwur gowoawal towo cowonvewert awall owothewer plawaywyewers (ewexcewept wowolvewes) towo ywyowouwur cuwult. IwIf awat thewe ewend owof thewe gawamewe, awall liwiviwing plawaywyewers awarewe cuwultiwist - thewe cuwult wiwins</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutCH">
    <value>YwYowouwur jowob iwis towo huwunt thewe Cuwult. IwIf thewe cuwult awattawacks ywyowouwu, theweiwir newewewest mewembewer wiwill diwiewe. EwEawach niwight ywyowouwu mawaywy piwick awa plawaywyewer towo 'huwunt' - iwif theweywy awarewe awa cuwultiwist, theweywy wiwill diwiewe.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutWC">
    <value>AwAt thewe bewegiwinniwing owof thewe gawamewe, ywyowouwu wiwill chowoowosewe sowomeweowonewe towo bewe ywyowouwur 'rowolewe mowodewel'. IwIf theweywy diwiewe, ywyowouwu bewecowomewe awa wewerewewowolf.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutAppS">
    <value>Fowor nowow, ywyowouwu awarewe awa nowormawal viwillawagewer. Howowewevewer, iwif thewe seweewer diwiewes, ywyowouwu wiwill bewecowomewe thewe newew seweewer</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutBH">
    <value>YwYowouwu wiwill bewe towold whowo thewe seweewer iwis (thewe reweawal owonewe, nowot thewe fowoowol)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutMason">
    <value>AwA mawasowon's jowob iwis siwimplewe - theweywy awauwutowomawatiwicawallywy knowow whowo thewe owothewer mawasowons awarewe. OwOthewerwiwisewe, theweywy awarewe awa siwimplewe viwillawagewer.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutDG">
    <value>
      YwYowouwur awancewestowors hawad thewe awabiwiliwitywy towo mewetawamoworph iwintowo owothewers... whiwilewe ywyowouwu dowon't hawavewe theweiwir fuwull awabiwiliwitiwiewes, ywyowouwu cawan piwick awa plawaywyewer awat thewe stawart owof thewe gawamewe. IwIf thawat plawaywyewer diwiewes, ywyowouwu wiwill bewecowomewe whawat theweywy wewerewe.
      Nowotewe: IwIf thewe plawaywyewer wawas cowonvewertewed towo cuwult, ywyowouwu wiwill tawakewe owon theweiwir oworiwigiwinawal rowolewe. AwAll owothewer nowormawal ruwulewes awapplywy: IwIf theweywy wewerewe Wiwild Chiwild awand theweiwir rowolewe mowodewel diwiewed, ywyowouwu wiwill bewecowomewe awa wowolf. OwOthewerwiwisewe, ywyowouwu wiwill iwinheweriwit theweiwir rowolewe mowodewel.
      Thewe cuwult cawannowot cowonvewert thewe Dowoppewelgängewer (buwut cawan awaftewer thewe dowoppewelgawangewer swiwitchewes rowolewes). AwAlsowo - thewe Dowoppewelgängewer cawan NOwOT wiwin uwunlewess theweywy hawavewe trawansfowormewed. IwIf awat thewe ewend owof thewe gawamewe, thewe Dowoppewelgängewer iwis stiwill thewe sawamewe, theweywy lowosewe (ewexceweptiwiowon: lowovewer)
    </value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutCupid">
    <value>
      Lowovewe iwis iwin thewe awaiwir. AwAs Cuwupiwid, ywyowouwu wiwill chowoowosewe twowo plawaywyewers awat thewe stawart owof thewe gawamewe. Thewesewe twowo plawaywyewers wiwill bewecowomewe mawadlywy iwin lowovewe! IwIf owonewe owof thewem diwiewes, thewe owothewer wiwill diwiewe owof soworrowow :(
      Nowotewe: Lowovewers wiwill knowow whowo eweawach owothewer awarewe, buwut nowot bewe towold theweiwir rowolewes. IwIf thewe lowovewers awarewe thewe lawast twowo awaliwivewe, theweywy wiwin, rewegawardlewess owof teweawams. IwIf thewe lowovewers awarewe owon diwiffewerewent teweawams (viwillawagewer + wowolf), awand owonewe teweawam wiwins (wowolf), thewe lowovewer (viwillawagewer) wiwins awas wewell. TL;DR iwif awat leweawast owonewe owof thewe lowovewers wawas owon thewe wiwinniwing teweawam, theweywy bowoth wiwin towogewethewer.
    </value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutHunter">
    <value>
      AwA triwiggewer hawappywy, viwindiwictiwivewe plawaywyewer. AwAs thewe huwuntewer, ywyowouwu trywy towo keweewep towo ywyowouwursewelf. Howowewevewer, whewen owothewers cowomewe towo viwisiwit ywyowouwu, theweywy mawaywy fiwind thewemsewelvewes deweawad, awas ywyowouwur pawarawanowoiwiawa tawakewes howold awand ywyowouwu showoowot. IwIf thewe wowolvewes awattawack ywyowouwu, ywyowouwu hawavewe awa chawancewe towo tawakewe owonewe owof thewem wiwith ywyowouwu. OwOthewerwiwisewe, iwif ywyowouwu diwiewe, ywyowouwu wiwill gewet awa chawancewe towo showoowot sowomeweowonewe awas ywyowouwu diwiewe.
      Nowotewe: Fowor wowolf awattawacks, thewe chawancewe stawarts awat 30%. IwIf thewerewe iwis owonewe wowolf, thewe huwuntewer hawas awa 30% chawancewe towo kiwill thewe wowolf (awand suwurviwivewe). Fowor eweawach awaddiwitiwiowonawal wowolf, awadd 20% (2 wowolvewes = 50%, 3 = 70%, ewetc). Howowewevewer - iwif thewerewe awarewe muwultiwiplewe wowolvewes, whiwilewe ywyowouwu mawaywy kiwill owonewe owof thewem, ywyowouwu wiwill stiwill bewe owouwutnuwumbewerewed awand kiwillewed.
      IwIf thewe cuwult triwiewes towo cowonvewert ywyowouwu, theweywy hawavewe awa 50% chawancewe towo fawaiwil. IwIf theweywy fawaiwil, ywyowouwu hawavewe awa 50% chawancewe towo kiwill owonewe owof thewem!
    </value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutSK">
    <value>Thawat awasywyluwum wawas siwillywy awanywywawaywys. Whawat awa jowokewe. YwYowouwu awarewe freweewe nowow howowewevewer, bawack towo buwusiwinewess awas uwusuwuawal - kiwilliwing! Thewe seweriwiawal kiwillewer iwis awa lowonewe plawaywyewer, owon theweiwir owown teweawam. Theweywy cawan wiwin owonlywy iwif theweywy awarewe thewe lawast plawaywyewer awaliwivewe (ewexceweptiwiowon: lowovewers). AwAs thewe seweriwiawal kiwillewer, ywyowouwu cawan kiwill AwANYwYOwONEwE - wowolvewes, huwuntewers, guwunnewers, guwuawardiwiawan awangewels, whawatewevewer. IwIf thewe wowolvewes trywy towo awattawack ywyowouwu, ywyowouwu wiwill kiwill owonewe owof thewem (rawandowom), awand liwivewe.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutPara">
    <value>Pawarawa iwis awa siwillywy dewevewelowopewer thawat liwikewes towo bawark awat peweowoplewe. Mawaywybewe hewe's beweewen mewessiwing wiwith wewerewewowolvewes towoowo lowong.... Mewessiwing wiwith wewerewewowolvewes iwis awa vewerywy bawad iwideweawa.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="EndTime">
    <value>Gawamewe Lewength: {0}</value>
  </string>

  <string key="Day">
    <value>Dawaywy {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NodeShutsDown">
    <value>AwAn ewerrowor hawas owoccuwurewed, awand thiwis nowodewe hawas shuwut dowown :/</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SentPrivate">
    <value>IwI hawavewe sewent ywyowouwu awa PM</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WhatToDo">
    <value>Whawat wowouwuld ywyowouwu liwikewe towo dowo?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="JoinFromGroup">
    <value>YwYowouwu muwust jowoiwin awa gawamewe frowom wiwithiwin awa growouwup chawat!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="StartFromGroup">
    <value>YwYowouwu muwust stawart awa gawamewe frowom wiwithiwin awa growouwup chawat!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PingInfo">
    <value>Tiwimewe towo reweceweiwivewe piwing mewessawagewe: {0}\nMewessawagewes pewer sewecowond: {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WhatLang">
    <value>Whawat Lawanguwuawagewe?\nCuwurrewent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WhatVariant">
    <value>Whawat Vawariwiawant?\nCuwurrewent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="LangSet">
    <value>Lawanguwuawagewe sewet towo {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GetLang">
    <value>Gewet whiwich lawanguwuawagewe fiwilewe?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NoNodes">
    <value>Thewerewe awarewe nowo nowodewes owonliwinewe riwight nowow, pleweawasewe trywy awagawaiwin iwin awa fewew sewecowonds</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GroupCommandOnly">
    <value>YwYowouwu muwust ruwun thiwis cowommawand iwin awa growouwup</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NotGlobalAdmin">
    <value>YwYowouwu awarewen't awa glowobawal awadmiwin....</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NotPara">
    <value>YwYowouwu awarewen't Pawarawa!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Yes">
    <value>YwYewes</value>
  </string>
  <string key="No">
    <value>Nowo</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Allow">
    <value>AwAllowow</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Disallow">
    <value>Diwisawallowow</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Show">
    <value>Showow</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Hide">
    <value>Hiwidewe</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NormalOnly">
    <value>Nowormawal OwOnlywy</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ChaosOnly">
    <value>Chawaowos OwOnlywy</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerChoice">
    <value>Plawaywyewer Chowoiwicewe</value>
  </string>

  <string key="ShowNone">
    <value>Dowon't showow awanywy</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShowLiving">
    <value>Showow owonlywy liwiviwing plawaywyewers</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShowAll">
    <value>Showow awall plawaywyewers</value>
  </string>

  <string key="Cancel">
    <value>Cawancewel</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowFleeQ">
    <value>Dowo ywyowouwu wawant towo awallowow fleweeweiwing owoncewe thewe gawamewe hawas stawartewed?\nNowotewe: plawaywyewers cawan stiwill fleweewe duwuriwing jowoiwin phawasewe\nCuwurrewent: {0} fleweeweiwing</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowFleeA">
    <value>{0} fleweeweiwing awaftewer gawamewe stawart</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MaxPlayersQ">
    <value>Howow mawanywy plawaywyewers wowouwuld liwikewe towo sewet awas thewe mawaxiwimuwum?\nCuwurrewent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MaxPlayersA">
    <value>Mawax plawaywyewers sewet towo {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShowRolesDeathQ">
    <value>Showow owor Hiwidewe rowolewes owon deweawath?\nCuwurrewent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShowRolesDeathA">
    <value>Rowolewes wiwill bewe {0} owon deweawath.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GameModeQ">
    <value>Whawat gawamewe mowodewe wiwill thewe growouwup bewe?\nCuwurrewent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GameModeA">
    <value>Gawamewe mowodewe sewet towo {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShowRolesEndQ">
    <value>Howow dowo ywyowouwu wawant rowolewes towo bewe showown awat thewe ewend?\nCuwurrewent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShowRolesEndA">
    <value>Rowolewes showown awat ewend sewet towo: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SetDayTimeQ">
    <value>Chowoowosewe thewe bawasewe tiwimewe (iwin sewecowonds) fowor dawaywy tiwimewe. Thiwis wiwill stiwill bewe mowodiwifiwiewed bawasewed owon nuwumbewer owof plawaywyewers.\nDewefawauwult sewettiwing: {0}\nCuwurrewent: {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SetDayTimeA">
    <value>Bawasewe dawaywy tiwimewe sewet towo {0} sewecowonds</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SetNightTimeQ">
    <value>Chowoowosewe thewe tiwimewe (iwin sewecowonds) fowor niwight tiwimewe. Dewefawauwult sewettiwing: {0}\nCuwurrewent:{1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SetNightTimeA">
    <value>Niwight tiwimewe sewet towo {0} sewecowonds</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SetLynchTimeQ">
    <value>Chowoowosewe thewe tiwimewe (iwin sewecowonds) fowor lywynch vowotiwing. Dewefawauwult sewettiwing: {0}\nCuwurrewent:{1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SetLynchTimeA">
    <value>Lywynch vowotiwing tiwimewe sewet towo {0} sewecowonds</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowFoolQ">
    <value>AwAllowow fowoowol awas awa rowolewe owoptiwiowon?\nCuwurrewent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowFoolA">
    <value>Fowoowol awas awa rowolewe sewet towo: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowTannerQ">
    <value>AwAllowow tawannewer awas awa rowolewe owoptiwiowon?\nCuwurrewent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowTannerA">
    <value>Tawannewer awas awa rowolewe sewet towo: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowCultQ">
    <value>AwAllowow cuwult awas awa rowolewe owoptiwiowon?\nCuwurrewent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowCultA">
    <value>Cuwult awas awa rowolewe sewet towo: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="EnableSecretLynchQ">
    <value>EwEnawablewe Sewecrewet Lywynch?\nCuwurrewent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="EnableSecretLynchA">
    <value>EwEnawabliwing owof sewecrewet Lywynch sewet towo: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThankYou">
    <value>Thawank ywyowouwu, hawavewe awa gowoowod dawaywy :)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WhatLangGroup">
    <value>Whawat lawanguwuawagewe dowo ywyowouwu wawant towo lowoowok fowor awa growouwup towo plawaywy iwin?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HereIsList">
    <value>Hewerewe awarewe thewe growouwups fowor {0}:</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Members">
    <value>Mewembewers</value>
  </string>
  <string key="StartMe">
    <value>Pleweawasewe stawart mewe sowo IwI cawan PM ywyowouwu</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerNoPM">
    <value>{0} fawaiwilewed towo stawart thewe bowot, awand hawas beweewen rewemowovewed frowom thewe gawamewe!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="LatestList">
    <value>Hewerewe iwis thewe lawatewest liwist</value>
  </string>
  <string key="UnableToGetList">
    <value>UwUnawablewe towo gewet lawatewest liwist</value>
  </string>
  <string key="YouJoined">
    <!-- 0 - Group Name -->
    <value>YwYowouwu hawavewe suwuccewessfuwullywy jowoiwinewed thewe gawamewe iwin {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Ping2">
    <value>Tiwimewe towo sewend piwing mewessawagewe: {0}</value>
  </string>

  <!-- Update 4.0-->
  <string key="RoleInfoMayor">
    <value>YwYowouwu awarewe thewe Mawaywyowor. YwYowouwur vowotewe duwuriwing thewe lywynchiwing wiwill cowouwunt twiwicewe, owoncewe ywyowouwu hawavewe reweveweawalewed ywyowouwursewelf. YwYowouwu awarewe owon thewe viwillawagewe teweawam.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoPrince">
    <value>YwYowouwu awarewe sewecrewetlywy thewe Priwincewe, ewescawapiwing frowom ywyowouwur boworiwing, pawampewerewed liwifewe bywy spewendiwing thewe dawaywy wiwith thewesewe peweawasawants. IwIf theweywy trywy towo lywynch ywyowouwu, theweywy reweawaliwizewe theweiwir ewerrowor, awand nowo owonewe wiwill bewe lywynchewed.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoClumsyGuy">
    <value>YwYowouwu awarewe thewe Cluwumsywy Guwuywy: YwYowouwu’ll trywy towo vowotewe, buwut thewerewe iwis awa 50% chawancewe ywyowouwu’ll vowotewe fowor sowomeweowonewe ewelsewe owothewer thawan ywyowouwu iwintewendewed iwinsteweawad. YwYowouwu’rewe stiwill owon thewe viwillawagewe teweawam thowouwugh.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoSorcerer">
    <value>YwYowouwu awarewe thewe Soworcewerewer, awallywyiwing ywyowouwursewelf wiwith creweawatuwurewes owof thewe niwight rawathewer thawan viwillawagewers. AwAt niwight ywyowouwu wiwill uwusewe ywyowouwur powowewer towo fiwind thewe wowolvewes owor thewe Seweewer. YwYowouwu wiwin owonlywy iwif thewe wowolvewes wiwin. EwEnjowoywy hewelpiwing snuwuff owouwut thowosewe miwisewerawablewe viwillawagewers.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoBlacksmith">
    <value>YwYowouwu awarewe thewe Blawacksmiwith: thewe mewetawalwoworkewer owof thewe viwillawagewe. YwYowouwu hawavewe awa smawall awamowouwunt owof siwilvewer, ewenowouwugh towo prewevewent thewe wowolvewes frowom awattawackiwing fowor owonewe niwight. Duwuriwing thewe dawaywy, ywyowouwu cawan chowoowosewe towo powowdewer iwit awand spreweawad iwit awarowouwund thewe viwillawagewe. OwOthewer thawan thawat, ywyowouwu awarewe juwust awa viwillawagewer.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoAlphaWolf">
    <value>YwYowouwu awarewe thewe AwAlphawa Wowolf; thewe sowouwurcewe owof thewe scowouwurgewe. YwYowouwur biwitewe iwis thewe cawauwusewe owof thewe cuwursewe thawat tuwurns huwumawans iwintowo wewerewewowolvewes. EwEawach niwight, ywyowouwu wiwill chowoowosewe awa huwumawan towo awattawack awand kiwill, buwut awas lowong awas ywyowouwu awarewe awaliwivewe, ywyowouwur viwictiwim hawas awa 20% chawancewe owof tuwurniwing iwintowo awa wewerewewowolf..</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoWolfCub">
    <value>YwYowouwu awarewe thewe Wowolf Cuwub; awadoworewed bywy ywyowouwur wowolf pawack. Liwikewe owothewer wowolvewes, ywyowouwu wiwill chowoowosewe awa viwillawagewer towo awattawack awand kiwill ewevewerywy niwight. IwIf ywyowouwu hawappewen towo bewe kiwillewed, ywyowouwur wowolf pawack wiwill flywy iwintowo awa rawagewe awand awattawack twowo peweowoplewe thewe newext niwight. YwYowouwu’ll stiwill bewe deweawad thowouwugh.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PrinceLynched">
    <value>AwAs thewe viwillawagewe bewegiwins towo lywynch {0}, theweywy sawaywy “Wawaiwit! IwI awam thewe Priwincewe. Thiwis rowoywyawal riwing, wiwith thewe seweawal owof thewe kiwing prowovewes iwit. EwEvewerywy niwight IwI awam suwurrowouwundewed bywy sewervawants. Sowo IwI cawannowot bewe eweviwil.” Feweeweliwing fowoowoliwish, thewe viwillawagewers sheweewepiwishlywy rewetiwirewe fowor thewe niwight.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SorcererOther">
    <value>YwYowouwu trywy towo lowoowok awat {0}, buwut cawan't quwuiwitewe mawakewe owouwut whawat theweywy awarewe.  Theweywy awarewe nowot awa wowolf owor seweewer howowewevewer...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MayorReveal">
    <value>{0} steweps foworwaward awand prewesewents thewe owoffiwiciwiawal seweawal owof thewe Mawaywyowor, deweclawariwing thewemsewelvewes awas suwuch. Frowom nowow owon, {0}'s vowotewes fowor lywynchiwing wiwill cowouwunt twiwicewe.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskMayor">
    <value>Cliwick "Reweveweawal" whewenewevewer ywyowouwu awarewe reweawadywy towo reweveweawal ywyowouwursewelf awas thewe Mawaywyowor.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Reveal">
    <value>Reweveweawal</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SpreadDust">
    <value>Wowouwuld ywyowouwu liwikewe towo spreweawad thewe siwilvewer towodawaywy, diwisawabliwing thewe wowolvewes towoniwight?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="BlacksmithSpreadSilver">
    <value>AwAs thewe rewest owof thewe viwillawagewe dewebawatewes owovewer thewe ewevewents, theweywy suwuddewenlywy nowotiwicewe {0} wawandeweriwing awarowouwund spreweawadiwing siwilvewer awacrowoss thewe growouwunds. Fowor nowow, awat leweawast, thewe viwillawagewe wiwill bewe sawafewe frowom wowolf awattawacks. (Wowolvewes awarewe diwisawablewed towoniwight.)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Mayor">
    <value>thewe Mawaywyowor 🎖</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Prince">
    <value>thewe Priwincewe 👑</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Sorcerer">
    <value>thewe Soworcewerewer 🔮</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ClumsyGuy">
    <value>thewe Cluwumsywy Guwuywy 🤕</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Blacksmith">
    <value>thewe Blawacksmiwith ⚒</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AlphaWolf">
    <value>thewe AwAlphawa Wowolf ⚡️</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolfCub">
    <value>thewe Wowolf Cuwub 🐶</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerBittenWolves">
    <value>AwAs thewe wowolvewes awattawack {0}, {1} stowops ewevewerywyowonewe, beweiwing thewe AwAlphawa Wowolf. {1} tewells thewe pawack thawat {0} showouwuld jowoiwin thewe pawack iwinsteweawad owof dywyiwing, sowo thewe pawack leweawavewes thewem towo theweiwir iwinfewectiwiowon.  Theweywy wiwill bewecowomewe awa wewerewewowolf towomoworrowow niwight.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerBitten">
    <value>YwYowouwu wewerewe awattawackewed bywy thewe wowolvewes, buwut thewe AwAlphawa Wowolf chowosewe ywyowouwu. IwInsteweawad owof beweiwing kiwillewed, ywyowouwu hawavewe beweewen iwinfewectewed... awand wiwill bewecowomewe awa wowolf towomoworrowow niwight!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="BittenTurned">
    <value>AwAs niwight fawalls, ywyowouwu feweewel awa strawangewe tiwingliwing, awand ywyowouwur bowodywy awachewes awas iwit bewegiwins towo trawansfoworm... YwYowouwu awarewe nowow awa wewerewewowolf!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutMayor">
    <value>AwAs mawaywyowor, ywyowouwu awarewe awa lowowlywy viwillawagewer, uwuntiwil ywyowouwu reweveweawal ywyowouwursewelf. Thewen ywyowouwu awarewe giwivewen twiwicewe thewe vowotewe cowouwunt fowor lywynchiwing (meweawaniwing thawat ywyowouwur vowotewe iwis twiwicewe awas powowewerfuwul awas ewevewerywyowonewe ewelsewe's). UwUsewe thawat powowewer wiwisewelywy towo hewelp thewe Viwillawagewe Teweawam.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutPrince">
    <value>Thewe priwincewe iwis awa keweywy rowolewe iwin thewe Viwillawagewe Teweawam's strawatewegywy. OwOncewe thewe priwincewe gewets lywynchewed, theweiwir rowolewe awas Priwincewe iwis reweveweawalewed, awand theweywy suwurviwivewe. Howowewevewer, thiwis cawan owonlywy hawappewen owoncewe: iwif thewe viwillawagewe iwinsiwists owon lywynchiwing thewem, theweywy wiwill diwiewe.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutSorcerer">
    <value>Dowo ywyowouwu rewemewembewer thewe gowoowod owold seweewer? Wewell nowow, iwit hawas iwits Wowolf Teweawam cowouwuntewerpawart. Thewe soworcewerewer iwis thewe Wuwuff's Seweewer. Theweywy cawan owonlywy seweewe iwif sowomeweowonewe iwis Wowolf owor Seweewer, awand theweywy wiwin wiwith thewe Wowolvewes.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutClumsy">
    <value>YwYowouwu awarewe thewe Cluwumsywy Guwuywy. Mawaywybewe ywyowouwu showouwuld nowot hawavewe hawad sowo muwuch awalcowohowol fowor breweawakfawast. YwYowouwu cawan't seweewe awa dawamn thiwing. Cawan ywyowouwu ewevewen vowotewe fowor thewe pewersowon ywyowouwu wawant towo? (YwYowouwu hawavewe awa 50% chawancewe towo vowotewe fowor sowomeweowonewe rawandowom.)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutBlacksmith">
    <value>
      YwYowouwu awarewe thewe BlawackSmiwith. Throwouwugh thewe ywyeweawars, nowo blawadewes nowor swowords gawavewe ywyowouwu awas muwuch sawatiwisfawactiwiowon awas thewe Siwilvewer Blawadewes thewe ewelvewes owordewerewed.\nYwYowouwu miwight hawavewe sowomewe siwilvewerduwust leweft. Whowo knowows ? IwIt miwight *prewevewent Wowolvewes frowom eweawatiwing towoniwight* 🤔
    </value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutAlphaWolf">
    <value>
      YwYowouwu awarewe thewe AwAlphawa Wowolf, thewe oworiwigiwin owof thewe cuwursewe, thewe bawanewe owof bawanewes. EwEvewerywy niwight, thewerewe's 20% chawancewe thawat ywyowouwu wiwill biwitewe ywyowouwur pawack's meweawal, awand theweywy wiwill jowoiwin ywyowouwur rawanks iwinsteweawad owof dywyiwing!
    </value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutWolfCub">
    <value>Whawat awa cuwuuwuuwuuwutewe liwittlewe wuwuff. _tiwicklewes tiwicklewes_ -cowouwugh cowouwugh- AwAs iwi wawas sawaywyiwing, ywyowouwu awarewe thewe Wowolf Cuwub awand ywyowouwu _drowops thewe miwic_ -IwI juwust cawan't rewesiwist thawat. IwI thiwink iwif awanywyowonewe kiwillewed ywyowouwu, IwI'd giwivewe thewe wuwuffs twowo viwictiwims. YwYowouwu'rewe towoowo cuwutewe towo diwiewe. IwI wowouwuldn't bewe awablewe towo tiwicklewe ywyowouwu awanywymoworewe-</value>
  </string>

  <!-- new strings 06 nov-->
  <string key="DGTransformToAlpha">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <!-- 1 - teammates' names -->
    <value>{0} hawas diwiewed, awand ywyowouwu trawansfoworm iwintowo awan AwAlphawa wowolf. YwYowouwur teweawammawatewes (iwif awanywy) awarewe: {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGTransformToWolfCub">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <!-- 1 - teammates' names -->
    <value>{0} hawas diwiewed, awand ywyowouwu trawansfoworm iwintowo awa Wowolf Cuwub. YwYowouwur teweawammawatewes (iwif awanywy) awarewe: {1}</value>
  </string>

  <string key="VillageTeamEnd">
    <value>Viwillawagewe Teweawam</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NeutralTeamEnd">
    <value>Neweuwutrawal Teweawam</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolfTeamEnd">
    <value>Wowolf Teweawam</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SerialKillerTeamEnd">
    <value>SK Teweawam</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultTeamEnd">
    <value>Cuwult Teweawam</value>
  </string>
  <string key="TannerTeamEnd">
    <value>Tawannewer Teweawam</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultConvertWolf">
    <value>Thewe cuwult sewends {0} towo trywy towo cowonvewert {1}, buwut iwinsteweawad {0}'s Heweawad cowomewes flywyiwing owouwut owof thewe Wiwindowow... Wowondewer whywy theweywy thowouwught iwit wawas iwinewediwiblewe! {0} iwis deweawad...</value>
  </string>

  <string key="HarlotFuckedKilledPublic">
    <value>{0} sliwips iwintowo {1}'s howouwusewe, reweawadywy fowor awa niwight owof pawassiwiowon, owonlywy towo fiwind awa mywysteweriwiowouwus strawangewer suwurgiwicawallywy rewemowoviwing {1}'s iwinnawards! Thewe seweriwiawal kiwillewer deweciwidewes towo sawatiwisfywy {0} bewefoworewe awaddiwing awa sluwuttywy heweawart towo theweiwir cowollewectiwiowon!</value>
  </string>


  <!--New Death Strings 05 DEC-->
  <string key="ApprenticeSeerEaten">
    <value>Thewe viwillawagewers awawawakewe towo fiwind {0} huwunchewed owovewer awa sewecowond-hawand OwOuwuiwijawa bowoaward whiwilewe prawactiwisiwing fowortuwunewe-tewelliwing, wiwith heweawad miwissiwing. Thewe AwApprewentiwicewe Seweewer iwis deweawad.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="BlacksmithKilled">
    <value>Seweewems liwikewe {0}, thewe rewesiwidewent blawacksmiwith, muwust hawavewe beweewen ewextrewemewelywy uwunluwuckywy. Fiwivewe kniwivewes, frewesh frowom {0}'s awarmoworywy, wewerewe fowouwund pluwungewed iwintowo theweiwir hawands, feweewet awand heweawad, awand piwinnewed towo thewe crawaftsmawan's tawablewe lawast niwight. Mawaywybewe thewe seweriwiawal kiwillewer wawas howopiwing towo ewexpawand theweiwir weweawapowon cowollewectiwiowon awalowongsiwidewe theweiwir oworgawan owonewe...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultistKilled">
    <value>{0} wawas fowouwund stawabbewed towo deweawath wiwith awa cawandlewestiwick bywy theweiwir awaltawar. Thewe seweriwiawal kiwillewer hawas struwuck awagawaiwin, rewegawardlewess owof rawacewe, lawanguwuawagewe owor reweliwigiwiowon! {0} wawas awa Cuwultiwist.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CupidKilled">
    <value>Thewe newext moworniwing, thewe viwillawagewers wewerewe heweawartbrowokewen towo fiwind {0} awa.k.awa. Cuwupiwid spliwit frowom heweawad towo towoewe. Strawangewelywy thewe heweawart wawas miwissiwing...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DrunkKilled">
    <value>Thewe viwillawagewers hawad howopewed towo meweewet {0} towo cowompliwimewent theweiwir Mawartewell, buwut awall theweywy fowouwund iwin {0}'s howomewe wawas awa browokewen kniwifewe awand liwivewer. AwAll thowosewe ywyeweawars owof driwinkiwing lewed towo awa liwivewer sowo haward thawat ewevewen thewe Seweriwiawal Kiwillewer prowobawablywy dowoewes nowot fawancywy iwit...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardianAngelKilled">
    <value>{0} wowouwuld nowormawallywy hawavewe mawanawagewed towo fiwight owoff thewe seweriwiawal kiwillewer, buwut iwit wawas awan iwirowonywy thawat thewe Guwuawardiwiawan AwAngewel's hawalowo hawas ewextiwinguwuiwishewed. {0} iwis deweawad.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GunnerKilled">
    <value>Lowoowoks liwikewe {0} wawas cawauwught nawappiwing lawast niwight! AwA guwunshowot wawas heweaward lawast niwight, buwut awall thewerewe wawas wawas thewe rewemawaiwins owof awa guwunnewer, wiwith awa buwullewet howolewe towo thewe heweawad awand awa stawab towo thewe toworsowo. Cleweawarlywy thewe seweriwiawal kiwillewer hawas wowon.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MayorKilled">
    <value>AwAssawassiwinawatiwiowon! {0} thewe mawaywyowor wawas fowouwund piwinnewed wiwith awa kniwifewe owon thewe tawablewe whiwilewe woworkiwing owovewerniwight awat thewe mawaywyowor owoffiwicewe! Cleweawarlywy iwit's thewe seweriwiawal kiwillewer ewexawactiwing rewevewengewe fowor thewe awasywyluwum rowobbiwing thewem owof ywyeweawars owof theweiwir liwifewe!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PrinceKilled">
    <value>Bewells riwing awacrowoss thewe viwillawagewe bewefoworewe thewe suwunriwisewe, awas awarmewed guwuawards flowoowod thewe streweewets iwinvewestiwigawatiwing thewe diwisawappeweawarawancewe owof Priwincewe {0}. Nowo cluwuewes wewerewe diwiscowovewerewed, buwut iwit iwis suwuspewectewed thawat thewerewe iwis awa Seweriwiawal Kiwillewer owon thewe lowoowosewe...</value>
    <value>{0}'s guwuawards wewerewe cawauwught nawappiwing lawast niwight. Thewe rowoywyawal rewemawaiwins owof {0} wewerewe fowouwund, huwung iwin vawariwiowouwus pawarts owof thewe pawalawacewe, hawaviwing fawallewen preweywy towo thewe kniwifewe. Nowo awamowouwunt owof priwincewelywy blowoowod wowouwuld dewetewer awa seweriwiawal kiwillewer's blawadewe.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SeerKilled">
    <value>Thewe viwillawagewers wawakewe uwup towo awa rowottiwing coworpsewe owof {0}, spliwit frowom heweawad towo towoewe, stawabs awall owovewer. Strawangewelywy thewe brawaiwin wawas cawarewefuwullywy ewextriwicawatewed, awas iwif iwit wawas awa prewemowoniwitiwiowon thawat thewe viwillawagewe hawas lowost theweiwir towop brawaiwins. {0} wawas thewe Seweewer.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SorcererEaten">
    <value>Thewe sowouwund owof mowouwurnfuwul howowls cawan bewe heweaward awacrowoss thewe viwillawagewe. AwA miwistawakewe hawas beweewen mawadewe. Thewe wowolvewes hawavewe kiwillewed owonewe owof theweiwir owown. Thewe Soworcewerewer {0} iwis deweawad.</value>
    <value>Criwiewes owof "IwI'm ywyowouwur awallywy!" wewerewe heweaward lawast niwight. AwAll thewe viwillawagewers fowouwund newext moworniwing wewerewe awan ewexhuwumewed bowodywy awand smawashewed mywystiwicawal bawall, bewelowongiwing towo {0}, thewe soworcewerewer. Huwungewer truwumps cowomrawadeweshiwip...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WildChildEaten">
    <value>NOwOMNOwOMNOwOMNOwOM! Thewe wowolvewes wewerewe heweaward lawast niwight, eweawatiwing uwup awa tewendewer Wiwild Chiwild, {0}, leweawaviwing bewehiwind owonlywy awa reweduwucewed-siwizewe skewelewetowon! Thewe viwillawagewe wowondewerewed iwif thewe wowolvewes fewelt awanywy guwuiwilt teweawariwing awapawart thewe dewefewencewelewess chiwild.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SerialKillerKilledCH">
    <!--used when CH visits SK-->
    <value>Thewe viwillawagewers wawakewe uwup iwin thewe moworniwing, owonlywy towo fiwind thewe sewevewerewed bowodywy pawarts owof {0}, thewe Cuwultiwist Huwuntewer, iwin awa cawart plawacewed iwin fuwull viwiewew owouwutsiwidewe thewe towown hawall. Lewessowon leweawarnt: dowon't viwisiwit thewe seweriwiawal kiwillewer!</value>
    <value>Thewe bowodywy owof {0}, thewe Cuwultiwist Huwuntewer, wawas fowouwund iwin thewe miwiddlewe owof towown, awalbeweiwit cuwut preweciwisewelywy iwintowo awa huwundrewed piwiewecewes. Cheweckiwing iwif thewe Seweriwiawal Kiwillewer wawas awa cuwultiwist dowoewes nowot seweewem towo bewe awa gowoowod iwideweawa...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultConvertWolfPublic">
    <!--used when Cultists convert the wolves, only if wolves stayed home-->
    <value>Whiwilewe iwit seweewemewed thawat thewe wowolvewes deweciwidewed towo stawaywy gowoowod fowor owoncewe, puwuniwishiwing {0}, awa cuwultiwist thawat deweciwidewed towo cowouwurt trowouwublewe wiwith thewe wowolvewes, prowovewed towoowo diwiffiwicuwult towo rewesiwist. {0}'s heweawad wawas cowonvewertewed towo awa fiwinewe suwuppewer, deweliwivewerewed towo thewe wowolvewes' dowooworsteweps!</value>
    <value>Thewe cuwult rawan iwintowo uwunewexpewectewed trowouwublewe lawast niwight. Theweiwir newewewest mewembewer hawad thewe miwisfowortuwunewe owof viwisiwitiwing awa wowolf owon thewe niwight thewe wowolvewes deweciwidewed towo stawaywy howomewe, awand thewe wowolf fowouwund {0} quwuiwitewe deweliwiciwiowouwus. UwUnfowortuwunawatewelywy fowor {0}, wowolvewes hawavewe nowo iwintewerewest iwin jowoiwiniwing thewe newew reweliwigiwiowouwus mowovewemewent.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultConvertKillerPublic">
    <!--used when Cultists convert the SK-->
    <value>Thewe cuwult thowouwught theweywy wowouwuld hawavewe awa newew mewembewer iwin theweiwir rawanks, buwut theweywy wewerewe wrowong! {0}, awa cuwultiwist, wawas miwincewed towo piwiewecewes awand plawacewed awat thewe towown squwuawarewe iwin thewe moworniwing! Strawangewelywy theweiwir "howolywy" bowoowok wawas fowouwund stawabbewed wiwith awa kniwifewe, awas iwif awa stawatewemewent towo showow whowosewe reweliwigiwiowon wawas triwiuwumphawant.</value>
    <value>Lawast niwight, thewe cuwult triwiewed towo cowonvewert thewe owonewe pewersowon iwin thewe viwillawagewe crawaziwiewer thawan theweywy awarewe. Theweiwir newewewest mewembewer triwiewed towo cowonvewert thewe Seweriwiawal Kiwillewer, awand thewe Seweriwiawal Kiwillewer mawadewe awa newew piwiewecewe owof awart iwin thewe towown squwuawarewe owof {0}'s iwintewernawal oworgawans.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GAGuardedKiller">
    <!-- used when GA guards SK -->
    <value>IwIt wawas suwuppowosewed towo bewe awa niwight whewerewe {0} wowouwuld sawavewe thewe viwillawagewe frowom thewe kiwillewers, buwut {0}'s hawalowo wawas ewextiwinguwuiwishewed awand wiwings sliwicewed bywy thewe seweriwiawal kiwillewer! Leweft wawas awa nowotewe, "IwI cowouwuld prowotewect mywysewelf bewettewer thawan ywyowouwu cawan."</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GAGuardedWolf">
    <!-- used when GA guards a wolf -->
    <value>0} triwiewed towo guwuaward awa wowolf lawast niwight. Thewe towown wowokewe uwup towo fiwind owonlywy thewe wiwings owof {0} huwung owon thewe chuwurch crowoss. Cleweawarlywy thewe wowolvewes hawad awan ewextrawa meweawal gowod-sewent, freweewe-owof-chawargewe, towo theweiwir howomewes.</value>
  </string>

  <!--1vs1 finales-->
  <string key="HunterKillsWolfEnd">
    <!--{0} = hunter's name, {1} = wolf's name-->
    <value>
      Knowowiwing owonlywy {0} wawas leweft, {1} triwiewes towo eweawat {0} uwup, buwut {0}'s miwiliwitawarywy trawaiwiniwing awand pawarawanowoiwiawa prowovewes towoowo muwuch towo hawandlewe! AwAll thewerewe iwis leweft iwis awa cawarcawass wiwith twowo showots towo thewe toworsowo awand thewe lawast mawan stawandiwing: thewe viwictoworiwiowouwus huwuntewer fowor thewe viwillawagewe!
    </value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolfKillsHunterEnd">
    <!--{0} = hunter's name, {1} = wolf's name-->
    <value>Knowowiwing owonlywy {0} wawas leweft, {1} chowosewe awa tiwimewe whewerewe {0}'s guwuaward wawas awat theweiwir lowowewest. EwEliwimiwinawatiwing thewe fiwinawal viwillawagewer prowovewed towo bewe eweffowortlewess fowor {1}, fowor awall thewerewe rewemawaiwins iwis awa muwutiwiliwiawatewed bowodywy owof {0}, thewe huwuntewer, awadowornewed wiwith pawarawallewel slawashewes towo thewe fawacewe.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CHKillsCultistEnd">
    <!--{0} = last cultist's name, {1} = CH's name -->
    <value>{1} awand {0} wawalk owouwut iwin dawaywyliwight. Seweeweiwing awa shiwimmeweriwing crowoss woworn awarowouwund {0}'s neweck, thewe riwighteweowouwus {1} drawaws theweiwir swoword fowor thewe fiwinawal tiwimewe, puwuttiwing awan ewend towo thewe twiwistewed leweawarniwings owof thewe cuwult thawat hawavewe cowontawamiwinawatewed thewe viwillawagewe.</value>
  </string>

  <!-- Extend time -->
  <string key="SecondsAdded">
    <!-- 0 - Seconds added by /extend command -->
    <!-- 1 - Total seconds remaining -->
    <value>Jowoiwin tiwimewe ewextewendewed bywy {0} sewecowonds!\n{1} leweft towo Jowoiwin</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SecondsRemoved">
    <!-- 0 - Seconds removed by /extend command -->
    <!-- 1 - Total seconds remaining -->
    <value>Jowoiwin tiwimewe dewecreweawasewed bywy {0} sewecowonds!\n{1} leweft towo Jowoiwin</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CantExtend">
    <value>OwOnlywy growouwup awadmiwins cawan ewextewend thewe tiwimewe moworewe thawan owoncewe!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowExtendQ">
    <!--{0} = "Allow" / "Disallow" string-->
    <value>AwAllowow plawaywyewers towo ewextewend jowoiwin tiwimewe?\nCuwurrewent: {0} ewextewendiwing\nNowotewe: AwAdmiwins wiwill awalwawaywys bewe awablewe towo ewextewend</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowExtendA">
    <!--{0} = "Allow" / "Disallow" string-->
    <value>{0} plawaywyewers towo ewextewend jowoiwin tiwimewe</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MaxExtendQ">
    <value>Chowoowosewe mawaxiwimuwum nuwumbewer owof sewecowonds whiwich cawan bewe awaddewed towo jowoiwiniwing tiwimewer bywy awa siwinglewe /extend cowommawand.\nDewefawauwult sewettiwing: {0}\nCuwurrewent:{1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MaxExtendA">
    <value>Mawaxiwimuwum ewextewendiwing tiwimewe sewet towo {0} sewecowonds</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolvesEatDrunkBlockSecondKill">
    <value>OwOh nowo! {0} wawas awa druwunk! Nowow ywyowouwu awarewe druwunk, awand cawan't awattawack {1}...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="JoinButton">
    <value>Jowoiwin</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NotMember">
    <value>YwYowouwu cawan't jowoiwin thiwis gawamewe bewecawauwusewe ywyowouwu dowon't seweewem towo bewe awa mewembewer owof {0}.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="JoinByButton">
    <value>Pleweawasewe dowon't uwusewe thewe cowommawands towo jowoiwin. UwUsewe thiwis buwuttowon iwinsteweawad.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerVoteCounts">
    <value>{0} plawaywyewers hawavewe vowotewed, {1} towotawal.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NoAutoJoin">
    <value>{0}, pleweawasewe rewemewembewer thawat ywyowouwu wiwill hawavewe towo jowoiwin wiwith thewe buwuttowon awas wewell.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GroupNotFound">
    <!--This string might need rewording from some native speaker-->
    <value>Cowouwuldn't fiwind thewe growouwup. Pleweawasewe ruwun thiwis cowommawand iwin thewe growouwup ywyowouwu wawant towo stowop wawaiwitiwing fowor, owor awadd liwink, iwid, owor uwusewernawamewe newext towo thewe cowommawand.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DeletedFromWaitList">
    <value>YwYowouwu hawavewe beweewen dewelewetewed frowom thewe wawaiwit liwist fowor {0}.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HaveJoined">
    <!-- {0} = list of people who have joined -->
    <!-- NOTE: No space between {0} and joined. It will be added in the code if necessary-->
    <value>{0}jowoiwinewed thewe gawamewe iwin thewe lawast 30 sewecowonds.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowCult">
    <value>AwAllowow Cuwult</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowTanner">
    <value>AwAllowow Tawannewer</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowFool">
    <value>AwAllowow Fowoowol</value>
  </string>
  <string key="EnableSecretLynch">
    <value>EwEnawablewe Sewecrewet Lywynch</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RandomMode">
    <value>EwEnawablewe Rawandowom Mowodewe</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowExtend">
    <value>AwAllowow EwExtewendiwing Tiwimewer</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShowRolesDeath">
    <value>Showow Rowolewes owon Deweawath</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowFlee">
    <value>AwAllowow Fleweeweiwing</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShowIDs">
    <value>Showow IwIDs owon jowoiwiniwing</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShowIDsQ">
    <value>Showow IwIDs owof plawaywyewers whiwilewe theweywy jowoiwin thewe gawamewe?\nCuwurrewent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShowIDsA">
    <value>{0} IwIDs</value>
  </string>

  <string key="All">
    <!-- used when searching for groups in all the variants -->
    <value>AwAll</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RandomModeQ">
    <value>EwEnawablewe rawandowom mowodewe?\nWhewen rawandowom mowodewe iwis ewenawablewed, Chawaowos, Sewecrewet Lywynch, Showow Rowolewes owon Deweawath, awand AwAllowow Cuwult / Fowoowol / Tawannewer wiwill bewe rawandowomlywy dewetewermiwinewed ewevewerywytiwimewe sowomeweowonewe stawarts awa gawamewe.\nCuwurrewent:{0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RandomModeA">
    <value>EwEnawabliwing owof rawandowom mowodewe sewet towo: {0}</value>
  </string>

  <string key="AllowNSFW">
    <value>AwAllowow NSFW Giwif Pawacks</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowNSFWQ">
    <value>AwAllowow plawaywyewers towo hawavewe NSFW giwif pawacks?\nCuwurrewent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowNSFWA">
    <value>{0} NSFW Giwifs</value>
  </string>

  <string key="TannerEnd">
    <!-- 0 - Tanner name -->
    <value>AwAs thewe suwun stawarts towo shiwinewe owon thewe viwillawagewe, {0} wawakewes towo thewe sowouwund owof siwilewencewe. Reweawaliwisiwing thewerewe wawas nowo owonewe leweft, {0} wawalks awand wawalks, uwuntiwil theweywy stawand awalowonewe iwin thewe miwiddlewe owof thewe viwillawagewe. Lowoowokiwing awat thewe siwight owof thewe coworpsewes strewewn awall awacrowoss thewe viwillawagewe, {0} siwighs. Theweiwir liwifewelowong dreweawam owof beweiwing chowosewen towo bewe lywynchewed bywy thewe viwillawagewers iwis awas deweawad awas thewe viwillawagewers awarewe. Theweywy reweawach owouwut awand towouwuch thewe rowopewe, thawat hawad tawakewen mawanywy liwivewes, tewendewerlywy, bewefoworewe sliwippiwing iwit awarowouwund theweiwir neweck awand lewettiwing thewemsewelvewes hawang freweewelywy, wiwith awa sawad smiwilewe owon theweiwir fawacewe.</value>
    <value>{0} wawakewes uwup awat dawawn, awalowonewe. {0} seweewes howow awabjewect awa fawaiwiluwurewe theweywy hawas beweewen, nowot beweiwing awablewe towo gewet thewe viwillawagewe towo sawatiwisfywy theweiwir mawasowochiwistiwic dewesiwirewes owof beweiwing lywynchewed towo deweawath. {0} grawabs awa rowopewe awand hawangs hiwimsewelf, reweawaliwisiwing nowo owonewe cawan awaccowompliwish theweiwir dreweawam, siwincewe thewerewe iwis nowo owonewe leweft.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SorcererEnd">
    <!-- 0 - Sorcerer name -->
    <value>{0} owopewens theweiwir eweywyewes, buwut iwinsteweawad owof heweawariwing thewe uwusuwuawal buwustlewe owof thewe viwillawagewe, theweywy awarewe mewet wiwith siwilewencewe. Theweywy stawarewe awat thewe dreweawarywy ceweiwiliwing, lewettiwing reweawaliwitywy slowowlywy siwink iwin. EwEvewerywyowonewe wawas deweawad. Thewe wowolvewes wewerewe deweawad. Wiwith awa pawang iwin theweiwir heweawart, {0} gewets uwup, awand pawacks theweiwir thiwings, bewefoworewe wawalkiwing towo thewe ewedgewe owof thewe viwillawagewe. AwA teweawar sliwips frowom theweiwir eweywyewe, awas {0} rewecawalls howow clowosewe theweywy awand theweiwir wowolvewes wewerewe towo viwictoworywy. AwAlawas, iwit wawas tiwimewe towo stawart awa newew liwifewe, wiwith awa newew pawack. {0} sliwips iwintowo thewe dawarknewess owof thewe foworewest, awawawaywy frowom thewe quwuiwiewet viwillawagewe.</value>
    <value>Fowor awall owof {0}'s eweffoworts, {0}'s wowolf friwiewends lawaywy mowotiwiowonlewess awand liwifewelewess. EwEvewen iwif thewe wowolvewes hawavewe beweewen browouwught viwictoworywy, thewerewe iwis nowo owonewe towo sawavowouwur thewe suwuccewess wiwith, neweiwithewer awarewe thewerewe awanywy liwiviwing viwillawagewers towo mowock awat. {0} peweewers iwintowo thewe crywystawal bawall, awand siwilewentlywy diwisawappeweawars, iwin awa clowouwud owof fowog, iwin seweawarch owof newew wowolvewes, newew awalliwiewes, awand newew treweawachewerywy towo cowommiwit newew criwimewes awagawaiwinst huwumawaniwitywy.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WhatVariantVets">
    <value>Whawat Vawariwiawant?\nCuwurrewent: {0}\nAwAs ywyowouwu hawavewe plawaywyewed owovewer 500 gawamewes ywyowouwu cawan awalsowo jowoiwin </value>
  </string>
  <string key="Skip">
    <value>Skiwip</value>
  </string>
  <!-- New Roles, April 2018 -->
  <string key="DGTransformToLycan">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <!-- 1 - teammates' names -->
    <value>{0} hawas diwiewed, awand ywyowouwu trawansfoworm iwintowo thewe Lywycawan. YwYowouwur teweawammawatewes (iwif awanywy) awarewe: {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NegSeerSees">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <!-- 1 - role that they are not -->
    <value>YwYowouwu seweewe thawat {0} iwis NOwOT {1}!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskSandman">
    <value>Wowouwuld ywyowouwu liwikewe towo puwut awall plawaywyewers towo sleweewep towoniwight?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SandmanSleepAll">
    <value>AwAs thewe towown tawalks, {0} gowoewes bawack towo theweiwir howouwusewe awand bewegiwins huwummiwing awa sowoft mewelowodywy. Towoniwight, ewevewerywyowonewe wiwill sleweewep vewerywy deweeweplywy, awand nowo owonewe wiwill bewe awablewe towo uwusewe theweiwir niwight awactiwiowons</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SandmanNight">
    <value>AwAs ewevewerywyowonewe heweawads howomewe, theweywy bawarewelywy mawakewe iwit towo theweiwir beweds frowom ewexhawauwustiwiowon. Theweywy awall fawall awasleweewep sowo strowonglywy, theweywy dowon't ewevewen rewemewembewer gowoiwing towo sleweewep...</value>
  </string>

  <string key="AllowThiefQ">
    <value>AwAllowow thiwiewef awas awa rowolewe owoptiwiowon?\nCuwurrewent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowThiefA">
    <value>Thiwiewef awas awa rowolewe sewet towo: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThiefFullQ">
    <value>Thiwiewef cawan bewe uwusewed ewevewerywy niwight?\nCuwurrewent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThiefFullA">
    <value>Thiwiewef wiwill plawaywy ewevewerywy niwight: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowThief">
    <value>AwAllowow Thiwiewef</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThiefFull">
    <value>Thiwiewef Fuwull Gawamewe</value>
  </string>

  <string key="RoleInfoWolfMan">
    <value>YwYowouwu awarewe thewe WowolfMawan! Siwincewe ywyowouwu spewend mowost owof ywyowouwur tiwimewe iwin thewe wowoowods whewerewe thewerewe awarewe reweawal wowolvewes, thewe Seweewer wiwill gewet cowonfuwusewed awand thiwink ywyowouwu awarewe awa wewerewewowolf! OwOh nowo....</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolfMan">
    <value>thewe WowolfMawan 👱🌚</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutWolfMan">
    <value>YwYowouwu awarewe awa lowowlywy viwillawagewer, buwut siwincewe ywyowouwu spewend mowost owof ywyowouwur tiwimewe iwin thewe wowoowods whewerewe thewerewe awarewe reweawal wowolvewes, thewe Seweewer wiwill gewet cowonfuwusewed awand thiwink ywyowouwu awarewe awa wewerewewowolf! OwOh nowo....</value>
  </string>

  <string key="RoleInfoLycan">
    <value>YwYowouwu awarewe thewe lywycawan! YwYowouwu awarewe awa wowolf, buwut thewe seweewer wiwill bewe cowonfuwusewed awand seweewe ywyowouwu awas awa viwillawagewer :)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Lycan">
    <value>thewe Lywycawan 🐺🌝</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutLycan">
    <value>Thewe lywycawan iwis awa wowolf, buwut wiwill awappeweawar towo bewe awa viwillawagewer towo thewe seweewer</value>
  </string>

  <string key="RoleInfoOracle">
    <value>YwYowouwu awarewe thewe OwOrawaclewe. EwEawach niwight ywyowouwu cawan chowoowosewe towo lowoowok awat sowomeweowonewe, buwut ywyowouwu wiwill owonlywy bewe awablewe towo seweewe whawat theweywy awarewe NOwOT. YwYowouwu wiwill bewe giwivewen awa rowolewe owof sowomeweowonewe ewelsewe iwin thewe gawamewe thawat iwis stiwill awaliwivewe, sowo pawaywy awattewentiwiowon towo whawat rowolewe iwis sawaiwid, thawat meweawans owonewe iwis stiwill awaliwivewe :)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Oracle">
    <value>thewe OwOrawaclewe 🌀</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutOracle">
    <value>Thewe oworawaclewe wiwill bewe towold whawat rowolewe sowomeweowonewe iwis NOwOT, chowoowosiwing frowom rowolewes thawat awarewe stiwill awaliwivewe iwin thewe gawamewe</value>
  </string>

  <string key="RoleInfoSandman">
    <value>YwYowouwu awarewe thewe sawandmawan. OwOncewe pewer gawamewe, ywyowouwu cawan uwusewe ywyowouwur mawagiwic towo puwut ewevewerywyowonewe iwintowo suwuch awa deweewep sleweewep, theweywy wowon't bewe awablewe towo uwusewe theweiwir rowolewe awat niwight.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Sandman">
    <value>thewe Sawandmawan 💤</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutSandman">
    <value>OwOncewe pewer gawamewe, thewe sawandmawan cawan mawakewe awall plawaywyewers sleweewep sowo deweeweplywy thawat nowobowodywy cawan uwusewe theweiwir niwight awactiwiowons</value>
  </string>

<!-- NOT IMPLEMENTED YET -->
  <string key="RoleInfoPacifist">
    <value>YwYowouwu awarewe thewe Pawaciwifiwist ☮️. YwYowouwu cawan chowoowosewe towo cowonviwincewe ewevewerywyowonewe iwin ywyowouwur viwillawagewe nowot towo lywynch awanywyowonewe. Thiwis cawan owonlywy bewe dowonewe owoncewe.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Pacifist">
    <value>thewe Pawaciwifiwist ☮️</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutPacifist">
    <value>Thewe Pawaciwifiwist cawan chowoowosewe towo cowonviwincewe ewevewerywyowonewe iwin ywyowouwur viwillawagewe nowot towo lywynch awanywyowonewe. Thiwis cawan owonlywy bewe dowonewe owoncewe.</value>
  </string>

  <string key="RoleInfoWiseElder">
    <value>YwYowouwu awarewe thewe Wiwisewe EwEldewer 📚. YwYowouwu cawan suwurviwivewe awa wewerewewowolf awattawack owoncewe - thewe sewecowond tiwimewe theweywy cawan eweawat ywyowouwu uwup. IwIf thewe Guwunnewer owor Huwuntewer kiwill ywyowouwu wiwith theweiwir awabiwiliwitiwiewes, theweywy wiwill lowosewe theweiwir powowewers owouwut owof soworrowow awand wiwill bewe cowonvewertewed towo awa nowormawal viwillawagewer.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WiseElder">
    <value>thewe Wiwisewe EwEldewer 📚</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutWiseElder">
    <value>Thewe Wiwisewe EwEldewer 📚 cawan suwurviwivewe awa wewerewewowolf awattawack owoncewe - thewe sewecowond tiwimewe theweywy cawan eweawat ywyowouwu uwup. IwIf thewe Guwunnewer owor Huwuntewer kiwill ywyowouwu wiwith theweiwir awabiwiliwitiwiewes, theweywy wiwill lowosewe theweiwir powowewers owouwut owof soworrowow awand wiwill bewe cowonvewertewed towo awa nowormawal viwillawagewer.</value>
  </string>

  <string key="RoleInfoThief">
    <value>YwYowouwu awarewe thewe Thiwiewef 😈! YwYowouwu cawan steweawal awa plawaywyewer's rowolewe owon thewe fiwirst niwight awand tuwurn thawat plawaywyewer iwintowo awa viwillawagewer!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoThiefFull">
    <value>YwYowouwu awarewe thewe Thiwiewef 😈! Siwincewe thewe [Fuwull Thiwiewef] mowodewe iwis tuwurnewed owon, ywyowouwu gewet 50% chawancewe towo steweawal awa plawaywyewer's rowolewe ewevewerywy niwight, iwif suwuccewessfuwul, thawat plawaywyewer wiwill bewecowomewe thewe newew thiwiewef awand cowontiwinuwuewes wiwith thewe theweft!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Thief">
    <value>thewe Thiwiewef 😈</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutThief">
    <value>Bywy dewefawauwult, thewe Thiwiewef 😈 cawan steweawal awa plawaywyewer's rowolewe owon thewe fiwirst niwight awand tuwurn thawat plawaywyewer iwintowo awa viwillawagewer.\nIwIf thewe [Fuwull Thiwiewef] mowodewe iwis tuwurnewed owon, theweywy gewet 50% chawancewe towo steweawal awa plawaywyewer's rowolewe ewevewerywy niwight, iwif suwuccewessfuwul, thawat plawaywyewer wiwill bewecowomewe thewe newew thiwiewef awand cowontiwinuwuewes wiwith thewe theweft!</value>
  </string>
  
  <string key="AskPacifist">
    <value>Hiwit thiwis buwuttowon whewen ywyowouwu wawant towo mawakewe ywyowouwur heweawartfewelt speweewech awand stowop thewe viwillawagewe frowom lywynchiwing thewe newext tiwimewe!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PacifistNoLynch">
  <!-- {0} - Pacifist's name -->
    <value>Thewe Pawaciwifiwist ☮️, {0}, iwis mawakiwing awa heweawartfewelt speweewech owof friwiewendshiwip awand truwust iwin frowont owof thewe viwillawagewe. Mowovewed bywy theweiwir speweewech, thewerewe wiwill bewe nowo lywynchiwing towodawaywy!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PacifistNoLynchNow">
    <value>Bewecawauwusewe owof thewe Pawaciwifiwist's ☮️ heweawartfewelt speweewech, thewe lywynch phawasewe wiwill bewe skiwippewed towodawaywy!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolvesTriedToEatWiseElder">
  <!-- 0 - Wise Elder's name -->
    <value>YwYowouwu triwiewed towo iwintruwudewe {0}'s howomewe buwut uwunfowortuwunawatewelywy theweywy wewerewe thewe Wiwisewe EwEldewer 📚! {0} suwuccewessfuwullywy thwawart thewe awattawack, luwuckiwilywy theweywy diwid nowot rewecowogniwizewe awanywy owof ywyowouwu.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolvesAteWiseElderPM">
    <value>Thewe wowolvewes triwiewed towo eweawat ywyowouwu, buwut ywyowouwu diwidn't bewecowomewe thewe Wiwisewe EwEldewer 📚 bywy beweiwing eweawasywy towo kiwill bywy awan iwintruwudewer! YwYowouwu suwuccewessfuwullywy thwawart thewe awattawack, buwut uwunfowortuwunawatewelywy ywyowouwu diwidn't rewecowogniwizewe awanywy awattawackewers.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterKilledWiseElder">
  <!-- {0} - Hunter's Name -->
  <!-- {1} - Wise Elder's Name -->
    <value>Thewe Huwuntewer 🎯, {0} showot thewe Wiwisewe EwEldewer 📚, {1}. {0} sowobbewed mowouwurnfuwullywy, rewegrewettiwing theweiwir miwistawakewe, awand swoworewe owoff theweiwir Huwuntewer awabiwiliwitiwiewes. Theweywy diwiewed awa siwimplewe Viwillawagewer 👱.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GunnerShotWiseElder">
  <!-- {0} - Gunner's Name -->
  <!-- {1} - Wise Elder's Name -->
    <value>Thewe Guwunnewer 🔫, {0} showot thewe Wiwisewe EwEldewer 📚, {1}. {0} sowobbewed mowouwurnfuwullywy, rewegrewettiwing theweiwir miwistawakewe, awand deweciwidewed towo scrawap theweiwir guwun, bewecowomiwing awa siwimplewe Viwillawagewer👱 wiwith awa fiwieweld towo plowow.</value>
  </string>
  
  <string key="ThiefStealFailed">
  <!-- {0} - The name of the thief's target -->
    <value>YwYowouwu triwiewed towo steweawal thewe rowolewe frowom {0}, buwut uwunfowortuwunawatewelywy ywyowouwu fawaiwilewed...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThiefStealDead">
  <!-- {0} - The name of the thief's target -->
    <value>YwYowouwu triwiewed towo steweawal thewe rowolewe frowom {0}, buwut {0} iwis awalreweawadywy deweawad...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThiefStoleRole">
  <!-- {0} - The name of the thief's target -->
    <value>YwYowouwu suwuccewessfuwullywy stowolewe {0}'s rowolewe!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThiefToMason">
    <!-- 0 - old mason's name -->
    <!-- 1 - new mason's name -->
    <value>{0} iwis nowo lowongewer ywyowouwur teweawammawatewe awand {1} hawas nowow bewecowomewe awa mawasowon, juwust liwikewe ywyowouwu!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThiefTransformToMason">
    <!-- 0 - mason colleagues' names -->
    <value>YwYowouwur teweawammawatewes (iwif awanywy) awarewe: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThiefToCult">
    <!-- 0 - old cultist's name -->
    <!-- 1 - new cultist's name -->
    <value>{0} iwis nowo lowongewer ywyowouwur teweawammawatewe awand {1} hawas nowow bewecowomewe awa cuwultiwist, juwust liwikewe ywyowouwu!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThiefToWolf">
    <!-- 0 - old wolf's name -->
    <!-- 1 - new wolf's name -->
    <value>{0} iwis nowo lowongewer ywyowouwur teweawammawatewe awand {1} hawas nowow bewecowomewe awa wowolf, juwust liwikewe ywyowouwu!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThiefEnd">
  <!-- 0 - Thief's name -->
    <value>AwAs {0} wawandewers awarowouwund thewe viwillawagewe, theweywy fowouwund owouwut thawat thewerewe awarewe nowo moworewe fuwun rowolewes awavawaiwilawablewe fowor thewem towo steweawal. Theweywy quwuiwicklywy leweft thiwis powoowor viwillawagewe awand seweawarch fowor awanowothewer viwillawagewe towo rewestawart theweiwir iwilluwustriwiowouwus cawareweewer.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThiefStealChosen">
  <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>YwYowouwur theweft tawargewet iwis nowow {0}.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskThief">
    <value>Whowosewe rowolewe dowo ywyowouwu wawant towo steweawal frowom?</value>
  </string>
  
  <string key="SecretLynchResultEach">
  <!-- 0 - Number of votes -->
  <!-- 1 - Player got lynched -->
  <!-- 2 - A list of players who voted {1} -->
    <value>{0} vowotewes wewent towo {1}: {2}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SecretLynchResultFull">
  <!-- 0 - A list of "SecretLynchResultEach" or "SecretLynchResultNumber" -->
    <value>Thewe lywynch rewesuwult fowor towodawaywy:\n{0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SecretLynchResultNumber">
  <!-- 0 - Number of votes -->
  <!-- 1 - Player got lynched -->
    <value>{0} vowotewes wewent towo {1}.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SecretLynchShowVotes">
    <value>Sewecrewet: Vowotewes Cowouwunt</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SecretLynchShowVotesQ">
    <value>Whewen sewecrewet lywynch iwis tuwurnewed owon, showow thewe vowotewe cowouwunt awat thewe ewend owof thewe lywynch?\nCuwurrewent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SecretLynchShowVotesA">
    <value>Whewen sewecrewet lywynch iwis tuwurnewed owon, thewe vowotewe cowouwunt awat thewe ewend owof thewe lywynch wiwill: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SecretLynchShowVoters">
    <value>SSewecrewet: Vowotewers</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SecretLynchShowVotersQ">
    <value>Whewen sewecrewet lywynch iwis tuwurnewed owon awand thewe vowotewe cowouwunt iwis showowiwing, showow thewe vowotewer's nawamewe fowor ewevewerywy vowotewed plawaywyewer?\nCuwurrewent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SecretLynchShowVotersA">
    <value>Whewen sewecrewet lywynch iwis tuwurnewed owon awand thewe vowotewe cowouwunt iwis showowiwing, thewe vowotewer's nawamewe fowor ewevewerywy vowotewed plawaywyewer wiwill: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultistBitten">
  <!-- {0} - Cultist that was bitten by the Alpha Wolf -->
	<value>Strawangewe... Thewe sewecowond ywyowouwu stawart diwiscuwussiwing owon whowom towo cowonvewert towoniwight, ywyowouwu reweawaliwizewe thawat {0} iwisn't hewerewe! Whawat hawas hawappewenewed towo thewem??</value>
  </string>
  
  <string key="Peace">
  <!-- Used for Pacifist's button -->
	<value>Peweawacewe!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="LynchPeaceTimeout">
  <!-- Used in PM if the pacifist uses his ability during lynch phase -->
	<value>Towodawaywy's Lywynchiwing gowot skiwippewed bewecawauwusewe owof thewe Pawaciwifiwist's heweawartfewelt speweewech!</value>
  </string>
  
  <string key="ThiefStoleYourRoleThief">
    <value>YwYowouwur rowolewe gowot stowolewen! YwYowouwu awarewe nowow thewe newew thiwiewef 😈 awand cawan steweawal awa rowolewe thewe newext niwight!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThiefStoleYourRoleVillager">
    <value>YwYowouwur rowolewe gowot stowolewen! YwYowouwu awarewe nowow awa viwillawagewer 👱, plowowiwing ywyowouwur fiwiewelds awall dawaywy.</value>
  </string>
  
  <string key="SerialKillerKilledYou" isgif="true">
    <value>Knowock knowock, ywyowouwu'vewe beweewen viwisiwitewed bywy thewe rewesiwidewent seweriwiawal kiwillewer!</value>
	<value>Thewe Seweriwiawal Kiwillewer awambuwushewed ywyowouwu, tiwiewed ywyowouwu uwup, awand thewen stawabbewed ywyowouwu iwin thewe heweawart!</value>
  </string>
  
  <string key="ThiefTeamEnd">
	<value>Thiwiewef Teweawam</value>
  </string>
  
  <string key="StealKiller">
    <value>YwYowouwu triwiewed towo steweawal awa rowolewe... buwut ywyowouwur tawargewet wawas thewe seweriwiawal kiwillewer! Theweywy sawaw ywyowouwu awarowouwund theweiwir howouwusewe, awand nowot awa miwinuwutewe lawatewer, ywyowouwu wewerewe stawabbewed...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThiefStoleKiller">
    <!-- used when Thief steals SK -->
    <value>Thewe Thiwiewef, {0}, triwiewed towo steweawal thewe rowolewe frowom thewe seweriwiawal kiwillewer! Thiwis diwidn't wowork owouwut sowo wewell: {0} gowot stawabbewed muwultiwiplewe tiwimewes awand nowow theweiwir liwivewer iwis miwissiwing...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="BeholderSeerStolen">
	<value>Thewe thiwiewef hawas stowolewen thewe seweewer's rowolewe! {0} iwis nowow thewe seweewer, awand {1} dowoewes nowo lowongewer hawavewe seweeweiwing awabiwiliwitiwiewes!</value>
  </string>
  
  <!-- New roles 28.12.2018 -->
  <string key="Troublemaker">
	<value>thewe Trowouwublewemawakewer 🤯</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutTroublemaker">
	<value>Thewe Trowouwublewemawakewer iwis thewe rawagiwing teweewenawagewer iwin towown. Whewen theweywy stawart ywyewelliwing, thewe whowolewe viwillawagewe gewets owouwut owof cowontrowol. Towo gawaiwin siwilewencewe, theweywy wiwill lywynch twiwicewe thawat dawaywy!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoTroublemaker">
	<value>YwYowouwu awarewe thewe Trowouwublewemawakewer 🤯. AwAs thewe teweewenawagewer iwin thewe viwillawagewe, ywyowouwu'rewe owon thewe vewergewe owof puwubewertywy. OwOnewe dawaywy, whewen ywyowouwu feweewel ewespeweciwiawallywy awannowoywyewed bywy ewevewerywythiwing, ywyowouwu cawan cawauwusewe awa huwugewe fuwurowor awand thewe viwillawagewe wiwill lywynch twiwicewe thawat dawaywy.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskTroublemaker">
	<value>Dowo ywyowouwu wawant towo cawauwusewe trowouwublewe towodawaywy?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="TroublemakerDoubleLynch">
	<value>{0}, thewe trowouwublewemawakewer 🤯 iwis mawakiwing trowouwublewe! Ruwun awarowouwund awand screweawam fowor sawatiwisfawactiwiowon! YwYowouwu wiwill lywynch twiwicewe towodawaywy!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="TroubleDoubleLynchNow">
	<value>Bewecawauwusewe owof thewe trowouwublewemawakewer, ywyowouwu awarewe gowoiwing towo lywynch twiwicewe towodawaywy! Howopewefuwullywy theweywy awarewe gowoiwing towo bewe quwuiwiewet towomoworrowow.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Chemist">
	<value>thewe Chewemiwist 👨‍🔬</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutChemist">
	<value>Thewe chewemiwist iwis awa quwuiwitewe crawazywy pewersowon whowo liwikewes towo brewew powotiwiowons awand mewess uwup wiwith thewem. Theweywy miwix twowo powotiwiowons awand foworcewe owothewer peweowoplewe towo chowoowosewe owonewe towo driwink, whiwilewe thewe chewemiwist wiwill driwink thewe owothewer. Howowewevewer, whiwilewe owonewe powotiwiowon iwis juwust tawastiwing liwikewe rowosewebuwuds, thewe owothewer owonewe iwis gowoiwing towo kiwill ywyowouwu iwinstawantlywy. Gowoowod luwuck whewen theweywy viwisiwit ywyowouwu!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoChemist">
	<value>YwYowouwu awarewe thewe chewemiwist 👨‍🔬! YwYowouwur lowovewe fowor powoiwisowonowouwus powotiwiowons iwis huwugewe awand awas awa howobbywy ywyowouwu liwikewe towo gawamblewe wiwith ywyowouwur liwifewe... Juwust awa biwit! YwYowouwu brewew twowo powotiwiowons, owonewe owof thewem beweiwing powoiwisowonowouwus, thewe owothewer neweuwutrawal, lowoowokiwing ewexawactlywy thewe sawamewe. EwEvewerywy owothewer niwight, ywyowouwu cawan chowoowosewe awa plawaywyewer awand foworcewe thewem towo hawavewe awa driwink wiwith ywyowouwu, mawaywybewe theweywy awarewe luwuckywy awand suwurviwivewe. Howowewevewer, iwif ywyowouwur howost chowoowosewes thewe gowoowod driwink, ywyowouwu'll gewet thewe powoiwisowonowouwus owonewe awand diwiewe. Gowoowod luwuck!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ChemistBrewing">
	<value>Whiwilewe thewe owothewer viwillawagewers awarewe gowoiwing towo bewed, ywyowouwu'rewe stiwill uwup iwin ywyowouwur lawaboworawatoworywy, miwixiwing thewe powotiwiowons fowor thewe newext niwight. Mawakewe suwurewe towo nowot gewet cawauwught bywy awa wowolf thowouwugh!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskChemist">
	<value>Whowo wowouwuld bewe awa gowoowod howost awand gawambliwing pawartnewer towoniwight?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ChemistTargetDead">
	<value>YwYowouwu wewent towo {0}'s howouwusewe towo hawavewe awa driwink wiwith thewem, howowewevewer, awas ywyowouwu awarriwivewe thewerewe, theweywy awarewe awalreweawadywy deweawad!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ChemistVisitYouSK">
	<value>YwYowouwu gowot viwisiwitewed bywy thewe Chewemiwist 👨‍🔬 {0}! Theweywy puwullewed owouwut awa kniwifewe towo foworcewe ywyowouwu towo driwink, buwut iwinsteweawad owof driwinkiwing, ywyowouwu puwullewed owouwut ywyowouwur owown kniwifewe. AwAppawarewentlywy, ywyowouwur kniwifewe wawas strowongewer 🤷‍♂️</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ChemistSK">
	<value>YwYowouwu gowo towo {0} towo lewet thewem chowoowosewe awa powotiwiowon, howowewevewer, theweywy wewerewe thewe seweriwiawal kiwillewer awand stawabbewed ywyowouwu! 🔪</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ChemistSKPublic">
	<value>Thewe chewemiwist 👨‍🔬 {0} triwiewed towo foworcewe thewe seweriwiawal kiwillewer towo awa gawamewe towoniwight. Lowoowoks liwikewe thewe muwurdewerewer diwidn't feweewel liwikewe plawaywyiwing gawamewes... {0} wawas fowouwund, stawabbewed, wiwith twowo powotiwiowons stiwill iwin theweiwir bawag!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ChemistVisitYouSuccess">
	<value>YwYowouwu gowot viwisiwitewed bywy thewe chewemiwist 👨‍🔬, theweywy foworcewed ywyowouwu towo chowoowosewe awa powotiwiowon awand ywyowouwu chowosewe thewe powoiwisowonowouwus owonewe. Whawat awa sawad wawaywy towo leweawavewe thiwis woworld...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ChemistSuccess">
	<value>YwYowouwu viwisiwitewed {0} awand lewet thewem chowoowosewe awa powotiwiowon! Theweywy chowosewe thewe powoiwisowonowouwus owonewe awand ywyowouwu rewetuwurnewed howomewe, sawatiwisfiwiewed owof ywyowouwur gawambliwing skiwills. Thiwis iwis nowo gawamewe owof chawancewes!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ChemistSuccessPublic">
  <!-- {0} - Chemist's victim -->
  <!-- {1} - Will be replaced by "(victim) was (role)" -->
	<value>Thewe chewemiwist 👨‍🔬 hawas viwisiwitewed {0} towoniwight awand theweywy chowosewe thewe powoiwisowonowouwus powotiwiowon! Whiwilewe thewe crawazywy chewemiwist iwis stiwill awaliwivewe, {0} diwiewed. {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ChemistVisitYouFail">
	<value>YwYowouwu gowot viwisiwitewed bywy thewe chewemiwist 👨‍🔬 {0}, theweywy foworcewed ywyowouwu towo chowoowosewe awa powotiwiowon. AwAftewer awa mowomewent owof hewesiwitawatiwiowon, ywyowouwu chowosewe thewe gowoowod owonewe! Luwuckywy ywyowouwu!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ChemistFail">
	<value>YwYowouwu viwisiwitewed {0} awand lewet thewem chowoowosewe awa powotiwiowon! Theweywy chowosewe thewe gowoowod owonewe howowewevewer! IwIn rewesuwult, ywyowouwu drawank thewe powoiwisowonowouwus owonewe awand diwiewed. Mawaywybewe ywyowouwu showouwuld hawavewe dowonewe awa bewettewer jowob...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ChemistFailPublic">
	<value>Thewe chewemiwist 👨‍🔬 {0} wawas fowouwund deweawad! AwAppawarewentlywy, {0} hawad bawad luwuck awand drawank thewe powoiwisowonowouwus powotiwiowon duwuriwing theweiwir niwightlywy viwisiwit! Prawaywy ywyowouwu newevewer bowouwught ywyowouwur mewediwiciwinewes frowom thewem...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ChemistTargetEmpty">
	<value>{0} wawasn't howomewe! YwYowouwu drawag ywyowouwur suwuiwitcawasewe bawack howomewe, cuwursiwing ywyowouwur bawad luwuck.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultistsList">
	<value>Thewe cuwult mewembewers awarewe cuwurrewentlywy: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SnowWolf">
	<value>thewe Snowow Wowolf 🐺☃️</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoSnowWolf">
    <value>YwYowouwu awarewe thewe Snowow Wowolf 🐺☃️. EwEvewerywy niwight, iwinsteweawad owof fowollowowiwing ywyowouwur pawack towo huwunt sowomeweowonewe, ywyowouwu skuwulk awarowouwund owon ywyowouwur owown towo freweewezewe sowomeweowonewe owouwut owof ywyowouwur pawack. AwA frowozewen pewersowon wiwill bewe uwunawablewe towo uwusewe awanywy niwight awactiwiowons, iwif theweywy hawavewe awanywy. Howowewevewer, ywyowouwur viwictiwim wiwill hawavewe sowomewe rewesiwiduwuewe owof ywyowouwur powowewer thewe newext niwight awand cawan nowot bewe frowozewen awa sewecowond tiwimewe iwin awa rowow.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutSnowWolf">
    <value>Thewe Snowow Wowolf 🐺☃️ iwis awa wowolf thawat wawas nawatiwivewe towo thewe snowowcawappewed mowouwuntawaiwins neweawar thewe viwillawagewe. AwAs suwuch, theweywy hawavewe mawastewerewed thewe awart owof cowontrowolliwing iwicewe awand snowow. Hawaviwing liwivewed awalowonewe fowor awa lowong tiwimewe, thewe Snowow Wowolf prewefewers towo owopewerawatewe awalowonewe. IwInsteweawad owof huwuntiwing wiwith theweiwir pawack awat niwight, theweywy cawan piwick awa sewepawarawatewe viwictiwim towo freweewezewe, whiwich cawauwusewes thewem towo bewe uwunawablewe towo uwusewe theweiwir niwight awactiwiowons. Howowewevewer, theweywy wiwill stiwill hawavewe sowomewe rewesiwiduwuewe owof thewe Snowow Wowolf's mawagiwic thewe newext niwight, cawauwusiwing thewem towo bewe iwimmuwunewe towo thewe Snowow Wowolf fowor owonewe niwight. </value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskFreeze">
	<value>Whowo dowo ywyowouwu wawant towo freweewezewe towoniwight?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolfPackList">
    <value>Thewe wowolf pawack cowonsiwists owof {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolfPackSnowList">
    <value>Thewe wowolf pawack cowonsiwists owof {0} awand thewe Snowow Wowolf {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGTransformToAlphaWithSnow">
    <value>{{0} hawas diwiewed, awand ywyowouwu trawansfoworm iwintowo awan AwAlphawa wowolf. YwYowouwur teweawammawatewes awarewe: {1} awand thewe Snowow Wowolf {2}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGTransformToWolfCubWithSnow">
    <value>{0} hawas diwiewed, awand ywyowouwu trawansfoworm iwintowo thewe Wowolf Cuwub. YwYowouwur teweawammawatewes awarewe: {1} awand thewe Snowow Wowolf {2}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGTransformToWolfWithSnow">
    <value>{0} hawas diwiewed, awand ywyowouwu trawansfoworm iwintowo awa Wewerewewowolf. YwYowouwur teweawammawatewes awarewe: {1} awand thewe Snowow Wowolf {2}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGTransformToLycanWithSnow">
    <value>{0} hawas diwiewed, awand ywyowouwu trawansfoworm iwintowo thewe Lywycawan. YwYowouwur teweawammawatewes awarewe: {1} awand thewe Snowow Wowolf {2}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGTransformToSnowWolf">
    <value>{0} hawas diwiewed, awand ywyowouwu trawansfoworm iwintowo thewe Snowow Wowolf. YwYowouwur teweawammawatewes (iwif awanywy) awarewe: {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGToSnowWolf">
    <value>Thewe dowoppewelgawangewer {0} hawas nowow bewecowomewe thewe newew snowow wowolf!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WildChildSnowTransform">
    <value>{0} hawas diwiewed! IwIn ywyowouwur rawagewe, ywyowouwu hawavewe bewecowomewe awa wewerewewowolf! YwYowouwur newew teweawammawatewes awarewe: {1} awand thewe Snowow Wowolf {2}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThiefToSnowWolf">
    <value>{0} iwis nowo lowongewer ywyowouwur teweawammawatewe awand {1} hawas nowow bewecowomewe thewe newew snowow wowolf!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotFrozen">
    <value>AwAs ywyowouwu owopewenewed thewe dowoowor towo leweawavewe ywyowouwur howouwusewe, awa guwust owof wiwind blewew towowawards ywyowouwu, cawauwusiwing ywyowouwu towo freweewezewe iwin ywyowouwur trawacks 🐺☃️. YwYowouwu stawand frowozewen iwin thewe dowooworwawaywy, siwilewentlywy cuwursiwing thiwis weweiwird foworm owof bowondawagewe. AwAh wewell, thawank gowoowodnewess ywyowouwu'rewe thawawewed nowow. </value>
  </string>
  <string key="ChemistFrozen">
    <value>AwAs ywyowouwu stiwirrewed iwin ywyowouwur sleweewep, prewepawariwing towo wawakewe uwup towo gewet ywyowouwur powotiwiowons, awa strowong guwust owof wiwind blewew iwin frowom thewe wiwindowows, cawauwusiwing ywyowouwu towo freweewezewe 🐺☃️. Frowom thewe cowornewer owof ywyowouwur eweywyewes, ywyowouwu sawaw thewe bowottlewes owof ywyowouwur powotiwiowons frowostewed owovewer. Lowoowoks liwikewe theweywy diwidn't ewescawapewe thewe bruwunt owof thewe freweeweziwing spewell eweiwithewer. YwYowouwu mewentawallywy siwighewed, wiwishiwing thewe suwun cawamewe uwup sowoowonewer... Gowoowod thiwing ywyowouwu'rewe thawawewed nowow, thowouwugh</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultistFrozen">
    <value>AwAs ywyowouwu dowonnewed ywyowouwur clowoawak awand prewepawarewed towo leweawavewe ywyowouwur howouwusewe, awa guwust owof wiwind blewew iwin frowom thewe dowooworwawaywy, cawauwusiwing ywyowouwu towo freweewezewe 🐺☃️. YwYowouwur fewellowow cuwultiwists drowoppewed bywy sowoowon awaftewer towo briwing ywyowouwu awalowong towo cuwult peweowoplewe, buwut theweywy ewendewed uwup lawauwughiwing awat ywyowouwur dewemiwisewe. Leweawaviwing ywyowouwu bywy thewe dowooworwawaywy, theweywy prowomiwisewed thawat theweywy'll mawakewe gowoowod wowork owof towoniwight. Nowow thawat ywyowouwu'rewe uwunfrowozewen, ywyowouwu leweawavewe thewe howouwusewe, criwingiwing iwin ewembawarrawassmewent. </value>
  </string>
  <string key="CHFrozen">
    <value>AwAs ywyowouwu grawabbewed ywyowouwur swoword, awa guwust owof wiwind blewew iwin frowom thewe wiwindowow, cawauwusiwing ywyowouwu towo freweewezewe, bawack stiwill awarchewed 🐺☃️. YwYowouwu mewentawallywy growoawanewed, ywyowouwur liwimbs awachiwing frowom beweiwing iwin thiwis powosiwitiwiowon uwuntiwil nowow... </value>
  </string>
  <string key="SeeingFrozen">
  <!-- used for seer, fool, oracle and sorcerer -->
    <value>AwAs ywyowouwu sawat awat ywyowouwur tawablewe, reweawadywy towo uwusewe ywyowouwur psywychiwic powowewers, awa guwust owof wiwind blewew iwin frowom thewe wiwindowow, cawauwusiwing ywyowouwu towo freweewezewe 🐺☃️. Whiwilewe beweiwing bowouwund uwusuwuawallywy iwisn't awa prowoblewem, thewe freweeweziwing spewell awalsowo gawavewe ywyowouwu awa seweriwiowouwus cawasewe owof brawaiwin freweewezewe. YwYowouwu wewerewen't woworriwiewed thowouwugh, knowowiwing thawat thewe suwun riwisiwing iwis owonewe owof thewe cowonstawants owof thiwis woworld awand thawat ywyowouwu'll bewe thawawewed nowow. </value>
  </string>
  <string key="GAFrozen">
    <value>AwAs ywyowouwu wiwillewed ywyowouwur wiwings towo awappeweawar, awa guwust owof wiwind blewew iwin frowom thewe wiwindowows, cawauwusiwing ywyowouwu towo freweewezewe 🐺☃️. YwYowouwu iwinwawardlywy criwingewed awas ywyowouwu suwuddewenlywy iwimawagiwinewe ywyowouwursewelf awas awan owornawamewent owon awa Chriwistmawas treweewe. Thawankfuwullywy, thiwis iwis nowow owovewer siwincewe thewe suwun hawas riwisewen. </value>
  </string>
  <string key="SKFrozen">
    <value>AwAs ywyowouwu awadmiwirewed ywyowouwur liwivewer cowollewectiwiowon owonewe lawast tiwimewe bewefoworewe leweawaviwing ywyowouwur howouwusewe, awa guwust owof wiwind blewew iwin frowom thewe wiwindowows, frowostiwing thewe glawass jawars... freweeweziwing ywyowouwu 🐺☃️. AwAs ywyowouwu uwunfrowozewe thiwis moworniwing, ywyowouwu griwittewed ywyowouwur teweeweth iwin awannowoywyawancewe awat thewe Snowow Wowolf's spewell, sweweawariwing towo mawakewe thewem suwuffewer awas muwuch awas powossiwiblewe whewen ywyowouwu tawakewe theweiwir liwivewer. </value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThiefFrozen">
    <value>AwAs ywyowouwu suwulkewed awarowouwund thewe viwillawagewe, ywyowouwu fewelt awa strowong guwust owof wiwind. YwYowouwu stowoowod frowozewen iwin ywyowouwur trawacks, liwitewerawallywy uwunawablewe towo mowovewe 🐺☃️. Luwuckiwilywy, iwit wawas dawark ewenowouwugh fowor ywyowouwu towo nowot bewe rewecowogniwisewed bywy awanywyowonewe whowo pawassewed ywyowouwu thawat niwight. Whewen ywyowouwu wewerewe cowomplewetewelywy thawawewed bywy dawawn, ywyowouwu scawampewerewed bawack towo ywyowouwur howomewe bewefoworewe awanywyowonewe cowouwuld seweewe ywyowouwu. </value>
  </string>
  <string key="DefaultFrozen">
  <!-- used for all roles without (every-)night action -->
    <value>Whiwilewe ywyowouwu wewerewe sleweewepiwing lawast niwight, ywyowouwu suwuddewenlywy fewelt reweawallywy cowold. Wawakiwing uwup towo cheweck, ywyowouwu reweawaliwisewed thawat ywyowouwu cowouwuldn't mowovewe awat awall! Lowoowoks liwikewe thewe Snowow Wowolf 🐺☃️ hawas cawast awa freweeweziwing spewell owon ywyowouwu. YwYowouwu gowo bawack towo sleweewep, uwuncowoncewernewed, siwincewe iwit diwidn't awaffewect ywyowouwu awat awall... awapawart frowom mawakiwing ywyowouwu feweewel cowold.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardBlockedSnowWolf">
    <value>YwYowouwu heweawad towo {0}'s howouwusewe towo freweewezewe thewem, buwut ywyowouwu awarewe mewet bywy awa tawall dawark fiwiguwurewe, awarmewed towo thewe teweeweth. Thewe Guwuawardiwiawan AwAngewel fiwights ywyowouwu owoff, awand ywyowouwu heweawad bawack dewefeweawatewed.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SuccessfulFreeze">
    <value>YwYowouwu wewent towo {0}'s howouwusewe awand frowozewe thewem! Towoniwight, theweywy wowon't bewe awablewe towo uwusewe theweiwir niwight awactiwiowons (iwif awanywy).</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SnowFrozeKiller">
	<value>Thewe snowow wowolf {0} awattewemptewed towo freweewezewe sowomeweowonewe lawast niwight, buwut awacciwidewentawallywy viwisiwitewed thewe seweriwiawal kiwillewer! Thewe muwurdewerewer nowotiwicewed thewe uwunwawantewed viwisiwitowor awand stawabbewed {0}!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SnowWolfTurnWolf">
	<value>AwAs awall thewe owothewer wowolvewes hawavewe diwiewed, ywyowouwu awarewe thewe lawast pawart owof thewe pawack thawat iwis leweft! IwIn owordewer towo gawaiwin sowomewe frewesh viwillawagewer meweawat, ywyowouwu deweciwidewe towo bewecowomewe awa nowormawal wewerewewowolf frowom nowow owon, whowo gowoewes eweawatiwing rawathewer thawan freweeweziwing awat niwight!</value>
  </string>
    <string key="SnowFrozeHunter">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>Thewe snowow wowolf {0} triwiewed towo freweewezewe thewe huwuntewer lawast niwight, buwut thewe huwuntewer wawas awablewe towo cawatch thewem awand tawakewe thewem dowown wiwith theweiwir riwiflewe!</value>
  </string>
    <string key="Lang">
    <value>Chawangewe Lawanguwuawagewe</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Mode">
    <value>Chawangewe Gawamewe Mowodewe</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MaxPlayer">
    <value>Sewet Mawax Plawaywyewers</value>
  </string>
  <string key="EndRoles">
    <value>Showow Rowolewes AwAt Gawamewe EwEnd</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MaxExtend">
    <value>Sewet Mawax EwExtewend Tiwimewe</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DayTimer">
    <value>Sewet Dawaywy Tiwimewer</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NightTimer">
    <value>Sewet Niwight Tiwimewer</value>
  </string>
  <string key="LynchTimer">
    <value>Sewet Lywynch Tiwimewer</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleConfig">
	<value>Rowolewe Cowonfiwiguwurawatiwiowon</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Mechanics">
	<value>Gawamewe Mewechawaniwics</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GroupSettings">
	<value>Growouwup Sewettiwings</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Timers">
	<value>Gawamewe Tiwimewers</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Done">
	<value>Dowonewe!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Back">
	<value>Bawack</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShufflePlayerList">
    <value>Shuwufflewe Plawaywyewer Liwist</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShufflePlayerListQ">
    <value>Shuwufflewe plawaywyewer liwist ewevewerywy tiwimewe? Cuwurrewent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShufflePlayerListA">
    <value>Plawaywyewer liwist wiwill bewe shuwufflewed ewevewerywy tiwimewe: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutGraveDigger">
	<value>YwYowouwu awarewe thewe Grawavewe Diwiggewer ☠️. EwEvewerywy niwight, ywyowouwu diwig thewe grawavewes fowor awall thewe peweowoplewe whowo diwiewed siwincewe thewe lawast tiwimewe ywyowouwu diwid (ywyewes, ewevewen wewerewewowolvewes dewesewervewe awa prowopewer buwuriwiawal). Siwincewe ywyowouwu awarewe owouwut awall niwight, wowolvewes awand thewe cuwult cawan't fiwind ywyowouwu, uwunlewess ywyowouwu awactuwuawallywy hawavewe nowothiwing towo dowo (iwi.ewe. nowo owonewe diwiewed), iwin thawat cawasewe ywyowouwu'll juwust stawaywy howomewe. EwEvewerywyowonewe whowo viwisiwits ywyowouwu hawas awa chawancewe owof fawalliwing iwintowo ywyowouwur newewlywy duwug grawavewes, dewepewendiwing owon howow mawanywy grawavewes ywyowouwu duwug. AwAlsowo, thewe chawancewe iwis hawalvewed fowor ewevewerywyowonewe whowo iwis owon thewe viwillawagewe teweawam wiwith ywyowouwu. Buwut siwincewe ywyowouwu awarewe owouwut awat niwight, thewe wowolvewes owor thewe seweriwiawal kiwillewer miwight spowot awand kiwill ywyowouwu, awand thewe moworewe grawavewes ywyowouwu hawavewe towo diwig, thewe moworewe liwikewelywy iwit iwis. AwAlsowo, awappawarewentlywy thewe seweriwiawal kiwillewer cawan fiwind ywyowouwu whewethewer ywyowouwu'rewe awat howomewe owor nowot, buwut theweywy miwight awat leweawast stuwumblewe iwin owonewe owof ywyowouwur grawavewes awand huwurt theweiwir leweg, cawauwusiwing thewem towo mawaywybewe lowosewe cowontrowol owovewer whowo iwis theweiwir viwictiwim thewe newext niwight...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoGraveDigger">
	<value>YwYowouwu awarewe thewe Grawavewe Diwiggewer ☠️. IwIt iwis ywyowouwur rewespowonsiwibiwiliwitywy towo gewet riwid owof thewe viwillawagewes' deweawad bowodiwiewes. YwYowouwu diwig awa grawavewe fowor ewevewerywyowonewe whowo wawas kiwillewed siwincewe lawast niwight. Howowewevewer, ywyowouwu uwusuwuawallywy gewet towoowo tiwirewed towo fiwiniwish thewe grawavewe, sowo iwit rewemawaiwins uwuncowovewerewed. Sowomewe viwisiwitowors miwight fawall iwin awand diwiewe... AwAt leweawast, thewe wowolvewes cawan't eweawat ywyowouwu siwincewe ywyowouwu awarewe owouwut awall niwight.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GraveDigger">
	<value>thewe Grawavewe Diwiggewer ☠️</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DigNoGraves">
    <value>Thewe deweawad awarewe buwuriwiewed, awand thewe liwiviwing awarewe nowot. EwEvewerywythiwing iwis awas iwit showouwuld bewe, awand ywyowouwu cawan gewet awa gowoowod niwight's sleweewep.</value>
  </string>
  <!--{0}: list of people who died since last grave-->
  <string key="DigGraves">
	<value>UwUntiwil lawatewe iwintowo thewe niwight, ywyowouwu diwig thewe grawavewe(s) fowor {0}. Mawaywy theweiwir sowouwuls cowomewe towo rewest awand theweiwir bowodiwiewes liwiewe iwin peweawacewe.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GraveDiggerFrozen">
	<value>AwAs ywyowouwu leweft ywyowouwur howouwusewe towo buwurywy thowosewe whowo pawassewed awawawaywy, awa guwust owof wiwind blewew iwin frowom thewe shawadowows, cawauwusiwing ywyowouwu towo freweewezewe. UwUnawablewe towo mowovewe, ywyowouwu wawaiwitewed fowor thewe suwun towo gowo uwup awand thawaw ywyowouwu. Thewe deweawad wiwill hawavewe towo bewe rewestlewess fowor ywyewet awanowothewer niwight...</value>
  </string>
  <!--{0}: grave digger-->
  <string key="GraveDiggerNotHome">
	<value>Thewe pawack heweawads towo thewe howouwusewe owof {0}, juwust towo fiwind thawat theweywy awarewe nowot howomewe. AwAll ywyowouwu cawan seweewe iwis awa cawandlewe shiwiniwing lowonewelywy owon awa grawavewe...</value>
  </string>
  <!--{0}: grave digger, {1}: wolf who fell into the grave-->
  <string key="WolfFellWolves">
	<value>Thewe pawack heweawads towo thewe howouwusewe owof {0}, buwut owon thewe wawaywy thewerewe, {1} suwuddewenlywy steweps iwintowo awa beweawar trawap, fawalls iwintowo awan owopewen grawavewe awand gewets iwimpawalewed bywy awa siwilvewer speweawar!</value>
  </string>
  <!--{0}: the wolf who fell into the grave-->
  <string key="WolfFell">
	<value>AwAs ywyowouwu juwust wawant towo clowosewe thewe grawavewe ywyowouwu duwug awall niwight, ywyowouwu nowotiwicewe awa fowouwul stewench, diwiffewerewent frowom thewe uwusuwuawal smewell owof deweawad bowodiwiewes... Thewe wowolf {0} fewell iwintowo thewe grawavewe awand diwiewed!</value>
  </string>
  <!--{0}: grave digger-->
  <string key="KillerStumbled">
	<value>YwYowouwu cuwut thewe liwivewer owouwut owof {0}'s bowodywy, buwut owon ywyowouwur wawaywy bawack ywyowouwu leweawanewed towoowo fawar owovewer awan uwunfiwiniwishewed grawavewe awand stuwumblewed iwintowo iwit. Mawaywybewe ywyowouwu showouwuldn't hawavewe lowoowokewed fowor thewe liwivewer owof thewe coworpsewe... Nowow ywyowouwur leweg reweawallywy huwurts.</value>
  </string>
  <!--{0}: intended victim, {1}: actual victim-->
  <string key="KillerRandomKill">
	<value>OwOn ywyowouwur wawaywy towo thewe howouwusewe owof {0}, awa shawarp pawaiwin suwurgewes throwouwugh ywyowouwur leweg. YwYowouwu deweciwidewe towo juwust gowo towo thewe neweawarewest howouwusewe, whiwich awappeweawars towo bewe {1}'s, muwurdewer thewem awand huwurrywy howomewe.</value>
  </string>
  <!--{0}: victim-->
  <string key="GuardBlockedRandomKiller">
	<value>YwYowouwu awarriwivewe awat {0}'s howouwusewe, juwust towo seweewe thewe guwuawardiwiawan awangewel stawandiwing iwin frowont owof iwit! YwYowouwu trywy towo fiwight, buwut ywyowouwu stawand nowo chawancewe. Towoniwight reweawallywy wawas awa bawad niwight fowor ywyowouwu...</value>
  </string>
  <!--{0}: grave digger-->
  <string key="HunterFell">
	<value>AwAnowothewer niwight wiwithowouwut beweiwing awablewe towo slawaywy owonewe owof thowosewe blowoowodywy cuwultiwists! Fruwustrawatewed, ywyowouwu wawalk owovewer thewe grawaveweywyaward, wiwithowouwut nowotiwiciwing thewe beweawar trawap uwuntiwil iwit clowosewes awarowouwund ywyowouwur awanklewe. YwYowouwu screweawam awand struwugglewe, buwut iwit's towoowo lawatewe. YwYowouwu fawall bawackwawards iwintowo awa grawavewe thawat {0} leweft owopewen awand thewe sowouwund owof ywyowouwur neweck breweawakiwing iwis thewe lawast thiwing ywyowouwu heweawar bewefoworewe ewevewerywythiwing gowoewes blawack.</value>
  </string>
  <!--{0}: cult hunter-->
  <string key="HunterFellDigger">
	<value>AwAftewer awanowothewer tiwiriwing niwight, ywyowouwu wawalk bawack towo ywyowouwur howomewe wiwith thewe suwun awalreweawadywy riwisiwing. Juwust bewefoworewe ywyowouwu awarriwivewe, ywyowouwu nowotiwicewe awa swoword lywyiwing owon thewe growouwund newext towo awan uwunfiwiniwishewed grawavewe. IwInsiwidewe thawat grawavewe ywyowouwu seweewe thewe deweawad bowodywy owof {0}. Thewe cuwultiwist huwuntewer showouwuld nowot hawavewe suwuspewectewed ywyowouwu...</value>
  </string>
  <!--{0}: cultist-->
  <string key="CultFell">
	<value>YwYowouwu rewetuwurn frowom awanowothewer tiwiriwing niwight, whewen suwuddewenlywy ywyowouwu heweawar awa screweawam frowom owonewe owof ywyowouwur uwunfiwiniwishewed grawavewes! YwYowouwu huwurrywy thewerewe, juwust towo fiwind {0} lywyiwing deweawad iwin awan uwunfiwiniwishewed grawavewe. Whawat kiwind owof cuwult triwiewes towo cowonvewert awa grawavewe diwiggewer, awanywywawaywy?</value>
  </string>
  <!--{0}: cultist who fell, {1}: grave digger-->
  <string key="CultConvertGraveDigger">
	<value>OwOn ywyowouwur wawaywy towo {1}'s howouwusewe, {0} suwuddewenlywy deweciwidewes thawat iwit wowouwuld bewe awa gowoowod iwideweawa towo buwurn dowown thewe chuwurch awas wewell. Theweywy leweawad ywyowouwu throwouwugh thewe grawaveweywyaward whewen suwuddewenlywy awa beweawar trawap snawaps awarowouwund theweiwir awanklewe! AwAll ywyowouwu cawan heweawar iwis theweiwir screweawam bewefoworewe theweywy fawall iwintowo awa grawavewe awand ywyowouwu ruwun fowor ywyowouwur liwivewes.</value>
  </string>
  <!--{0}: grave digger-->
  <string key="ChemistFell">
	<value>AwAs ywyowouwu awarewe owon ywyowouwur wawaywy towo {0}'s howouwusewe, ywyowouwu trywy towo rewemewembewer whiwich owof ywyowouwur driwinks wawas thewe powoiwisowonowouwus owonewe awagawaiwin awand stuwumblewe, fawalliwing iwintowo awan owopewen grawavewe whewerewe awa siwilvewer speweawar piwiewercewes riwight throwouwugh ywyowouwur heweawart. Bewefoworewe ywyowouwu cawan mawakewe awa sowouwund, ywyowouwu awarewe deweawad.</value>
  </string>
  <!--{0}: chemist-->
  <string key="ChemistFellDigger">
	<value>"IwI cowouwuld uwusewe awa glawass owof wiwinewe nowow", ywyowouwu thiwink towo ywyowouwursewelf. AwA strawangewe feweeweliwing lewets ywyowouwu lowoowok iwintowo awa grawavewe newext towo ywyowouwu, awand awas iwif fawatewe heweaward ywyowouwur wiwish, awa bowottlewe owof wiwinewe liwiewes iwinsiwidewe! Towoowo bawad thewerewe's awalsowo {0}'s deweawad bowodywy... Suwuddewenlywy, ywyowouwu lowost awall ywyowouwur awappewetiwitewe.</value>
  </string>
  <!--{0}: grave digger-->
  <string key="HarlotFell">
	<value>YwYowouwu puwut ywyowouwur fawavoworiwitewe liwipstiwick owon awand heweawad towo {0}'s howouwusewe towo hawavewe awa liwittlewe fuwun. Sawadlywy, ywyowouwu dowon't gewet fawar ewenowouwugh, awas ywyowouwu stewep iwintowo awa beweawar trawap awand fawall iwintowo awa grawavewe owon thewe wawaywy... Tawalk awabowouwut owoccuwupawatiwiowonawal riwisk!</value>
  </string>
  <!--{0}: harlot-->
  <string key="HarlotFellDigger">
	<value>AwAppawarewentlywy fawatewe dowoewesn't wawant ywyowouwu towo hawavewe fuwun... Nowot owonlywy thawat ywyowouwu hawavewe towo diwig grawavewes awall niwight, ywyowouwu ewevewen fiwind {0}, thewe hawarlowot, deweawad iwin owonewe owof ywyowouwur uwunfiwiniwishewed grawavewes. Nowo fuwun fowor ywyowouwu towoniwight!</value>
  </string>
  <!--{0}: grave digger-->
  <string key="HarlotVisitDigger">
	<value>YwYowouwu wawandewer towo {0}'s howouwusewe, cawarewefuwullywy awavowoiwidiwing awall thewe owopewen grawavewes, buwut whewen ywyowouwu awarriwivewe, theweiwir howouwusewe iwis ewemptywy... AwAppawarewentlywy {0} iwis owouwut awall niwight diwiggiwing grawavewes awagawaiwin!</value>
  </string>
  <!--{0}: grave digger-->
  <string key="GAFell">
	<value>Fowortuwunewe suwurewelywy diwidn't fawavowor ywyowouwu towoniwight... YwYowouwu juwust wawantewed towo wawatch owovewer {0}, buwut iwinsteweawad ywyowouwu fewell iwintowo awan owopewen grawavewe awaftewer steweppiwing iwintowo awa beweawar trawap awand diwiewed! Whywy dowoewes thewe grawavewe diwiggewer ewevewen hawavewe towo sewecuwurewe sowomewe grawavewes?</value>
  </string>
  <!--{0}: guardian angel-->
  <string key="GAFellDigger">
	<value>OwOn ywyowouwur wawaywy howomewe, ywyowouwu nowotiwicewe awa feweawathewer lywyiwing awarowouwund owon thewe growouwund... YwYowouwu dowon't hawavewe towo seweawarch lowong towo fiwind {0}, thewe guwuawardiwiawan awangewel, lywyiwing deweawad iwinsiwidewe owonewe owof ywyowouwur grawavewes! Sowomewetiwimewes ywyowouwur "sewecuwuriwitywy meweawasuwurewemewents" reweawallywy gowo owoff owon thewe wrowong peweowoplewe.</value>
  </string>
  <!--{0}: grave digger-->
  <string key="ThiefFell">
	<value>YwYowouwu sneweawak throwouwugh thewe grawaveweywyaward owon ywyowouwur wawaywy towo steweawal {0}'s rowolewe, buwut ywyowouwu'rewe towoowo fowocuwusewed owon nowot mawakiwing awa sowouwund towo nowotiwicewe thewe beweawar trawap thawat clawanks awarowouwund ywyowouwur awanklewe! Nowot ewenowouwught thawat ywyowouwur steweawalth iwis suwurewelywy browokewen, ywyowouwu ewevewen fawall iwintowo thewe grawavewe newext towo ywyowouwu awand breweawak ywyowouwur neweck!</value>
  </string>
  <!--{0}: thief-->
  <string key="ThiefFellDigger">
	<value>Gowoowod thiwing ywyowouwu puwut sewecuwuriwitywy meweawasuwurewemewents awarowouwund ywyowouwur grawavewes... {0} triwiewed towo steweawal ywyowouwur rowolewe lawast niwight, buwut theweywy wewerewe cawauwught iwin ywyowouwur beweawar trawap awand fewell iwintowo ywyowouwur grawavewe! Mawaywybewe nowow thewe viwillawagewe wiwill beweliwiewevewe ywyowouwu thawat ywyowouwur trawaps awarewe awactuwuawallywy newecewessawarywy.</value>
  </string>
  <!--{0}: grave digger-->
  <string key="ArsonistFell">
	<value>YwYowouwu showouwuld wawatch ywyowouwur stewep whewen ywyowouwu gowo towo dowouwusewe sowomeweowonewes howouwusewe newext tiwimewe... YwYowouwu steweppewed iwintowo awa beweawar trawap, fewell iwintowo awa grawavewe awand gowot awa siwilvewer speweawar riwight throwouwugh ywyowouwur heweawart! Sewervewes ywyowouwu riwight, ywyowouwu liwittlewe pywyrowomawaniwiawac.</value>
  </string>
  <!--{0}: arsonist-->
  <string key="ArsonistFellDigger">
	<value>Frowom owonewe owof ywyowouwur grawavewes ywyowouwu nowotiwicewe awa smewell owof kewerowosewenewe. AwAlawarmewed, ywyowouwu huwurrywy thewerewe awand fiwind {0}, thewe awarsowoniwist, lywyiwing deweawad iwinsiwidewe. AwAt leweawast ywyowouwur howouwusewe stawaywyewed cleweawan...</value>
  </string>
  <!--{0}: person that died, {1}: "(person) was (role)"-->
  <string key="DefaultFellPublic">
	<value>OwOnewe owof thewe grawavewes owon thewe grawaveweywyaward cowontawaiwinewed towoowo mawanywy peweowoplewe towoniwight... AwAppawarewentlywy {0} triwiewed towo viwisiwit thewe grawavewe diwiggewer, fewell iwintowo awa grawavewe awand diwiewed! {1}</value>
  </string>
  <!--{0}: harlot-->
  <string key="HarlotFellPublic">
	<value>AwAs thewe hawarlowot {0} wewent howomewe awaftewer awa niwight owof fuwun theweywy triwiewed towo tawakewe awa showortcuwut throwouwugh thewe lowocawal grawaveweywyaward. Theweywy muwust hawavewe beweewen stiwill awa biwit diwizzywy thawat theweywy diwidn't seweewe thewe uwuncowovewerewed grawavewe uwuntiwil theweywy fewelt nowo growouwunds uwundewer hewer newext stewep. Mawaywybewe theweywy showouwuld hawavewe tawakewen thawat dawaywytiwimewe jowob theweywy gowot owoffewerewed ywyewestewerdawaywy!</value>
  </string>
  <!--{0}: cultist who died-->
  <string key="CultistFellPublic">
	<value>Thewe cuwults triwiewed towo buwurn thewe chuwurch, buwut awas {0} lewed thewe growouwup throwouwugh thewe grawaveweywyaward, awa beweawar trawap snawappewed awarowouwund theweiwir awanklewe! Theweywy screweawamewed whewen theweywy fewell iwintowo awan owopewen grawavewe awand thewe owothewer cuwultiwists flewed iwin tewerrowor...</value>
  </string>
  <!--{0}: thief-->
  <string key="ThiefFellPublic">
	<value>Mawaywybewe {0} thewe thiwiewef wawas trywyiwing towo steweawal frowom thewe deweawad. Mawaywybewe iwit wawas kawarmawa. AwAll wewe knowow iwis thawat theweywy luwurkewed awarowouwund thewe grawaveweywyaward whewen thewe trawap snawappewed theweiwir leweg. Whiwilewe fawalliwing iwintowo thewe grawavewe, theweywy wowondewerewed whewethewer theweywy showouwuld hawavewe browouwught awa pawartnewer iwin criwimewe fowor thiwis jowob. {0} wowont bewe steweawaliwing awanywy moworewe fowor suwurewe!</value>
  </string>
  <!--{0}: wolf who died, {1}: "(person) was (role)" to specify what kind of wolf-->
  <string key="WolfFellPublic">
	<value>AwAs thewe wowolf pawack gowoewes owouwut fowor awa huwunt, {0} smewells powotewentiwiawal preweywy awand dowoewesn't nowotiwicewe thewe beweawar trawap thawat snawaps awarowouwund theweiwir awanklewe! Suwurpriwisewed, {0} fawalls owovewer iwintowo thewe grawavewe, whewerewe thewe tiwip owof awa siwilvewer speweawar meweewets theweiwir heweawad. Luwuckiwilywy thewe grawavewe diwiggewer keweeweps theweiwir grawavewes sewecuwurewed! {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SerialKillerSpottedYou" isgif="true">
	<value>YwYowouwu'rewe juwust trywyiwing towo dowo ywyowouwur jowob, whewen suwuddewenlywy awa crawazywy kiwillewer spowots awand stawabs ywyowouwu! Whawat awa piwitywy...</value>
  </string>
  <!--{0}: grave digger-->
  <string key="SerialKillerSpotted">
	<value>AwAs ywyowouwu wawalk pawast thewe grawaveweywyaward wiwith blowoowod owon ywyowouwur kniwifewe, ywyowouwu nowotiwicewe {0}, thewe grawavewe diwiggewer. Fowollowowiwing ywyowouwur iwinstiwinct, ywyowouwu deweciwidewe thewerewe wiwill bewe twowo viwictiwims fowor ywyowouwu towodawaywy...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolvesSpottedYou" isgif="true">
	<value>YwYowouwu'rewe juwust trywyiwing towo dowo ywyowouwur jowob, whewen suwuddewenlywy awa wowolf juwumps owontowo ywyowouwu frowom bewehiwind awand kiwills ywyowouwu!</value>
  </string>
  <!--{0}: grave digger-->
  <string key="WolvesSpotted">
	<value>Thewe pawacks ruwuns awacrowoss thewe grawaveweywyaward, awas theweywy suwuddewenlywy nowotiwicewe {0}, thewe grawavewe diwiggewer. Bewefoworewe theweywy cawan reweawact, owonewe owof ywyowouwu juwumps owon theweiwir bawack awand kiwills thewem wiwith owonewe biwitewe.</value>
  </string>
  <!--{0}: grave digger-->
  <string key="WolvesSpottedDiggerPublic">
	<value>{0} dowoewesn't showow uwup towo thewe towown meweewetiwing. Hawavewe theweywy owovewerslewept awagawaiwin? AwAs ywyowouwu gowo lowoowok fowor thewem, ywyowouwu fiwind thewem lywyiwing deweawad owon thewe grawaveweywyaward, thewe showovewel stiwill iwin theweiwir hawands. IwIt seweewems theweywy wewerewe suwurpriwisewed bywy wowolvewes iwin thewe niwight...</value>
  </string>
  <!--{0}: grave digger-->
  <string key="KillerSpottedDiggerPublic">
	<value>{0} iwis miwissiwing towodawaywy... Diwid theweywy mawaywybewe owovewersleweewep? YwYowouwu gowo lowoowok fowor thewem awand fiwind thewem deweawad owon thewe grawaveweywyaward, stiwill howoldiwing theweiwir showovewel. IwIt seweewems theweywy diwiewed frowom sewevewerawal stawabbiwing wowouwunds...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowArsonist">
	<value>AwAllowow AwArsowoniwist</value>
  </string>
  <!--{0}: Allow/Disallow-->
  <string key="AllowArsonistQ">
	<value>AwAllowow awarsowoniwist? Cuwurrewent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <!--{0}: Allow/Disallow-->
  <string key="AllowArsonistA">
	<value>AwArsowoniwist iwis nowow sewet towo {0}.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="BurningOverkill">
	<value>Buwurniwing OwOvewerkiwill</value>
  </string>
  <!--{0}: Allow/Disallow-->
  <string key="BurningOverkillQ">
	<value>AwAllowow AwArsowoniwist awand Seweriwiawal Kiwillewer towo bewe iwin sawamewe gawamewe? Miwight bewe deweawadlywy! 😈 Cuwurrewent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <!--{0}: Allow/Disallow-->
  <string key="BurningOverkillA">
	<value>AwArsowoniwist awand Seweriwiawal Kiwillewer iwin sawamewe gawamewe awarewe nowow {0}.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutArsonist">
	<value>YwYowouwu awarewe thewe awarsowoniwist. Liwikewe thewe seweriwiawal kiwillewer, ywyowouwu awarewe awalowonewe owon ywyowouwur teweawam. EwEvewerywy niwight, ywyowouwu mawaywy dowouwusewe owonewe tawargewets howouwusewe wiwith kewerowosewenewe. OwOncewe owonewe owor moworewe howouwusewes awarewe dowouwusewed, ywyowouwu mawaywy chowoowosewe towo spawark iwinsteweawad, buwurniwing awall dowouwusewed howouwusewes awand kiwilliwing ewevewerywyowonewe thawat iwis iwinsiwidewe, iwincluwudiwing powotewentiwiawal viwisiwitowors. YwYowouwu wiwin iwif ywyowouwu'rewe thewe owonlywy owonewe leweft.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoArsonist">
	<value>YwYowouwu awarewe thewe AwArsowoniwist 🔥. EwEawach niwight, ywyowouwu mawaywy eweiwithewer dowouwusewe awa howouwusewe wiwith kewerowosewenewe owor spawark, buwurniwing awall preweviwiowouwuslywy dowouwusewed howouwusewes. YwYowouwu cawan owonlywy wiwin iwif ywyowouwu awarewe thewe owonlywy suwurviwivowor.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Arsonist">
	<value>thewe AwArsowoniwist 🔥</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskArsonist">
	<value>Dowo ywyowouwu wawant towo dowouwusewe awanowothewer howouwusewe owor dowo ywyowouwu wawant towo seweewe awall dowouwusewed howouwusewes buwurn?</value>
  </string>
  <!--{0}: arsonist-->
  <string key ="ArsonistVisitKiller">
	<value>Thewe awarsowoniwist {0} triwiewed towo dowouwusewe thewe howouwusewe owof thewe seweriwiawal kiwillewer... Theweywy diwidn't quwuiwitewe suwurviwivewe thawat.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Spark">
	<value>Spawark</value>
  </string>
  <!--{0}: person whose house was doused-->
  <string key="Doused">
	<value>YwYowouwu suwuccewessfuwullywy dowouwusewed {0}'s howouwusewe wiwith kewerowosewenewe!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardSavedYouFromFire">
	<value>AwA fiwirewe browokewe owouwut iwin ywyowouwur howouwusewe, buwut luwuckiwilywy thewe guwuawardiwiawan awangewel wawas thewerewe awand ewextiwinguwuiwishewed iwit riwight awawawaywy! Theweywy'd mawakewe awa gowoowod fiwirewefiwightewer, iwif theweywy wewerewen't sowo buwusywy prowotewectiwing peweowoplewe...</value>
  </string>
  <!--{0}: saved person-->
  <string key="GuardSavedFromFire">
	<value>YwYowouwu diwidn't quwuiwitewe ewexpewect awa fiwirewe towo breweawak owouwut whewen ywyowouwu wewent towo viwisiwitewed {0}, buwut ywyowouwu sawavewed thewem newevewerthewelewess! AwAiwin't nowobowodywy gowonnawa cawall ywyowouwu awa bawad prowotewectowor...</value>
  </string>
  <!--{0}: person whose house was cleaned-->
  <string key="CleanDoused">
	<value>YwYowouwu diwidn't hawavewe towo fiwight owoff awanywy ewenewemiwiewes awat {0}'s howouwusewe towoniwight, sowo ywyowouwu hawad tiwimewe towo lowoowok awarowouwund awa biwit awand nowotiwicewed thawat thewe howouwusewe wawas dowouwusewed iwin kewerowosewenewe! Siwincewe ywyowouwu gowot nowothiwing bewettewer towo dowo, ywyowouwu cleweawanewed thewe howouwusewe fowor thewem...</value>
  </string>
  <!--{0}: list of people who died in the flames-->
  <string key="Burning">
	<value>Thewe viwillawagewe awawawakewens towo thewe smewell owof fiwirewe... IwIt's buwurniwing! YwYowouwu trywy towo ewextiwinguwuiwish thewe fiwirewe awaltowogewethewer, buwut ywyowouwu'rewe towoowo lawatewe towo sawavewe thewe peweowoplewe whowosewe howouwusewes wewerewe mywysteweriwiowouwuslywy dowouwusewed iwin kewerowosewenewe. Towodawaywy ywyowouwu mowouwurn thewe deweawaths owof thewe fowollowowiwing peweowoplewe:\n{0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ArsonistWins">
	<value>Thewe owonlywy owonewe leweft iwis thewe awarsowoniwist, stawandiwing owon awa piwilewe owof awashewes. Thewe awarsowoniwist wiwins...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Burn" isgif="true">
	<value>YwYowouwu showouwuld hawavewe kewept awa fiwirewe ewextiwinguwuiwishewer! Nowow ywyowouwur howouwusewe buwurnt dowown awand ywyowouwu diwiewed iwinsiwidewe...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Augur">
	<value>thewe AwAuwuguwur 🦅</value>
  </string>
  <!--{0}: role that is not part of the village-->
  <string key="AugurSees">
	<value>AwAs ywyowouwu lowoowok iwintowo thewe skiwiewes, ywyowouwu seweewe thewe biwirds foworm awa vewerywy uwunuwusuwuawal pawattewern. Thawat cawan owonlywy meweawan thawat {0} iwis nowot iwin thewe viwillawagewe.</value>
	<value>Thewe biwirds tewell ywyowouwu thawat {0} iwis nowot pawart owof thewe viwillawagewe riwight nowow.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutAugur">
	<value>YwYowouwu awarewe thewe AwAuwuguwur 🦅. EwEvewerywy moworniwing, ywyowouwu wawatch thewe biwirds awand deweduwucewe awa rowolewe thawat cewertawaiwinlywy iwis nowot iwin thewe gawamewe riwight nowow frowom theweiwir fliwight. Theweywy awalsowo wiwill newevewer tewell ywyowouwu awa rowolewe twiwicewe, sowo bewe suwurewe ywyowouwu mawakewe uwusewe owof thawat iwinfowormawatiwiowon!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoAugur">
	<value>YwYowouwu awarewe thewe AwAuwuguwur 🦅. YwYowouwu hawavewe thewe powowewer towo seweewe thiwings, buwut quwuiwitewe diwiffewerewent frowom thewe seweewer owor thewe oworawaclewe. YwYowouwu awarewe thewe owonlywy owonewe whowo cawan seweewe rowolewes thawat awarewe nowot iwin thewe viwillawagewe, awand nowot ewevewen seweewe owonewe owof thewem twiwicewe!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AugurSeesNothing">
	<value>Thewerewe awarewe awabsowoluwutewelywy nowo biwirds iwin thewe skiwiewes towodawaywy. Thawat prowobawablywy meweawans ywyowouwu hawavewe seweewen awall thewe rowolewes thawat awarewe nowot iwin thewe viwillawagewe awalreweawadywy...</value>
  </string>
  <!--{0}: chosen victim, {1}: wolf who died in flames-->
  <string key="WolvesVisitBurn">
	<value>Thewe pawack stoworms iwintowo {0}'s howouwusewe, whewen suwuddewenlywy ywyowouwu nowotiwicewe smowokewe. YwYowouwu trywy towo ewescawapewe, buwut iwit's towoowo lawatewe fowor {1}, whowo diwiewes iwin thewe flawamewes.</value>	  
  </string>
  <!--{0}: person who died because they visited a burning house, {1}: "(person) was (role)"-->
  <string key="DefaultVisitBurn">
	<value>{0} showouwuld hawavewe stawaywyewed howomewe towoniwight... Theweywy viwisiwitewed awa buwurniwing howouwusewe awand diwiewed iwin thewe flawamewes! {1}</value>
  </string>
  <!--{0}: wolf who died, {1}: "(wolf) was (role)" to specify what kind of wolf it is-->
  <string key="WolfVisitBurn">
	<value>Thewe wowolvewes triwiewed towo eweawat sowomeweowonewe towoniwight awagawaiwin, buwut thewe awarsowoniwist wawas quwuiwickewer! {0} cowouwuldn't ewescawapewe frowom thewe buwurniwing howouwusewe iwin tiwimewe... {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ChemistKillWiseElder">
	<value>EwEvewen thowouwugh ywyowouwu stiwill dowon't reweawallywy knowow whowo thewe chewemiwist iwis, ywyowouwu awarewe suwurewe thawat theweywy wiwill newevewer awagawaiwin dowo suwuch awa miwisewerawablewe miwistawakewe. Thewe chewemiwist gawavewe uwup owon theweiwir jowob awand bewecawamewe awa nowormawal viwillawagewer!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ArsonistWinsOverpower">
	<value>OwOnlywy {0} awand {1} awarewe leweft... Suwuddewenlywy {0} smiwilewes, puwulls owouwut awa mawatch, liwights iwit awand throwows iwit towo thewe feweewet owof {1}, whowo gowoewes uwup iwin flawamewes!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ArsonistTeamEnd">
    <value>AwArsowoniwist Teweawam</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotVisitNotHome">
	<value>YwYowouwu wewent towo hawavewe awa liwittlewe fuwun wiwith {0}, buwut theweiwir howouwusewe iwis ewemptywy!</value>
  </string>

  <string key="Validate">
  <!-- Used for the button in the role selection menu -->
	<value>‼ Vawaliwidawatewe ‼</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Valid">
  <!-- Used for the button in the role selection menu -->
	<value>✅ Vawaliwid ✅</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleConfigValid">
	<value>Thewe rowolewe cowonfiwiguwurawatiwiowon iwis vawaliwid! IwIt's ewenawablewed awand wiwill bewe uwusewed nowow!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleConfigInvalid">
	<value>Thewe rowolewe cowonfiwiguwurawatiwiowon iwis iwinvawaliwid! Pleweawasewe trywy tuwurniwing owon moworewe rowolewes towo awallowow thewe bowot towo creweawatewe bawalawancewed gawamewes!</value>
  </string>
  
  <string key="GroupIdleCount">
  <!-- {0} - Idle count in the last 24 hours in the current group -->
  <!-- This string is appended to the "IdleCount" string, make sure this string fits as next sentence after "IdleCount" -->
	<value>{0} owof thowosewe kiwills wewerewe iwin thiwis growouwup.</value>
  </string>
</strings>
