<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<strings xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <language name="English Restaurant" base="English" variant="Restaurant" owner="Pelicopter" code="en" />
  <string deprecated="true" key="NotInGame">
    <value>You don't appear to be working in any restaurant right now...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerStartedGame">
<!-- 0 - Player name -->
    <value>{0} has opened a new Michelin 3-star restaurant called “Le Jardin Bleu”! Are you ready to cook?</value>
    <value>{0} has opened a new Michelin 3-star restaurant called “Le Jardin Bleu”! Ready for a food fight?</value>
    <value>{0} has opened a new Michelin 3-star restaurant called “Bistro a la Bobo”! Are you ready to cook?</value>
    <value>{0} has opened a new Michelin 3-star restaurant called “Bistro a la Bobo”! Ready for a food fight?</value>
    <value>{0} has opened a new Michelin 3-star restaurant called “Vie de Babi”! Are you ready to cook?</value>
    <value>{0} has opened a new Michelin 3-star restaurant called “Vie de Babi”! Ready for a food fight?</value>
    <value>{0} has opened a new Michelin 3-star restaurant called “Miel Miracle”! Are you ready to cook?</value>
    <value>{0} has opened a new Michelin 3-star restaurant called “Miel Miracle”! Ready for a food fight?</value>
    <value>{0} has opened a new Michelin 3-star restaurant called “Paradis Salé”! Are you ready to cook?</value>
    <value>{0} has opened a new Michelin 3-star restaurant called “Paradis Salé”! Ready for a food fight?</value>
    <value>{0} has opened a new Michelin 3-star restaurant called “Where there are Friends, there is France”! Are you ready to cook?</value>
    <value>{0} has opened a new Michelin 3-star restaurant called “Where there are Friends, there is France”! Ready for a food fight?</value>
    <value>“Il est temps de manger!” as the French says. Come and be a part of {0}'s renowned restaurant!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerStartedChaosGame">
<!-- 0 - Player name -->
    <value>{0} has opened a new Michelin 3-star bistro (chaos) called “Le Jardin Bleu”! Are you ready to cook?</value>
    <value>{0} has opened a new Michelin 3-star bistro (chaos) called “Le Jardin Bleu”! Ready for a food fight?</value>
    <value>{0} has opened a new Michelin 3-star bistro (chaos) called “Bistro a la Bobo”! Are you ready to cook?</value>
    <value>{0} has opened a new Michelin 3-star bistro (chaos) called “Bistro a la Bobo”! Ready for a food fight?</value>
    <value>{0} has opened a new Michelin 3-star bistro (chaos) called “Vie de Babi”! Are you ready to cook?</value>
    <value>{0} has opened a new Michelin 3-star bistro (chaos) called “Vie de Babi”! Ready for a food fight?</value>
    <value>{0} has opened a new Michelin 3-star bistro (chaos) called “Miel Miracle”! Are you ready to cook?</value>
    <value>{0} has opened a new Michelin 3-star bistro (chaos) called “Miel Miracle”! Ready for a food fight?</value>
    <value>{0} has opened a new Michelin 3-star bistro (chaos) called “Paradis Salé”! Are you ready to cook?</value>
    <value>{0} has opened a new Michelin 3-star bistro (chaos) called “Paradis Salé”! Ready for a food fight?</value>
    <value>{0} has opened a new Michelin 3-star bistro (chaos) called “Where there are Friends, there is France”! Are you ready to cook?</value>
    <value>{0} has opened a new Michelin 3-star bistro (chaos) called “Where there are Friends, there is France”! Ready for a food fight?</value>
    <value>“Il est temps de manger!” as the French says. Come and be a part of {0}'s renowned restaurant (chaos)!</value>
  </string>
  <string deprecated="true" key="NoJoinGameRunning">
    <value>You can't join now! The restaurant is already open</value>
  </string>
  <string deprecated="true" key="AlreadyJoined">
    <value>You've already joined!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MinuteLeftToJoin">
    <value>1 minute left to become a Chef</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SecondsLeftToJoin">
<!-- 0 - remaining seconds (number) -->
    <value>{0} seconds left to put on your aprons</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NotEnoughPlayers">
    <value>Not enough Chefs, closing the restaurant!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="StartingGameWait">
    <value>The restaurant is in business, please wait while I assign roles and update the database.</value>
  </string>
  <string deprecated="true" key="BannedForExploit">
<!-- 0 - Player name -->
    <value>{0} is banned for attempting an exploit (no names starting with /)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ChangeNameToJoin">
<!-- 0 - Player name -->
    <value>{0}, please change your name to join</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerLimitReached">
    <value>Sorry, max staff limit has been reached!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerJoined">
<!-- 0 - Player name -->
<!-- 1 - current players -->
<!-- 2 - Minimum players -->
<!-- 3 - Maximum players -->
    <value>{0} has become a Chef. {1} Chefs in game, {2} minimum, {3} max</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PMTheBot">
<!-- 0 - Player name -->
<!-- 1 - bot username -->
    <value>{0} Please click the start button below or {1} and start me, so I can PM you your role. You may not become a Chef until you do.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DeadFlee">
    <value>You can't flee from the restaurant because you already left!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Flee">
<!-- 0 - Player name -->
    <value>{0} has fled the restaurant with a few scones in their hands!</value>
    <value>{0} has fled the restaurant with a few tortillas in their hands!</value>
    <value>{0} has fled the restaurant with a stolen box of macarons in their hands!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerRoleWas">
<!-- 0 - Player name -->
<!-- 1 - Player role -->
    <value>{0} was {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CountPlayersRemain">
<!-- 0 - Number of players -->
    <value>{0} Chefs and staff remain.</value>
  </string>
  <string deprecated="true" key="DidntAsk">
    <value>Hey I didn't ask you anything yet!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NotPlaying">
    <value>You don't seem to be hired by the restaurant...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NoPlayerName">
    <value>I can't find a player by that name!</value>
  </string>
  <string deprecated="true" key="AnswerNonValid">
    <value>This answer is not valid!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolfVotedKill">
<!-- 0 - wolf teammate name -->
<!-- 1 - Victim name -->
    <value>{0} has voted to recruit {1} to the competitor's restaurant.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerVotedLynch">
<!-- 0 - Voter name -->
<!-- 1 - Target name -->
    <value>{0} says {1} cut open all the en papillote too early.</value>
    <value>{0} says that {1} is an idiot sandwich.</value>
    <value>{0} says that {1} served raw fish to the food critic.</value>
    <value>{0} says the lobster bisque prepared by {1} is thinner than water.</value>
    <value>{0} cannot wait for the day {1} gets demoted to be a dishwasher.</value>
    <value>{0} wants to send {1} back to culinary school to learn how to use a knife.</value>
    <value>{0} would rather have a 5-year old do the plating than ask {1} to do it.</value>
    <value>{0} says the customers' leftovers look more appetising than the tartare that {1} made.</value>
    <value>{0} saw {1} use the most expensive Chateau Lafite for flambéing!</value>
    <value>{0} says the orange genoise cake made by {1} is black as coal and hard as a brick.</value>
    <value>{0} wants {1} to go back to culinary school and learn the difference between beef and veal.</value>
    <value>{0} saw {1} take a bite out of every foie gras canister on the shelves.</value>
    <value>{0} thinks that {1} used only ketchup and water to make the chicken fricassee sauce.</value>
    <value>{0} thinks that a can opener has more functionality than {1}.</value>
    <value>{0} has never seen someone as bad as {1} because they can't even crack an egg properly.</value>
    <value>{0} thinks the chocolate truffles prepared by {1} look like rabbit droppings.</value>
    <value>{0} thinks that {1} is a cupcake nubcake.</value>
	<value>{0} saw {1} crawling under the counters like a spy.</value>
	<value>{0} says the restaurant is on track to be the worst in history thanks to {1}.</value>
	<value>{0} says the customers only eat the edible flowers on the dishes made by {1} - it's just that bad.</value>
	<value>{0} thinks that even McDonalds won't want to hire {1}.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="IdleKill">
<!-- 0 - player name -->
<!-- 1 - player role -->
    <value>{0} has been absent from voting for 2 evenings in a row and has been fired by HR. {1}</value>
    <value>{0} didn't come to pick up their paycheck for 2 evenings and was therefore fired. {1}</value>
    <value>{0} has been forgotten by everyone as they didn't show up for 2 evenings. {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="TraitorTurnWolf">
    <value>You return to work the next day to find the competitor's manager standing at the front door. You are officially offered a position in the competitor's restaurant... as a talent poacher 🍔(🐺)! Now, go and recruit more staff for the competitor, your new boss.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ChoiceAccepted">
    <value>Choice accepted.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="BeholderSeer">
<!-- 0 - seer name -->
    <value>\nThe Executive Chef 🥖(👳) is {0}.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ApprenticeNowSeer">
<!-- 0 - seer name -->
    <value>{0} was the Executive Chef. HR has informed you that you are now promoted to become the Executive Chef 🥖(👳).</value>
  </string>
  <string key="BeholderNewSeer">
<!-- 0 - apprentice name -->
<!-- 1 - seer name -->
    <value>{0} was the Sous Chef, and has now been promoted to take {1}'s place as the Executive Chef 🥖(👳).</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SeerSees">
<!-- 0 - player name -->
<!-- 1 - player role -->
    <value>After close supervision of {0} for a day, you believe that they are {1}!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskLynch">
    <value>Who should be fired today?</value>
    <value>Who do you think is a spy disguised as a chef?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskDetect">
    <value>Whose time records and performance appraisal do you want to check?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskShoot">
<!-- 0 - bullet count -->
    <value>Who do you want to accuse as a spy? {0} accusation(s) remain.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskVisit">
    <value>Who do you want to chat with today?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskSee">
    <value>Whose work do you want to oversee today?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskGuard">
    <value>Who do you want to supervise today?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskEat">
    <value>Who do you want to recruit to your restaurant?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskHunt">
    <value>Whose lunchbox will you check?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskRoleModel">
    <value>Who will be your mentor?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskConvert">
    <value>Who do you want to inspire to try your vegan lunchbox?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DiscussWith">
<!--Leave the leading spaces here please-->
<!-- 0 - teammate names -->
    <value>  Make sure you discuss with {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="And">
<!--this is paired with "DiscussWith".  again, leave the spaces!-->
    <value> and </value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoCursed">
    <value>You are the Kitchen Porter 💩(😾). Your job is even worse than the Dishwasher's because you are responsible for cleaning the toilets and the floors of the kitchen (including the stinky Durian warehouse...). So eager to leave your job and get a higher pay, if a spy from the competitor talks to you during the day, you will immediately accept their offer and even help them to invite other Chefs to join the competitor's restaurant.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoDetective">
    <value>You are the Accountant 🕰(🕵️). At the end of every working day, you have to sit at your desk at the corner of the office and issue everyone's paycheck, during which you have the option to do a detailed check on the working hour records and the performance appraisal of that person. In the process, you may learn something about their job and whether or not they are a spy... Be careful to work quietly or else the spies may notice you hunched at your desk in the corner! (40% chance)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoDrunk">
    <value>You are the Sommelier 🍷(🍻) who is in charge of the wine service. You know your way around the best wines such as the different Pinot Noirs.  If the talent poachers recruit you, they would take your keys and enter your wine cellar. They would then take sips from the Pinot Noirs stocked there and get so drunk that they would have to take a day off on the next day.</value>
    <value>You are the Sommelier 🍷(🍻) who is in charge of the wine service. You know your way around the best wines such as the different Chardonnays.  If the talent poachers recruit you, they would take your keys and enter your wine cellar. They would then take sips from the Chardonnays stocked there and get so drunk that they would have to take a day off on the next day.</value>
    <value>You are the Sommelier 🍷(🍻) who is in charge of the wine service. You know your way around the best wines such as the different Toscanas.  If the talent poachers recruit you, they would take your keys and enter your wine cellar. They would then take sips from the Toscanas stocked there and get so drunk that they would have to take a day off on the next day.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoGuardianAngel">
    <value>You are the Safety Supervisor ⚠️(👼). You enforce kitchen safety rules to prevent deadly accidents. Each day, you can supervise one of the Chefs from afar. If you see them about to do something dangerous, you would drag them out to the back-alley and give them a talking. Be careful though - if you supervised a spy or dangerous chef, you could be the one getting into danger!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoGunner">
    <value>You are the Senior Chef 🧀(🔫). You worked for over 30 years in this kitchen and your advice has a lot of influence. Every day, you can advise the restaurant's owner about a possible spy chef. By the end of the day, the owner will publicly fire the one you accused with you standing next to them, letting everyone know that you were responsible. You only get a maximum of 2 accusations!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoHarlot">
    <value>You are the Server 🍒(💋). You are a chatterbox who loves to chat with customers and all the staff in the kitchen. It is also your duty to take the customers' orders and deliver the food to them. Each day, apart from delivering the dishes, you will choose to use your spare time to chat with one of the staff in the back-alley. If you chose to chat with a spy, you will be some fascinated by their persuasion that you resign immediately to start a wonderful new career in the competitor's restaurant.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoTraitor">
    <value>You are the Valet Attendant 🔑(🖕),  standing at the main door to help customers park their cars. You have a low-pay, boring job, but because you always see the ads on the competitor's restaurant across the street, you always think about getting a better job there some day. \n\nWhen all Talent Poachers 🍔(🐺) are fired from this restaurant, the competitor would invite you to become one and you will eagerly accept the offer. When you go into the kitchen to get a drink, the Executive Chef may see you as just a normal Line Cook 🧑‍🍳(👱)!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoWolf">
    <value>You are a Talent Poacher 🍔(🐺)! You were hired by this restaurant's competitor (who is across the street) to work as a Chef. The competitor is trying to dismantle this Michelin 3-star restaurant by taking all their talented staff away, and it is your job every day to invite one staff and persuade them to quit their job and join the competitor's restaurant instead.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoSeer">
    <value>You are the Executive Chef 🥖(👳). Thanks to your excellent leadership and menu-planning, this restaurant received its 3 Michelin stars a few years ago. To ensure your staff are performing at the highest standards, you can supervise any staff of your choice every day in secret (e.g. tasting the dishes they make), after which you will also learn their role.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoVillager">
    <value>You are a Line Cook 🧑‍🍳(👱). This restaurant has 3 Michelin stars thanks to the many complicated and fancy dishes that the Executive Chef has planned. You are merely a chef working on cutting lemons and limes for the seafood line. Time to get chopping!</value>
    <value>You are a Line Cook 🧑‍🍳(👱). This restaurant has 3 Michelin stars thanks to the many complicated and fancy dishes that the Executive Chef has planned. You are merely a chef working on frenching the lamb racks for the meat line. Time to get frenching!</value>
    <value>You are a Line Cook 🧑‍🍳(👱). This restaurant has 3 Michelin stars thanks to the many complicated and fancy dishes that the Executive Chef has planned. You are merely a chef working on mixing egg yolks with sugar for the pastry line. Time to get mixing!</value>
    <value>You are a Line Cook 🧑‍🍳(👱). This restaurant has 3 Michelin stars thanks to the many complicated and fancy dishes that the Executive Chef has planned. You are merely a chef working on slicing and assembling carrots into roses. Time to get slicing!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoTanner">
    <value>You are the Dishwasher 🧽(👺). With the worst pay in the restaurant, you would be more than excited to be fired as the severance pay you get is worth 6 months of your pay (someone should review these contracts...)!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoWildChild">
    <value>You are a Commis Chef 🧅(👶)! You work as an apprentice for Line Cooks and help them do basic prep work. In addition, you get to choose one staff member as your mentor, so you can closely observe their work and learn some extra skills. If your mentor leaves the restaurant, you will feel that this restaurant has not served them well and go apply to be a Talent Poacher 🍔(🐺) in your disappointment.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoBeholder">
    <value>You are the Sauce Chef 🥘(👁). Your signature mushroom velouté sauce is the pièce de résistance for many of the Executive Chef's beef and chicken entrées. That is why you are always working closely with the them to create his dishes and will always know who the Executive Chef is.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoApprenticeSeer">
    <value>You are the Sous Chef 🥐(🙇) . Being the second-in-command in the kitchen, you follow the Executive Chef's 🥖(👳) orders and train other chefs to plate dishes to a Michelin 3-star standard. You also have to check all the equipment in the kitchen every day, so you do not actually spend much time talking to the Executive Chef. If the Executive Chef resigns or is assigned another role, you will be promoted as the new Executive Chef 🥖(👳).</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoCultist">
    <value>You are a Vegan Chef 🥑(👤). You were recently hired only because a food critic wrote a review last year about how this professional restaurant lacks options for vegan customers. Having worked in the kitchen for some time, you are also disappointed how little awareness the staff has about the ethical and environmental importance of veganism. You aim to change that by sharing your vegan lunchbox with one staff every day and inspiring them to embrace veganism. You win if everyone in the restaurant turns vegan!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoCultistHunter">
	<value>You are the Butcher Chef 🍖(💂). Ever since a new Vegan Chef 🥑(👤) was hired last year to create dishes to please the younger generation, you've suspect that veganism is spreading in the kitchen and your job is at risk. Every day, you can check any staff's lunchbox to see if they eat meat or not. If you find a vegan lunchbox, you will sneak in a piece of meat and make them quit their job in rage. If a Vegan wants you to try their lunchbox, you would sneak some meat into it and return the lunchbox to them!</value>  
  </string>
  <string key="LynchTime">
<!-- 0 - number of seconds -->
    <value>
      Time for the restaurant staff to vote on who they think the spy chef(s) are... 
      Everyone now has {0} seconds to vote!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DayTime">
<!-- 0 - number of seconds -->
    <value>It's evening time! All the staff gathered in the common room to discuss who the spies may be. You have {0} seconds to discuss.</value>
    <value>Everyone is tired after a hard day of work! All the staff gathered in the common room to discuss who the spies may be. You have {0} seconds to discuss.</value>
    <value>Business was not so busy today and everyone was already seated in the common room. Let's share our observations! You have {0} seconds to discuss.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NightTime">
<!-- 0 - number of seconds -->
    <value>~Whoosh~ Another day of work begins! Everyone heads to their stations and starts preparing their mise en place or doing their assigned tasks. To those with decisions: you have {0} seconds to decide!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="LynchKill">
<!-- 0 - player name -->
<!-- 1 - player role -->
    <value>The votes are in. {0} has been fired! {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="LynchTie">
    <value>The votes are in and the Chefs were unable to agree on who to fire. Everyone returns to their home, tired after a busy day...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NoLynchVotes">
    <value>Was everyone too busy eating cake? Why didn't anyone vote? No one is fired today then...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DetectiveEaten">
<!-- 0 - victim name -->
    <value>It is evening time. Everyone gathers at the common room and see that the office is oddly dark inside. Walking towards the dark corner, they found that the Accountant 🕰(🕵️) has resigned from their job and took their desk lamp with them! The idle computer screen shows that {0} - the Accountant, has taken their last paycheck and left the restaurant.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardianEaten">
<!-- 0 - victim name -->
    <value>In the kitchen, safety comes first for everyone...  except the Safety Supervisor {0} ⚠️(👼) themself. The staff gather in the common room to find a resignation letter pinned to the noticeboard. It seems {0} has resigned due to a "hand injury"... 🍔(🐺) Nothing suspicious there.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GunnerEaten">
<!-- 0 - victim name -->
    <value>Everyone was shocked to learn that the Senior Chef 🧀(🔫) {0} has resigned and left behind their tailor-made Chef's uniform in the common room. The Chef has cherished this uniform for the last thirty years of their loyal work. Perhaps they have decided to leave behind the past and continue their career across the street...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SeerEaten">
<!-- 0 - victim name -->
    <value>The staff enter the common room and are embraced with a wall of words over the noticeboard. The Executive Chef 🥖(👳) {0} has written a lengthy paragraph expressing their thanks to all the Chefs they have worked with. Apparently, a better life awaits them across the street and they have resigned from the restaurant.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DrunkEaten">
<!-- 0 - victim name -->
    <value>The staff walk into the common room and find a couple of empty 1942 Chardonnay bottles opened. Seems the Sommelier 🍷(🍻) {0} has resigned and the spies have used their keys to take some sips from these precious bottles of white wine... I wonder how much wine they did drink?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="FoolEaten">
<!-- 0 - victim name -->
	<value>The Chief of Operations 🍞(🃏) {0} has resigned today. They left behind a resignation letter and their thick notebook, which contained receipts, printed emails sent by clients... as well as poorly-drafted menus that look like what an apprentice chef would plan. Maybe they drank too much wine and thought they were actually the Executive Chef 🥖(👳)!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DefaultEaten">
<!-- 0 - victim name -->
<!-- 1 - victim role -->
    <value>The staff walk into the common room, disappointed to learn that {0} has resigned today. It is so worrying to see people "quitting" (*cough* getting poached by the competitor *cough*) everyday. {1} </value>
    <value>{0} has left the restaurant with immediate effect. Seems they received a good job offer at the competitor's restaurant and resigned! {1} </value>
    <value>No one is celebrating today as everyone learnt that {0}, one of the most beloved staff has left the restaurant... perhaps to find better opportunities across the street! {1} </value>
    <value>Oh no! {0} has resigned today and left their station in a mess. Someone saw them leave in a hurry so that they can start working across the street at the competitor's restaurant ASAP... {1} </value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterKilledCultist">
<!-- 0 - victim name -->
    <value>There is an open lunchbox on one of the tables, inside you can see a bed of kale leaves, chickpeas and a half-eaten piece of fish... It is {0}'s vegan lunchbox 🥑(👤)! They must have left the restaurant in rage after finding meat in their lunchbox...</value>
    <value>There is an open lunchbox on one of the tables, inside you can see some half-eaten soba noodles, fresh green edamame... and some thinly-sliced salmon disguised as carrots? It is {0}'s vegan lunchbox 🥑(👤)! They must have left the restaurant in rage after being served meat in their lunchbox...</value>
    <value>There is an open lunchbox on one of the tables, inside you can see a some cold roasted potatoes, a half-eaten seared portabello and some crackers with cheese on top... It is {0}'s vegan lunchbox 🥑(👤)! That cheese doesn't smell like the vegan substitute though, they must have left the restaurant in rage after being served real cheese in their lunchbox...</value>
    <value>There is an open lunchbox on one of the tables. The lunchbox is empty but you can spot in the floor below a spilled glass of what seems to be a strawberry milkshake... It is {0}'s vegan lunch 🥑(👤)! They must have left the restaurant in rage after being served strawberry juice with milk...</value>
    <value>There is an open lunchbox on one of the tables, inside you can see some cooked curry lentils, fresh baby spinach and some falafel but with pork shreddings on top... It is {0}'s vegan lunchbox 🥑(👤)! They must have left the restaurant in rage after being served meat in their lunchbox...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NoAttack">
    <value>The staff gather in the common room. To everyone's surprise, it seems that everyone is here! No one has resigned today.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CursedBitten">
    <value>While taking out the trash of the night shift, you were approached by a chef with a big smile on their face. Turns out they are one of the spies from the competitor. Eager to get a better job, you offered to help them on their mission and became a Talent Poacher 🍔(🐺) yourself! Time to put your spying skills to the test...</value>
  </string>
  <string deprecated="true" key="WolfTeam">
<!-- 0 - teammate names -->
    <value>The other Talent Poachers 🍔(🐺) are: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CursedBittenToWolves">
<!-- 0 - victim name -->
    <value>You followed {0} into the back-alley to persuade them to join the competitor's restaurant. You were surprised to find that they were taking out the trash of the night shift as the Kitchen Porter 💩(😾). They willingly agreed to join the competitor and even offered to become a Talent Poacher with you to help your mission!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolvesEatYou">
    <value>A mysterious chef invited you to the back-alley and gave you an attractive job offer in the competitor's restaurant across the street! Wasting no time, you submitted your resignation and left the restaurant.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolvesEatDrunk">
<!-- 0 - victim name -->
    <value>Lucky for you, you were able to recruit {0} the Sommelier 🍷(🍻)  to join the competitor's restaurant! Taking their keys to the wine cellar, you and your spymates spent the rest of the day taking sips from the valuable wine collection and feel a little bit tipsy now... Why don't you all take a day off tomorrow?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardWolf">
    <value>You caught a dubious chef trying to cut a baguette using a fish knife and dragged them to the back-alley to give them a talking to. Turns out they were one of the Talent Poachers 🍔(🐺) and they offered you an attractive job offer as the Senior Safety Supervisor at the competitor's restaurant! Time to pack your bags and quit your job!</value>
    <value>You caught an odd chef that doesn't know how to use the mandolin and dragged them to the back-alley to give them a talking to. Turns out they were one of the Talent Poachers 🍔(🐺) and they offered you an attractive job offer as the Senior Safety Supervisor at the competitor's restaurant! Time to pack your bags and quit your job!</value>
    <value>You caught a naughty chef who was using the dirty fish knife to cut some lemons for the aperitifs. You dragged them to the back-alley to give them a talking to. Turns out they were one of the Talent Poachers 🍔(🐺) and they offered you an attractive job offer as the Senior Safety Supervisor at the competitor's restaurant! Time to pack your bags and quit your job!</value>
    <value>You caught a mischievous chef trying to lick some frosting off of the champagne cake that the pastry chef made for tonight's event. You dragged them to the back-alley to give them a talking to. Turns out they were one of the Talent Poachers 🍔(🐺) and they offered you an attractive job offer as the Senior Safety Supervisor at the competitor's restaurant! Time to pack your bags and quit your job!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardSaved">
<!-- 0 - saved player name -->
    <value>You see that {0} was cutting onions the wrong way and took them into the back-alley to lecture them. On the way, you saw a disappointed Chef holding a flyer returning to their station. Seems you have just stopped a Talent Poacher 🍔(🐺) from recruiting {0} to the competitor's restaurant!</value>
    <value>You see that {0} was about to pour chicken stock into a pan of hot oil and took them into the back-alley to lecture them. On the way, you saw a disappointed Chef holding a flyer returning to their station. Seems you have just stopped a Talent Poacher 🍔(🐺) from recruiting {0} to the competitor's restaurant!</value>
    <value>You see that {0} left the crème fraîche on the counter uncovered and took them into the back-alley to lecture them. On the way, you saw a disappointed Chef holding a flyer returning to their station. Seems you have just stopped a Talent Poacher 🍔(🐺) from recruiting {0} to the competitor's restaurant!</value>
    <value>You smelled burning food from {0}'s station and saw that they have left their cheesecake in the oven baking for more than 3 hours. You took them into the back-alley to lecture them. On the way, you saw a disappointed Chef holding a flyer returning to their station. Seems you have just stopped a Talent Poacher 🍔(🐺) from recruiting {0} to the competitor's restaurant!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardNoAttack">
<!-- 0 - player name -->
    <value>You supervised {0} for the entire day and even tasted the lavender eclairs that they prepared. Nothing dangerous happened and you are very satisfied with their safety performance.</value>
    <value>You supervised {0} for the entire day and even tasted the squid ink capellini that they prepared. Nothing dangerous happened and you are very satisfied with their safety performance.</value>
    <value>You supervised {0} for the entire day and even tasted the dragon fruit pico de gallo that they prepared. Nothing dangerous happened and you are very satisfied with their safety performance.</value>
    <value>You supervised {0} for the entire day and even tasted the Basque cheesecake that they prepared. Nothing dangerous happened and you are very satisfied with their safety performance.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardEmptyHouse">
<!-- 0 - player name -->
    <value>You tried to supervise {0} today but learnt that they weren't at their station!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardSavedYou">
    <value>You were dragged into the back-alley by the Safety Supervisor ⚠️(👼), who gave you a long lecture. As you returned to your station, the supervisor told you that they have saved you from grave danger. You feel glad that you could work another day, safe in this prestigious kitchen.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotEaten">
<!-- 0 - player name -->
    <value>Even the talkative Server 🍒(💋) {0} resigned from the restaurant today! Apparently, job offers from a certain restaurant are more valuable than the friendships that the Server has built up with everyone they have talked to in this kitchen.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotNotHome">
<!-- 0 - player name -->
    <value>Today you were planning to recruit {0} to the competitor's restaurant, but they were not seen at their station! Where could they be...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotFuckWolf">
<!-- 0 - player name -->
    <value>You tried to invite {0} for a bit of chit-chat but you caught them leaving their stations into the back-alley. Following them there, you overhear that the competitor's restaurant is hiring Servers for twice the pay you are currently getting! Well, time to quit your job and get across the street!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotFuckedWolfPublic">
<!-- 0 - player name -->
    <value>{0} went to have some chit-chat with the Talent Poacher 🍔(🐺) today! They left their Server 🍒(💋) uniform on the floor in the common room because they excitedly resigned to get a better job at the competitor's restaurant. Who's going to deliver the dishes now?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotFuckedVictimPublic">
<!-- 0 - harlot name -->
<!-- 1 - victim name -->
    <value>{0} went to have some chit-chat with {1} in the back-alley but found that {1} was talking to a Talent Poacher 🍔(🐺). They were both offered excellent positions in the competitor's restaurant and resigned immediately! Who's going to deliver the dishes now?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotVisitNonWolf">
<!-- 0 - target name -->
    <value>You had a very enjoyable chit-chat with {0} in the back-alley and returned to your work.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotVisitYou">
    <value>It was a busy day but you were relieved when one of the staff summoned you to the back-alley for a short break and a bit of chit-chat. You saw them change into a set of clean Server's 🍒(💋) uniform as you both returned to the kitchen afterwards.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DetectiveCaught">
<!-- 0 - detective name -->
    <value>You look into the dark office and faintly see the figure of {0} working at the desk in the corner. Apparently, {0} is the Accountant 🕰(🕵️) who is able to check your time records and know if you have been doing your "recruiting" business in the back-alley!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DetectiveSnoop">
<!-- 0 - target name -->
<!-- 1 - target role -->
    <value>You reviewed the time records and performance appraisal of {0} and issued their paycheck for the day. Based on your experience, you are confident that they are {1}.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotShot">
<!-- 0 - gunner's name -->
<!-- 1 - Harlot's name -->
    <value>Seems the Senior Chef 🧀(🔫) {0} was very dissatisfied with the Server 🍒(💋) {1} as they are always missing from the kitchen, leaving the food to cool and dry out. The Senior Chef has made an accusation and {1} has been fired from their restaurant!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DefaultShot">
<!-- 0 - Gunner's name -->
<!-- 1 - target name -->
<!-- 2 - Target's revealed name ( Target was a role) -->
    <value>Suddenly, the door of the restaurant owner's room opens. Everyone sees the owner walk out with {0} 🧀(🔫) behind them, looking like they just made an accusation. The owner announced that {1} will be immediately fired! {2}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolfWins">
    <value>With only a Talent Poacher 🍔(🐺) and one staff left, the other staff easily agreed to take the job offered at the competitor's restaurant. The spies have won!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolvesWin">
    <value>The spies from the competitor's restaurant now represent more than half the staff in the restaurant. They have voted out the owner and successfully taken over the restaurant!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="VillageWins">
    <value>~ Whoosh ~ From the next day onwards, no more of your staff left the restaurant and you maintained your 3 Michelin stars. You have succeeded in saving the restaurant!</value>
    <value>~ Whoosh ~ On the next day, you hear the news that the competitor's restaurant has been closed down. Seems the owner has invested too much money in hiring spies to sabotage your restaurant that they went bankrupt. Anyways, you have succeeded in saving the restaurant!</value>
    <value>~ Whoosh ~ The restaurant continues to run normally for the next 3 months. All the spies have been kicked out and you have saved the restaurant!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="TannerWins">
    <value>The restaurant fired the Dishwasher 🧽(👺)! Regardless of what happens next to the restaurant and the competitor's, the Dishwasher is the biggest winner here as they receive a severance pay which is worth 6 months of their pay! Yay!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RemainingPlayersEnd">
    <value>Remaining Chefs and staff, job positions, and teams:</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultistVotedConvert">
<!-- 0 - Voter's name -->
<!-- 1 - target name -->
    <value>{0} votes to enthuse {1} about the magic of lentil-soaking</value>
    <value>{0} wants to share their coconut milk with {1}</value>
    <value>{0} has prepared a whole fruit basket to persuade {1} to become a vegan</value>
    <value>{0} made tofu by hand just to invite {1} to try vegan foods</value>
    <value>{0} pulsed their nuts to make cashew milk for {1} to try</value>
    <value>{0} wants to beat {1}'s carnivorous heart with their hearty beetroot salad</value>
    <value>{0} wants share their spice mix recipe with {1} so that they could cook delicious vegan treats</value>
    <value>{0} votes to share their vegan lunchbox with {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultConvertCultHunter">
<!-- 0 - Yougest Cultist (killed)'s name' -->
<!-- 1 - CultHunter's name -->
    <value>Today, it was {0}'s turn to inspire one of the staff to become a vegan. However, they chose {1} out of everyone, who was the Butcher Chef 🍖(💂)! Seems like the Butcher rejected their lunchbox offer and even mixed in a bit of meat into {0}'s lunchbox...Finding they have been given meat for lunch, {0} resigned and left in a great rage.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultHunterKilledCultVisit">
<!-- 0 - Youngest Cultist's name -->
<!-- 1 - Number of cultists left -->
    <value>During lunchtime, {0}'s tried to impress you with their vegetable tempura bento 🥑(👤), but you refused them and even snuck in a piece of meat into their lunchbox while they were distracted. Hopefully they will get so angry that they resign from the restaurant! Muahaha! There are {1} Vegan Chefs left.</value>
    <value>During lunchtime, {0}'s tried to impress you with their falafel burger 🥑(👤), but you refused them and even snuck in a piece of meat into their lunchbox while they were distracted. Hopefully they will get so angry that they resign from the restaurant! Muahaha! There are {1} Vegans left.</value>
    <value>During lunchtime, {0}'s tried to impress you with their pasta primavera 🥑(👤), but you refused them and even snuck in a piece of meat into their lunchbox while they were distracted. Hopefully they will get so angry that they resign from the restaurant! Muahaha! There are {1} Vegans left.</value>
    <value>During lunchtime, {0}'s tried to impress you with their curry broccoli 🥑(👤), but you refused them and even snuck in a piece of meat into their lunchbox while they were distracted. Hopefully they will get so angry that they resign from the restaurant! Muahaha! There are {1} Vegans left.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultConvertYou">
    <value>You applied to become a Vegan Chef 🥑(👤) today after you tasted a delicious vegan lunchbox! You will continue to spread veganism in this kitchen by choosing to share your lunchbox with one person per day. You win if everyone in the restaurant turns vegan!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultTeam">
<!-- 0 - Number of cultists -->
    <value>The other Vegan Chefs 🥑(👤) are: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultJoin">
<!-- 0 - new cultist's name -->
    <value>{0} was very inspired and decided to apply to become a Vegan Chef!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultVisitEmpty">
<!-- 0 - Newest cultist's name -->
<!-- 1 - target name -->
    <value>{0} tried to share their delicious vegan lunchbox with {1}, but they were nowhere to be found! Were they in the back-alley?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultWins">
    <value>Roasted garbanzo carrot soup, sesame broccolini and tofu salad, Artiste miso risotto.... the restaurant's menu has turned vegan 🥑(👤) too after everyone in the kitchen embraced veganism! Who cares about competitors taking away our 3 Michelin stars? All Hail Kale!</value>
    <value>Mongolian Seitan salad, Colorado Seitan burgers, lentil Seitan Salisburg steak... the restaurant's menu has turned vegan 🥑(👤) too after everyone in the kitchen embraced Seitan-ism! Who cares about competitors taking away our 3 Michelin stars? All Hail Seitan!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterVisitDead">
<!-- 0 - target name -->
    <value>You tried to check {0}'s lunchbox but heard that they didn't have one... because they already resigned!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterFindCultist">
<!-- 0 - target name -->
    <value>You peek into {0}'s lunchbox to find a horrible bed of iceberg lettuce! Where's the meat🥑(👤)? You snuck in a little piece of meat and pray that the {0} will be grateful for what you did.</value>
    <value>You peek into {0}'s lunchbox to find a ginormous chunk of tofu! Where's the meat 🥑(👤)? You snuck in a little piece of meat and pray that the {0} will be grateful for what you did.</value>
    <value>You peek into {0}'s lunchbox to find a weird-looking "vegan egg"! Where's the meat 🥑(👤)? You snuck in a little piece of meat and pray that the {0} will be grateful for what you did.</value>
    <value>You peek into {0}'s lunchbox to find some dubious cream that smells of crushed nuts... cashews to be exact! Where's the meat 🥑(👤)? You snuck in a little piece of meat and pray that the {0} will be grateful for what you did.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterFailedToFind">
<!-- 0 - target name -->
    <value>You checked {0}'s lunchbox and you are pleased to find that they have ordered chicken afritada for lunch. Certainly, {0} is not one of those pesky Vegan Chefs 🥑(👤)!</value>
    <value>You checked {0}'s lunchbox and you are pleased to find that they have ordered kung pao pork for lunch. Certainly, {0} is not one of those pesky Vegan Chefs 🥑(👤)!</value>
    <value>You checked {0}'s lunchbox and you are pleased to find that they have ordered filet mignon for lunch. Certainly, {0} is not one of those pesky Vegan Chefs 🥑(👤)!</value>
    <value>You checked {0}'s lunchbox and you are pleased to find that they have ordered a Wagyu beef burger for lunch. Certainly, {0} is not one of those pesky Vegan Chefs 🥑(👤)!</value>
    <value>You checked {0}'s lunchbox and you are pleased to find that they have ordered shrimp scampi for lunch. Certainly, {0} is not one of those pesky Vegan Chefs 🥑(👤)!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WildChildToWolves">
<!-- 0 - Werechild's name -->
    <value>{0}'s mentor just left the restaurant! Feeling like an unvalued Commis 🧅(👶) in the kitchen, {0} walked over to the competitor's restaurant and applied to be a Talent Poacher just like you!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WildChildTransform">
<!-- 0 - role's name -->
<!-- 0 - teammates' names -->
<!-- Villager, Drunk, Harlot, Seer, Traitor, GuardianAngel, Detective, Wolf, Cursed, Gunner, Tanner, Fool, WildChild, Beholder, ApprenticeSeer, Cultist, CultistHunter-->
<!-- Do NOT change the emoji's, even if you are translating werewolf in a non-standard mode! -->
    <value>You cannot believe that your mentor, {0} has left the restaurant! Feeling disappointed, you walk across the street to the competitor's restaurant and applied to be their Talent Poacher 🍔(🐺), hoping that you can learn from a few of the chefs that you help recruit through your new job. The other Talent Poachers are: {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Villager">
    <value>a Line Cook 🧑‍🍳(👱)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Drunk">
    <value>the Sommelier 🍷(🍻)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Harlot">
    <value>the Server 🍒(💋)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Seer">
    <value>the Executive Chef 🥖(👳)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Traitor">
    <value>the Valet Attendant 🔑(🖕)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardianAngel">
    <value>the Safety Supervisor ⚠️(👼)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Detective">
    <value>the Accountant 🕰(🕵️)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Wolf">
    <value>a Talent Poacher 🍔(🐺)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Cursed">
    <value>the Kitchen Porter 💩(😾)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Gunner">
    <value>the Senior Chef 🧀(🔫)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Tanner">
    <value>the Dishwasher 🧽(👺)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Fool">
    <value>the Chief of Operations 🍞(🃏)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WildChild">
    <value>the Commis Chef 🧅(👶)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Beholder">
    <value>the Sauce Chef 🥘(👁)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ApprenticeSeer">
    <value>the Sous Chef 🥐(🙇)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Cultist">
    <value>a Vegan Chef 🥑(👤)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultistHunter">
<!-- These are for the player list -->
    <value>the Butcher Chef 🍖(💂)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RanAway">
    <value>Fled the restaurant</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Dead">
    <value>🏃 Left the restaurant</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Alive">
    <value>😋 Working</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayersAlive">
    <value>Staff in the Restaurant</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Mason">
    <value>a Sashimi Chef 🍣(👷)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoMason">
    <value>You are a Sashimi Chef 🍣(👷). Coming from the Aomori prefecture of Japan, you help to prepare fresh sashimi every day for the Asian lunch specials. You always know if there is another Sashimi Chef(s) in the kitchen because you are the only ones who prefer to speak in Japanese! You are just like any Line Cook, working diligently at your station and slicing, slicing slicing...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MasonEaten">
<!-- 0 - dead man's name -->
    <value>The staff gather at the common room and find an interesting letter. It is written in Japanese and wrapped in a very neat envelope. Seems the Sashimi Chef 🍣(👷) {0} has resigned from their position!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MasonTeam">
    <value> The Sashimi Chefs are: {0}. So desu ne!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultTargetDead">
<!-- 0 - Youngest cultists name -->
    <value>You tried to share your delicious vegan lunchbox with {0}, but you learnt that they had left the restaurant.....</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardBlockedWolf">
<!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>The Talent Poachers were about to invite {0} into the back-alley when they saw the Safety Supervisor ⚠️(👼) get to {0} first. Since it's likely that the Safety Supervisor will give {0} a long lecture, everyone decided to return to their stations and continue "working".</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultUnableToConvert">
<!-- 0 - newest  -->
<!-- 1 - target's name -->
    <value>{0} tried to share their delicious vegan lunchbox with {1}, but they didn't like it! Maybe you can try to inspire them again on another day~</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NameExists">
<!-- 0 - target's name -->
<!-- 1 - name -->
    <value>@{1}, a player with the name {0} has already joined.  Please change your name to join.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotDiscoverCult">
<!-- 0 - target's name -->
<!-- new string May 13 2016-->
    <value>You took {0} into the back-alley for some lunchtime chit-chat, during which you learnt that they had something called "Seitan" for lunch? Isn't that what the Vegan Chefs 🥑(👤) love to eat?</value>
    <value>You took {0} into the back-alley for some lunchtime chit-chat, during which you learnt that they had something called "Aquafaba" for lunch? Isn't that what the Vegan Chefs 🥑(👤) love to eat?</value>
    <value>You took {0} into the back-alley for some lunchtime chit-chat, during which you learnt that they had something called "Sea grape" for lunch? Isn't that what the Vegan Chefs 🥑(👤) love to eat?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Was">
    <value>was</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GenericDeathNoReveal">
<!-- 0 - Dead's name -->
    <value>As everyone walks into the common room, they find the resignation letter of {0}. {0} has left the restaurant!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MasonConverted">
<!-- 0 - mason's name -->
<!-- new string May 16 2016-->
    <value>You realised that {0} has returned their Sashimi Chef uniform and got a new one... did they transfer to another position?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="FleeDisabled">
    <value>The security guard stopped you from fleeing from the restaurant while you are working!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="IsDead">
<!-- used when gunner shoots a player -->
<!-- MORE STRINGS May 16, 2016 -->
    <value>has been fired.</value>
  </string>
  <string deprecated="true" key="AdminAdded">
<!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>{0} added to admin list. Use /config to change group settings.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AlreadyInGame">
<!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>You are already employed in a restaurant! ({0})</value>
  </string>
  <string deprecated="true" key="MultipleGames">
    <value>Your group has managed to start multiple games... Killing extras.</value>
  </string>
  <string deprecated="true" key="GroupQueue">
<!-- 0 - target's name -->
<!-- 1 - target's name -->
<!-- 0 - target's name -->
<!-- 1 - target's name -->
    <value>Your group is currently in the queue. Position: {0} / {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string deprecated="true" key="MaintBreak">
<!-- 0 - target's name -->
<!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>Sorry, I'm about to start a short maintenance break, you can't start a game right now.\nWaiting on {0} games to end...\nGo to @greywolfdev for more information</value>
  </string>
  <string deprecated="true" key="MaxGames">
<!-- 0 - target's name -->
<!-- 1 - target's name -->
<!-- 0 - target's name -->
<!-- 1 - target's name -->
    <value>Sorry, max concurrent games has been reached ({0}). \nPosition in queue: {1} / {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string deprecated="true" key="SkipQueue">
<!-- 0 - target's name -->
<!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>{0} is a preferred group, and has skipped the queue!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NoGame">
    <value>There is no restaurant in operation. Open one using /startgame or start a chaos restaurant with /startchaos</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GroupAdminOnly">
    <value>Only a member of the Restaurant Discipline Council can authorize with this command.</value>
  </string>
  <string deprecated="true" key="ShuttingDown">
    <value>After this game, I am shutting down for maintenance.</value>
  </string>
  <string deprecated="true" key="ShuttingDownUpdate">
    <value>After this game, I am shutting down momentarily for an update (automated).</value>
  </string>
  <string deprecated="true" key="NullIdAdmin">
    <value>UserId was null.  Are you sure you sent this as a reply?</value>
  </string>
  <string deprecated="true" key="AlreadyAdmin">
<!-- 0 - target's name -->
<!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>{0} is already an admin!</value>
  </string>
  <string deprecated="true" key="NotAdmin">
<!-- 0 - target's name -->
<!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>{0} is not an admin!</value>
  </string>
  <string deprecated="true" key="AdminRemoved">
<!-- 0 - target's name -->
<!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>{0} removed from admin list.</value>
  </string>
  <string deprecated="true" key="LanguageSet">
<!-- 0 - language's name -->
<!-- 0 - language's name -->
    <value>Language set to {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NoSeer">
    <value>\nTurns out there is no Executive Chef running this kitchen! Who will use your sauces now...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="TimesUp">
<!-- new strings june 10 2016 -->
    <value>Time's up!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoCupid">
    <value>You are the Barista ☕️(🏹) . Your job is to operate the corner café of the restaurant. Each season, you receive only one shipment of the expensive Hacienda El Roble coffee beans from Colombia. These beans are so rare that only celebrity-class customers would order them. Even you are not allowed to take a sip without paying... However, the restaurant director allows you to brew two cups of this exotic coffee and give them to two of the staff for taste-testing, just for them to give you some feedback. The coffee is so exotic and interesting that these two staff will start researching the art of coffee brewing and work closely together, even leaving the restaurant together if any one decides to leave.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoDoppelganger">
    <value>You are a Management Trainee 🙇(🎭). You are still in culinary school and are working part-time in the restaurant to hone your skills. At the start, you can choose one of the staff whose job you will take up when they leave the restaurant, and you will study their job functions as your major area at school.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoHunter">
    <value>You are the Food Critic 🖋(🎯). You are renowned for writing in-depth reviews about how a restaurant works and prepare their dishes... you can do that because you always disguise yourself as a chef and sneak into kitchens. Now that you are in this kitchen, if you are fired or asked to leave by anyone, you will reveal yourself and either criticise them or publish your review (where you can name and shame one staff in the process). The person you "attacked" would soon be fired as well!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoSerialKiller">
    <value>You are the Vengeful Customer ☠️(🔪).  You once got a serious allergy while eating this restaurant's signature seafood dish, but when you were wriggling on the floor with hives spreading across your face, no staff helped you because everyone was busy singing "~Happy Birthday~" to their VIP guest... You came back to take revenge by disguising yourself as a chef and triggering allergic reactions for one staff per day. Surely they will learn to never leave a customer unattended again! MUAHAHAHA</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CupidChosen">
    <value>You were chosen to taste the rare Hacienda Le Roble coffee prepared by the Barista ☕️(🏹). You and {0} were fascinated by the deep layers of bitterness and the lingering taste of Colombian soil, so much so that you decided to study the art of coffee brewing together. \n\nYour dream is to be alone with {0} and turn this restaurant into your own café! If {0} leaves the restaurant for any reason, you will follow them and together chase your dreams of starting your own café.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterLynchedChoice">
    <value>You are fired from the restaurant! Now is the time you publish your restaurant review and in particular, name one of the staff that you dislike to most in the article. Who will you shame?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterNoChoiceLynched">
    <value>Before {0} left the restaurant, they published a review about their experiences here. Contrary to everyone's expectations, the review was fairly positive and no one was named for doing a bad job...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterSkipChoiceLynched">
    <value>Before {0} left the restaurant, they published a review about their experiences here. Contrary to everyone's expectations, the review was fairly positive and no one was named for doing a bad job...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterKilledFinalLynched">
<!-- 0 - hunter's name -->
<!-- 1 - target's name -->
<!-- 2 - target's role -->
    <value>Before {0} left the restaurant, they published a review about their experiences here. Renowned critics and wealthy customers now know that your restaurant's food and service is pretty good, but the performance of {1} was less than satisfactory. After reading the article, the restaurant owner also decided to fire {1} for doing a bad job! {2}</value>
    <value>Before {0} left the restaurant, they published a review about their experiences here. Renowned critics and wealthy customers now know that your restaurant's food and service is terrible, especially the bread pudding made by {1}. After reading the article, the restaurant owner also decided to fire {1} for doing a bad job! {2}</value>
    <value>Before {0} left the restaurant, they published a review about their experiences here. Tourists and Queen Elizabeth now know that your restaurant's food and service is pretty good, but the performance of {1} was less than satisfactory. After reading the article, the restaurant owner also decided to fire {1} for doing a bad job! {2}</value>
    <value>Before {0} left the restaurant, they published a review about their experiences here. Tourists and Queen Elizabeth now know that your restaurant's food and service is terrible, especially the bread pudding made by {1}. After reading the article, the restaurant owner also decided to fire {1} for doing a bad job! {2}</value>
    <value>Before {0} left the restaurant, they published a review about their experiences here. Kanye West and Nicki Minaj now know that your restaurant's food and service is pretty good, but the performance of {1} was less than satisfactory. After reading the article, the restaurant owner also decided to fire {1} for doing a bad job! {2}</value>
    <value>Before {0} left the restaurant, they published a review about their experiences here. Kanye West and Nicki Minaj now know that your restaurant's food and service is terrible, especially the bread pudding made by {1}. After reading the article, the restaurant owner also decided to fire {1} for doing a bad job! {2}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterShotChoice">
    <value>You are about to leave the restaurant! Now is the time you publish your restaurant review and in particular, name one of the staff that you dislike to most in the article. Who will you shame?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterNoChoiceShot">
<!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>Before {0} left the restaurant, they published a review about their experiences here. Contrary to everyone's expectations, the review was fairly positive and no one was named for doing a bad job...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterSkipChoiceShot">
<!-- 0 - hunter's name -->
    <value>Before {0} left the restaurant, they published a review about their experiences here. Contrary to everyone's expectations, the review was fairly positive and no one was named for doing a bad job...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterKilledFinalShot">
<!-- 0 - hunter -->
<!-- 1 - target's name -->
<!-- 2 - target's role -->
    <value>Before {0} left the restaurant, they published a review about their experiences here. Renowned critics and wealthy customers now know that your restaurant's food and service is pretty good, but the performance of {1} was less than satisfactory. After reading the article, the restaurant owner also decided to fire {1} for doing a bad job! {2}</value>
    <value>Before {0} left the restaurant, they published a review about their experiences here. Renowned critics and wealthy customers now know that your restaurant's food and service is terrible, especially the bread pudding made by {1}. After reading the article, the restaurant owner also decided to fire {1} for doing a bad job! {2}</value>
    <value>Before {0} left the restaurant, they published a review about their experiences here. Tourists and Queen Elizabeth now know that your restaurant's food and service is pretty good, but the performance of {1} was less than satisfactory. After reading the article, the restaurant owner also decided to fire {1} for doing a bad job! {2}</value>
    <value>Before {0} left the restaurant, they published a review about their experiences here. Tourists and Queen Elizabeth now know that your restaurant's food and service is terrible, especially the bread pudding made by {1}. After reading the article, the restaurant owner also decided to fire {1} for doing a bad job! {2}</value>
    <value>Before {0} left the restaurant, they published a review about their experiences here. Kanye West and Nicki Minaj now know that your restaurant's food and service is pretty good, but the performance of {1} was less than satisfactory. After reading the article, the restaurant owner also decided to fire {1} for doing a bad job! {2}</value>
    <value>Before {0} left the restaurant, they published a review about their experiences here. Kanye West and Nicki Minaj now know that your restaurant's food and service is terrible, especially the bread pudding made by {1}. After reading the article, the restaurant owner also decided to fire {1} for doing a bad job! {2}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterShotWolfMulti">
<!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>The Talent Poachers 🍔(🐺) tried to recruit the Food Critic 🖋(🎯) to work at the competitor's restaurant today. How silly! Don't they realise who they were talking to? Today the Food Critic was in a good mood so they decided to play along and "resign" from the restaurant to review the competitor's restaurant as well. Being a responsible person though, the Critic told the restaurant owner about {0} and they were fired immediately for being a spy!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterShotWolf">
<!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>The Talent Poachers 🍔(🐺) tried to recruit the Food Critic 🖋(🎯) to work at the competitor's restaurant today. How silly! Don't they realise who they were talking to? After the Food Critic received all the details about the job, they turned down the offer and immediately went to social media to shame the competitor's about such unethical business behaviour. It's an unlucky day for {0} the Talent Poachers, who left the restaurant afterwards because the competitor has dismissed them as a Talent Poacher.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SerialKillerKilledWolf">
    <value>The Talent Poachers 🍔(🐺) thought it would be another successful day as they tried to persuade one of the chefs to join the competitor's restaurant. However, soon after shaking hands with the "chef", {0}'s face puffed up and had trouble breathing. {0} the Talent Poacher had an allergic reaction ☠️(🔪) and was rushed to the hospital! Goodbye, {0}.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DefaultKilled">
<!-- 0 - target's name -->
<!-- 1 - target's role -->
    <value>{0} was just decorating a plate with some edible flowers when their nose started bleeding uncontrollably. They were soon rushed to the hospital due to a serious intrinsic allergy ☠️(🔪). How could this have happened? {1}</value>
    <value>{0} was just assembling a croquembouche when their hands started trembling uncontrollably. They were soon rushed to the hospital due to a serious intrinsic allergy ☠️(🔪). How could this have happened? {1}</value>
    <value>{0} was just cleaning some ladles when they fainted and fell head first into the sink. They were soon rushed to the hospital due to a serious intrinsic allergy ☠️(🔪). How could this have happened? {1}</value>
    <value>{0} was just toasting some croutons when they started to wheeze and feel difficulty breathing. They were soon rushed to the hospital due to a serious intrinsic allergy ☠️(🔪). How could this have happened? {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardBlockedKiller">
<!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>You spread some of your allergen powder on {0}'s station and watched from afar... how disappointed you were when you saw the Safety Supervisor ⚠️(👼) step in and clean their station for them! Better luck tomorrow...</value>
    <value>You spread some of your allergen powder on your latex gloves and was about to go shake {0}'s hand when you saw them being dragged into the back-alley by the Safety Supervisor ⚠️(👼)! Better luck tomorrow...</value>
    <value>You added some chlorine to {0}'s cup of water watched from afar... just as they were about to drink it, they were stopped by the Safety Supervisor ⚠️(👼) who asked them to only drink fluids in the common room! Better luck tomorrow...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultConvertHunter">
<!-- 0 - Youngest Cultist's name -->
<!-- 1 - target's name -->
    <value>The Vegan Chef 🥑(👤) {0} tried to inspire {1} to try their vegan lunchbox, in which they did... but gave a lengthy, critical review about the food in it afterwards 🖋(🎯). {0} feels utterly ashamed that despite 5 years of culinary school, that they were unable to appreciate and critique food the way {1} could. {0} resigned immediately and decided to go back to culinary school...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultConvertSerialKiller">
<!-- 0 - Youngest Cultist's name -->
<!-- 1 - target's name -->
    <value>The Vegan Chef 🥑(👤) {0} tried to share their lunchbox with {1}. What a pleasant surprise when {1} not only accepted their offer, but gave {0} a tasty, 100% vegan nutty bar afterwards! The bar was actually a curse in disguise because after {0} ate it, hives started spreading across their face and they were rushed to hospital immediately ☠️(🔪)!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardKiller">
    <value>You caught one of the chefs dipping their hands in a cup of water and you thought you would give them a good talking in the back-alley. After they shook your hand as a gesture of "thanks", you soon feel dizzy and have trouble breathing. Now you are being rushed to the hospital ☠️(🔪)... regretting that you didn't pay attention to your own safety.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotFuckKiller">
<!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>You went into the back-alley with {0} and had a nice chit-chat. {0} even snuck a chocolate tartlet from the pastry rack which you delightfully chowed down. It was fine for another few hours until you felt stabbing pain in your belly... ow ow ow! You were rushed immediately to the hospital after the first-aider said you had serious food poisoning ☠️(🔪).</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotFuckKillerPublic">
    <value>Everyone was told that the Server 🍒(💋) {0} was rushed to the hospital after getting serious food poisoning. Maybe they ate food made by an "untrained chef" ☠️(🔪)...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGToMason">
<!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>The Management Trainee 🙇(🎭) {0} has completed their education and was assigned to be a Sashimi Chef just like you!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGTransformToMason">
<!-- 0 - dead mason's name -->
<!-- 1 - mason colleagues' names -->
    <value>Because {0} has left the restaurant, you were assigned to replace them as the new full-time Sashimi Chef 🍣(👷), working next to {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGToCult">
<!-- 0 - new cultist's name -->
    <value>The Management Trainee 🙇(🎭) {0} has completed their education and was assigned to be a Vegan Chef just like you!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGTransformToCult">
<!-- 0 - role's name -->
<!-- 1 - teammates' names -->
    <value>Because {0} has left the restaurant, you were assigned to replace them as the new full-time Vegan Chef 🥑(👤), working next to {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGToWolf">
<!-- 0 - DG's name -->
    <value>The Management Trainee 🙇(🎭) {0} has completed their education, but was recruited by the competitor's restaurant instead and assigned to be a Talent Poacher just like you!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGTransformToWolf">
<!-- 0 - target's name -->
<!-- 1 - teammates' names -->
    <value>Because {0} has left the restaurant, you were assigned to replace them. On the way to work, one of the staff from the competitor's restaurant came to tell you that {0} was actually a Talent Poacher 🍔(🐺), working next to {1}. You are working for the competitor now!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SerialKillerWins">
    <value>The Vengeful Customer ☠️(🔪), who was left unattended when they suffered a food allergy here a few years back, is the only one left standing in the kitchen. They have successfully taken revenge on the restaurant!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskKill">
    <value>Who do you want to send to the hospital today by triggering an allergic reaction on them?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="LoverDied">
<!-- 0 - dead's name -->
<!-- 1 - lover's name -->
<!-- 2 - roles -->
    <value>Following {0}, {1} decided to resign as well. They were both entranced by the deep flavours of the Hacienda Le Roble coffee that the Barista ☕️(🏹) let them taste, so much so that they would continue to research the wonders of coffee and open a café together. {2}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskDoppelganger">
    <value>Which staff's job will you take up when they leave the restaurant?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskCupid1">
    <value>The first cup of Hacienda Le Roble coffee is ready! Who should taste this cup?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskCupid2">
    <value>The second cup of Hacienda Le Roble coffee is ready! Who should taste this cup?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Hunter">
    <value>the Food Critic 🖋(🎯)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Cupid">
    <value>the Barista ☕️(🏹)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SerialKiller">
    <value>the Vengeful Customer ☠️(🔪)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Doppelgänger">
    <value>the Management Trainee 🙇(🎭)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NewWCRoleModel">
<!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>Because the Commis Chef 🧅(👶) has left the restaurant, you were assigned to replace them as the new full-time Commis Chef... which means you are still going to have a mentor (yippee...). Your mentor is {0} and you will join the competitor's restaurant as a Talent Poacher 🍔(🐺) in frustration if they ever leave the restaurant.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="LoversWin">
    <value>Could this be? The lucky chefs who had the chance to taste the two cups of Hacienda La Roble coffee ☕️(🏹) found themselves as the only one left standing in this elegantly decorated Michelin 3-star restaurant. Even the Barista who served them the coffee has left. Finally, they can sell the restaurant and open their own café to spread their love of coffee. The coffee-lovers have won!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterKilledVisiter">
<!-- 0 - target's name -->
<!-- 1 - role -->
    <value>The staff walk into the common room and find the resignation letter of {0}. It is a detailed and emotional letter where {0} explained how humiliated they felt when they were criticised by their fellow chef for their "terrible work". Could it be that one of the staff is actually a Food Critic 🖋(🎯) in disguise? {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultAttempt">
    <value>Someone invited you to try their vegan lunchbox today 🥑(👤), but you didn't feel like trying Seitan, so you turned them down.</value>
    <value>Someone invited you to try their vegan lunchbox today 🥑(👤), but you didn't feel like trying lingonberry jam, so you turned them down.</value>
    <value>Someone invited you to try their vegan lunchbox today 🥑(👤), but you didn't feel like trying chickpea pâté, so you turned them down.</value>
    <value>Someone invited you to try their vegan lunchbox today 🥑(👤), but you didn't feel like trying aquafaba, so you turned them down.</value>
    <value>Someone invited you to try their vegan lunchbox today 🥑(👤), but you didn't feel like trying silken tofu, so you turned them down.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AlreadyOnWaitList">
<!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>You are already on the wait list for {0}.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AddedToWaitList">
<!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>You have been added to the wait list for {0}. I will send an email to you when a new restaurant opens.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NotifyNewGame">
<!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>A new restaurant opened in {0}.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SerialKillerWinsOverpower">
<!-- 0 - SK's name -->
<!-- 1 - target's name -->
    <value>On the next day, the restaurant opens with only two staff remaining. {0} gives {1} an evil smile then pours a pot of boiling water over them, letting them burn and wriggle on the ground without any help... After all these years, feeling humiliated on that day when the restaurant neglected them while they wriggled on the floor with an allergic reaction, the Vengeful Customer ☠️(🔪) has finally taken their revenge!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NoWinner">
    <value>~ Whoosh ~ The next day, the whole restaurant is empty... seems everyone has left the restaurant. No one wins!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SKHunterEnd">
<!-- 0 - SK's name -->
<!-- 1 - Hunter's name -->
    <value>On the next day, the restaurant opens with only two staff remaining. {0} gives {1} an evil smile and was about to pour a pot of boiling water over them, when {1} pulled out their phone and started a livestream on their Food Critic 🖋(🎯) channel, revealing {0} as the maniacal Vengeful Customer ☠️(🔪) to everyone. {1} was badly burnt by the water while {0} was soon arrested by the police... The restaurant closes because everyone has left, no one wins!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleModelChosen">
<!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>You didn't choose in time, so one of the managers have chosen for you: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Won">
    <value>Won</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Lost">
    <value>Lost</value>
  </string>
  <string key="IdleCount">
<!-- 0 - player's name -->
<!-- 1 - idle count -->
<!--New strings 7th of July-->
<!--If you are translating werewolf in a non-standard mode (eg. Mafia, Pokémon and similar) please put the role and the emoji in front of the string.
  For example in Mafia, AboutMason would be:
  Caporegime 👷\nYou are a caporegime blah blah
  -->
<!-- 0 - player's name -->
<!-- 1 - idle count -->
<!--New strings 7th of July-->
<!--If you are translating werewolf in a non-standard mode (eg. Mafia, Pokémon and similar) please put the role and the emoji in front of the string.
  For example in Mafia, AboutMason would be:
  Caporegime 👷\nYou are a caporegime blah blah
  -->
    <value>{0} has been fired for not voting {1} times in the past 24 hours.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutVG">
    <value>You are the Line Cook. Your job is only to try to survive in the kitchen.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutSeer">
    <value>You are the Executive Chef 🥖(👳). To ensure your staff are performing at the highest standards, you can supervise any staff of your choice every day in secret (e.g. tasting the dishes they make), after which you will also learn their role.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutWw">
    <value>You are the Talent Poacher, working for the competitor's restaurant. You will act like a normal chef and infiltrate the restaurant. Each day, you can invite a staff into the back-alley and persuade them to join the competitor's restaurant. \nIf you invite the low-paid Kitchen Porter, they will agree and even become a Talent Poacher like you. \nIf you invite the Sommelier, you will take their keys afterwards to access the wine cellar and get yourselves drunk and unable to come to work the next day.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutHarlot">
    <value>You are the Server. You can invite one person to have some chit-chat with every day at the back-alley. If you invited one of the Talent Poachers, you will be easily talked into resigning and join the competitor's restaurant instead. If you visited someone who was being invited by the Talent Poachers, you will be curious and resign to join the competitor as well. If the Talent Poachers try to invite you while you were having chit-chat with someone else, they won't find you.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutDrunk">
    <value>You are the Sommelier who is in charge of the wine service. If you are recruited by the talent poachers, they would take your keys and enter the wine cellar, taking sips from the wine stocked there and getting so drunk that they would have to take a day off on the next day.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutCursed">
    <value>You are the Kitchen Porter, responsible for cleaning the kitchen floors and toilets. With a low-pay and a poor job, when the Talent Poacher invites you to join the competitor's restaurant, not only would you agree to that excitedly, you would even volunteer to become a Talent Poacher yourself.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutTraitor">
    <value>You are the Valet Attendant. You stand outside the restaurant and help customers to park their cars. Because you are the only one who is physically outside the restaurant, when all Talent Poachers are removed from the restaurant, the competitor will approach you and give you the chance to become a Talent Poacher for them, to which you would agree to due to the high pay they offer!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutGA">
    <value>You are the Safety Supervisor ⚠️(👼). You enforce kitchen safety rules to prevent deadly accidents. Each day, you can supervise one of the Chefs from afar. If you see them about to do something dangerous, you would drag them out to the back-alley and give them a talking. Be careful though - if you supervised a spy or dangerous chef, you could be the one getting into danger!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutDetective">
    <value>You are the Accountant. At the end of each working day, you sit in the desk at the corner of the office to issue the paychecks for the staff. You can choose to check the time records and performance appraisal of any staff to make sure they are paid fairly - and determine their job as well. There is a 40% chance that the Talent Poachers spot you hunching over your corner desk.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutGunner">
    <value>You are the Senior Chef 🧀(🔫). Every day, you can advise the restaurant's owner about a possible spy chef. By the end of the day, the owner will publicly fire the one you accused with you standing next to them, letting everyone know that you were responsible. You only get a maximum of 2 accusations!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutTanner">
    <value>You are the Dishwasher. You win if you get voted by everyone to fire you because you will get a severance pay that is worth 6 times your monthly pay.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutFool">
    <value>You are the Chief of Operations. You work closely with the different departments and every day you need to supervise some staff to ensure they are doing their job... but that doesn't make you the Executive Chef, because you just are not experienced enough to tell chefs apart from each other. You will be able to "guess" a random job position of a staff you supervise every day.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutCult">
    <value>You are a Vegan Chef. Your goal is to convert every staff in the restaurant to become a vegan like you. You win when everyone becomes vegan.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutCH">
    <value>You are the Butcher Chef. You are worried about the spreading of veganism in the kitchen because your job will be at risk. Every day, you can check someone's lunchbox to see if they are vegan. If you find a vegan lunchbox, you will sneak in a piece of meat. They will be so angry when they find out that their lunch has meat, that they resign immediately.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutWC">
    <value>You are a Commis Chef and you can pick a staff to be your mentor when the restaurant first opens. If that staff leaves the restaurant, you will be very disappointed and turn to work for the competitor as one of their Talent Poachers.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutAppS">
    <value>You are the Sous Chef, second in command in the kitchen. Since you work closely with the Executive Chef (who you don't know actually...), you will take their role when they leave the kitchen.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutBH">
    <value>You are the Sauce Chef and you work closely with the Executive Chef to plan menus. You always know who the Executive Chef is.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutMason">
    <value>You are a Sashimi Chef. You are like any other chef, except you prefer to speak Japanese with the other Sashimi Chefs. Therefore you will know each other very well.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutDG">
    <value>You are the Management Trainee. When the restaurant first opens, you can choose a staff whose job you will replace if they leave the restaurant. Vegan Chefs cannot persuade you to try their lunchbox because you are so busy that you never really eat... (banksad)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutCupid">
    <value>You are the Barista, responsible for managing the corner café of the restaurant. Each season, you receive a rare shipment of Hacienda Le Roble coffee. You can only give two cups of these coffee for tasting to two staff - the rest are for our VIP customers. These two lucky staff will fall in love with the art of coffee and study about it together. They will dream of opening their own café, so much so that if one of them leaves the restaurant, the other will follow, or if they are the only two left in the restaurant, that they will sell the restaurant to open their own café. At the end of the game, if one of them is on the winning team, the other will win as well!    </value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutHunter">
    <value>
      You are the Food Critic 🖋(🎯). You are renowned for writing in-depth reviews about how a restaurant works and prepare their dishes... you can do that because you always disguise yourself as a chef and sneak into kitchens. Now that you are in this kitchen, if you are fired or asked to leave by anyone, you will reveal yourself and either criticise them or publish your review (where you can name and shame one staff in the process). The person you "attacked" would soon be fired as well!
      Note: For one Talent Poacher, there is a 30% chance they are evicted. For each additional Talent Poacher, add 20%. Where they are multiple Talent Poachers, although you may evict one of them, you will also be more likely to resign yourself. For Vegan Chefs, they have a 50% chance to inspiring you to embrace veganism and a 50% chance that you would lash out to them for supporting such a cause.
    </value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutSK">
    <value>You are the Vengeful Customer ☠️(🔪).  You came back to take revenge by disguising yourself as a chef and triggering allergic reactions for one staff per day. Surely they will learn to never leave a customer unattended again! MUAHAHAHA</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutPara">
    <value>Para opens a small café next to this restaurant. Or something like that. Idk.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="EndTime">
<!--New strings, July the 8th -->
    <value>Game Length: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Day">
<!--0 - Day -->
    <value>Evening {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NodeShutsDown">
    <value>An error has occurred, and this node has shut down</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SentPrivate">
    <value>I have sent you a PM</value>
  </string>
  <string deprecated="true" key="StartPM">
    <value>Please send me a pm so I can PM you: @werewolfbot</value>
  </string>
  <string deprecated="true" key="PMTrue">
    <value>Thanks for starting me! I can PM you now.</value>
  </string>
  <string deprecated="true" key="MustReplySmite">
    <value>You must reply to the user you want to smite</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WhatToDo">
    <value>What would you like to do?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="JoinFromGroup">
    <value>You must apply to join a restaurant from within a group chat!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="StartFromGroup">
    <value>You must open a restaurant from within a group chat!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PingInfo">
    <value>Time to receive ping message: {0}\nMessages per second: {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WhatLang">
    <value>What Language?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WhatVariant">
    <value>What Variant?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="LangSet">
    <value>Language set to {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GetLang">
    <value>Get which language file?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NoNodes">
    <value>There are no nodes online right now, please try again in a few seconds</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GroupCommandOnly">
    <value>You must run this command in a group</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NotGlobalAdmin">
    <value>You aren't a global admin...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NotPara">
    <value>You aren't Para!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Yes">
    <value>Yes</value>
  </string>
  <string key="No">
    <value>No</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Allow">
    <value>Allow</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Disallow">
    <value>Disallow</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Show">
    <value>Show</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Hide">
<!-- Game Mode Choices-->
    <value>Hide</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NormalOnly">
    <value>Normal Restaurants Only</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ChaosOnly">
    <value>Chaos Restaurants Only</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerChoice">
<!-- Show Roles on End Game -->
    <value>Chefs' Choice</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShowNone">
    <value>Don't show any</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShowLiving">
    <value>Show only staff still in restaurant</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShowAll">
    <value>Show all staff and roles</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Cancel">
    <value>Cancel</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowFleeQ">
    <value>Do you want to allow fleeing once the restaurant is open for business?\nNote: players can still flee during join phase\nCurrent: {0} fleeing</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowFleeA">
    <value>{0} fleeing after restaurant opens for business</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MaxPlayersQ">
    <value>How many staff would you like to set as the maximum?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MaxPlayersA">
    <value>Max staff number set to {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShowRolesDeathQ">
    <value>Show or Hide roles on leaving the restaurant?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShowRolesDeathA">
    <value>Roles will be {0} on leaving the restaurant.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GameModeQ">
    <value>What game mode will the group be?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GameModeA">
    <value>Game mode set to {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShowRolesEndQ">
    <value>How do you want roles to be shown at the end?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShowRolesEndA">
    <value>Roles shown at end set to: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SetDayTimeQ">
    <value>Choose the base time (in seconds) for Evening meeting time. This will still be modified based on number of players.\nDefault setting: {0}\nCurrent: {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SetDayTimeA">
    <value>Base Evening meeting time set to {0} seconds</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SetNightTimeQ">
    <value>Choose the time (in seconds) for Day time. Default setting: {0}\nCurrent:{1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SetNightTimeA">
    <value>Day time set to {0} seconds</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SetLynchTimeQ">
    <value>Choose the time (in seconds) for voting. Default setting: {0}\nCurrent:{1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SetLynchTimeA">
    <value>Voting time set to {0} seconds</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowFoolQ">
    <value>Allow Chief of Operations (Fool) as a role option?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowFoolA">
    <value>Chief of Operations (Fool) as a role set to: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowTannerQ">
    <value>Allow Dishwasher (Tanner) as a role option?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowTannerA">
    <value>Dishwasher (Tanner) as a role set to: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowCultQ">
    <value>Allow Vegan Chef (Cultist) as a role option?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowCultA">
    <value>Cult as a role set to: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="EnableSecretLynchQ">
    <value>Enable Secret Voting?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="EnableSecretLynchA">
    <value>Enabling of Secret Voting set to: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThankYou">
    <value>Thank you, Bon Appetit :)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WhatLangGroup">
    <value>What language do you want to look for a group to play in?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HereIsList">
    <value>Here are the groups for {0}:</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Members">
    <value>Members</value>
  </string>
  <string key="StartMe">
    <value>Please start me so I can PM you</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerNoPM">
    <value>{0} failed to start the bot, and has been removed from the restaurant!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="LatestList">
    <value>Here is the latest list</value>
  </string>
  <string key="UnableToGetList">
    <value>Unable to get latest list</value>
  </string>
  <string key="YouJoined">
<!-- 0 - Group Name -->
    <value>You have successfully joined the restaurant in {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Ping2">
<!-- Update 4.0-->
    <value>Time to send ping message: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoMayor">
    <value>You are Gordon Ramsay 🌟(🎖), the world-renowned British chef and one of the hosts of Masterchef. You are renowned for disguising yourself as a normal chef and infiltrating kitchens to surprise other chefs... which is what you are doing now! You can reveal to everyone during any evening meeting. After revealing, your votes will count twice as all the chefs look up to you.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoPrince">
    <value>You are the Bartender 🍹(👑). You practice your bar tricks and cocktail mixing during the day and use them to impress VIP guests at night. If the staff try to vote you out of the restaurant, you will immediately grab an empty bottle and perform a bottle toss to prove to everyone that you are the Bartender and not an imposter chef.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoClumsyGuy">
    <value>You are the Prep Cook 🥒(🤕), your sole job being to cut the food that the Line Cook asks you to. You are very focused in your work and seldom look around the kitchen, so you often forget who's who. During the voting, there is a 50% chance that you would vote for the wrong person because you mistook them for someone else!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoSorcerer">
    <value>You are the Fake Customer 😛(🔮). Being a fan of the competitor's restaurant, you help their Talent Poachers' 🍔(🐺) mission by coming to the restaurant every day and ordering some cheap food, perhaps sneaking into the kitchen to attend some staff meetings too. You can ask one staff per day to deliver your "compliments" to the Executive Chef. You will can tell whether that staff is an Executive Chef 🥖(👳) if they looked very pleased, a Talent Poacher if they look disgusted, or neither if they agreed to pass on your compliments.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoBlacksmith">
    <value>You are the Event Manager 🎂(⚒) and you plan all the special events in the restaurant. Each season, you can organise one big event and announce it during any evening staff meeting. After you announce the event, all the chefs will be so busy the next day that the Talent Poachers 🍔(🐺) will not be able to recruit anyone to the competitor's restaurant (they would be busy chopping vegetables too!).</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoAlphaWolf">
    <value>You are the Manager of the Competitor's Restaurant 🍟(⚡️). You lead your team of Talent Poachers 🍔(🐺) to do their mission in this kitchen. For each staff your team recruits, there is a 20% chance that you come across a chef skillful enough to become a Talent Poacher themselves, in which case you will harness all your charisma to persuade them to join your team as a Talent Poacher on the next day.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoWolfCub">
    <value>You are the Food Destroyer 🦴(🐶). You work with the Talent Poachers 🍔(🐺) to sabotage this restaurant, where your job is to destroy fresh ingredients and make them rot (e.g. pouring wine into the sink). You always clean up afterwards to avoid being caught, but you if you left the restaurant, the kitchen will be very stinky and the Talent Poachers would be twice as successful on the next day.</value>
    <value>You are the Food Destroyer 🦴(🐶). You work with the Talent Poachers 🍔(🐺) to sabotage this restaurant, where your job is to destroy fresh ingredients and make them rot (e.g. hiding expensive meats under the counter). You always clean up afterwards to avoid being caught, but you if you left the restaurant, the kitchen will be very stinky and the Talent Poachers would be twice as successful on the next day.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PrinceLynched">
    <value>{0} was about to pack their bags and leave when they found a bottle of vodka they kept in their locker. They immediately grabbed it to perform a bottle throw trick, surprising everyone and letting them know that they were just the Bartender 🍹(👑). {0} is relieved that everyone understands and could continue working.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SorcererOther">
    <value>"This is how bacon is supposed to be!" you told {0} pretentiously, who was standing next to the table. They thanked you for your feedback and promised to pass your compliments to the Executive Chef. Clearly, they were neither the Executive Chef 🥖(👳) nor one of the Talent Poachers 🍔(🐺).</value>
    <value>"The fries, they blend so perfectly!" you told {0} pretentiously, who was standing next to the table. They thanked you for your feedback and promised to pass your compliments to the Executive Chef. Clearly, they were neither the Executive Chef 🥖(👳) nor one of the Talent Poachers 🍔(🐺).</value>
    <value>"The cheese up in here is goin' ham!" you told {0} pretentiously, who was standing next to the table. They thanked you for your feedback and promised to pass your compliments to the Executive Chef. Clearly, they were neither the Executive Chef 🥖(👳) nor one of the Talent Poachers 🍔(🐺).</value>
    <value>"Dayum, dayum, dayum!" you told {0} pretentiously, who was standing next to the table. They thanked you for your feedback and promised to pass your compliments to the Executive Chef. Clearly, they were neither the Executive Chef 🥖(👳) nor one of the Talent Poachers 🍔(🐺).</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MayorReveal">
    <value>"Everyone, may I have your attention please?" The room went silent as {0} stepped onto a chair and peeled off his fake moustache. "It's me!" Everyone gasped as they realised that Gordon Ramsay 🌟(🎖) has visited this restaurant as an undercover chef. From now on, Gordon will mentor the chefs and his votes will count twice!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskMayor">
    <value>Click "It's Me!" whenever you are ready to peel off your fake moustache and reveal yourself as Gordon Ramsay</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Reveal">
    <value>It's Me!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SpreadDust">
    <value>Will you announce that you are planning a special event for tomorrow?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="BlacksmithSpreadSilver">
    <value>{0} the Event Manager 🎂(⚒) announces that there would be a celebrity wedding tomorrow evening! Everyone is thrilled and worried at the same time, as they know they would have to cook their hearts out tomorrow. There will be so much work that the Talent Poachers 🍔(🐺) would find it difficult to recruit anyone tomorrow.</value>
    <value>{0} the Event Manager 🎂(⚒) announces that there would be a baby shower event tomorrow evening! Everyone is thrilled and worried at the same time, as they know they would have to cook their hearts out tomorrow. There will be so much work that the Talent Poachers 🍔(🐺) would find it difficult to recruit anyone tomorrow.</value>
    <value>{0} the Event Manager 🎂(⚒) announces that there would be a special retirement party tomorrow evening! Everyone is thrilled and worried at the same time, as they know they would have to cook their hearts out tomorrow. There will be so much work that the Talent Poachers 🍔(🐺) would find it difficult to recruit anyone tomorrow.</value>
    <value>{0} the Event Manager 🎂(⚒) announces that the restaurant is celebrating its 25th anniversary tomorrow evening! Everyone is thrilled and worried at the same time, as they know they would have to cook their hearts out tomorrow. There will be so much work that the Talent Poachers 🍔(🐺) would find it difficult to recruit anyone tomorrow.</value>
    <value>{0} the Event Manager 🎂(⚒) announces that there would be a birthday banquet for the restaurant owner's child tomorrow evening! Everyone is thrilled and worried at the same time, as they know they would have to cook their hearts out tomorrow. There will be so much work that the Talent Poachers 🍔(🐺) would find it difficult to recruit anyone tomorrow.</value>
    <value>{0} the Event Manager 🎂(⚒) announces that there would be a big international buffet tomorrow evening! Everyone is thrilled and worried at the same time, as they know they would have to cook their hearts out tomorrow. There will be so much work that the Talent Poachers 🍔(🐺) would find it difficult to recruit anyone tomorrow.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Mayor">
    <value>Gordon Ramsay 🌟(🎖)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Prince">
    <value>the Bartender 🍹(👑)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Sorcerer">
    <value>the Fake Customer 😛(🔮)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ClumsyGuy">
    <value>the Prep Cook 🥒(🤕)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Blacksmith">
    <value>the Event Manager 🎂(⚒)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AlphaWolf">
    <value>the Manager of the Competitor's Restaurant 🍟(⚡️)️</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolfCub">
    <value>the Food Destroyer 🦴(🐶)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerBittenWolves">
    <value>The Talent Poachers 🍔(🐺) were successful to recruit {0} to the competitor's restaurant. The Manager of the Competitor's Restaurant 🍟(⚡️), {1}, believes that {0} would make a great addition to the team and gives a heart-moving speech to woo them. They were totally convinced and agreed that they would become a Talent Poacher tomorrow.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerBitten">
    <value>You were invited by the Talent Poachers 🍔(🐺) to join the competitor's restaurant. With such an attractive offer, you couldn't resist. The Manager of the Competitor's Restaurant 🍟(⚡️) was also there and wholeheartedly asked that you help them on your mission. You feel like you just found renewed purposed in life after their speech and so you promised that you would become a Talent Poacher tomorrow!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="BittenTurned">
    <value>~ Whoosh ~ The next day comes and you officially begin your "new job" as a Talent Poacher 🍔(🐺).</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutMayor">
    <value>You are Gordon Ramsay 🌟(🎖), the world-renowned British chef and one of the hosts of Masterchef. You are renowned for disguising yourself as a normal chef and infiltrating kitchens to surprise other chefs... which is what you are doing now! You can reveal to everyone during any evening meeting. After revealing, your votes will count twice as all the chefs look up to you.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutPrince">
    <value>You are the Bartender. If you are voted by the staff to be fired, just before you leave, you will perform a bottle toss trick to prove you are the Bartender and continue working the next day. If you are voted to be fired again, you will feel defeated and just leave the restaurant.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutSorcerer">
    <value>You are the Fake Customer. You help the Talent Poachers, in particular to identify who the Executive Chef is by ordering food to your table and asking one staff to deliver your compliments to the Executive Chef. If the staff says they are the Executive Chef 👳 themselves, you have found them! If the staff gives you a disdainful look, they are certainly one of the Talent Poachers 🐺!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutClumsy">
    <value>You are the Prep Cook, focusing every hour of your work on chopping all the food that the Line Cook assigns to you. That is why you cannot recognise 90% of the chefs. When you are voting, half the time you would realise you voted for someone wrongly because you mistook them for someone.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutBlacksmith">
    <value>You are the Event Manager who is in charge of planning the special events of the restaurant. You can hold one event per season and announce this event during any evening staff meeting. After you announced the event which will be held on the next day, the staff will have to work their hearts out and Talent Poachers would not be able to recruit anyone the next day.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutAlphaWolf">
    <value>You are the Manager of the Competitor's Restaurant. You manage your team of Talent Poachers and join them to recruit chefs. There is a 20% chance that you will come across a skillful chef, after which you will channel your charisma to persuade them to become a Talent Poacher themselves on the next day.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutWolfCub">
<!-- new strings 06 nov-->
    <value>You are the Food Destroyer, part of the Talent Poachers team. Apart from recruiting chefs, you have an additional task of destroying the fresh ingredients in the kitchen, which means letting them rot and then throwing them out. If you leave the restaurant, the food you leave rotting would be unchecked and leave a great stink in the kitchen. This helps the Talent Poacher recruit 2 staff instead of 1 the next day.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGTransformToAlpha">
<!-- 0 - target's name -->
<!-- 1 - teammates' names -->
    <value>Because {0} has left the restaurant, you were assigned to replace them. On the way to work, the boss of the competitor's restaurant came to tell you that {0} was actually the Manager of the Competitor's Restaurant 🍟(⚡️), who is working undercover together with the Talent Poachers {1}. You feel like you hit jackpot and willingly take up your new, high-paid job!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGTransformToWolfCub">
<!-- 0 - target's name -->
<!-- 1 - teammates' names -->
    <value>Because {0} has left the restaurant, you were assigned to replace them. On the way to work, one of the staff from the competitor's restaurant came to tell you that {0} was actually the Food Destroyer 🦴(🐶), working next to the Talent Poachers {1}. You are working for the competitor now!</value>
  </string>
  <string deprecated="true" key="VillageTeam">
    <value>Restaurant Team</value>
  </string>
  <string deprecated="true" key="NeutralTeam">
    <value>Neutral Team</value>
  </string>
  <string deprecated="true" key="SerialKillerTeam">
    <value>Vengeful Customer Team</value>
  </string>
  <string deprecated="true" key="TannerTeam">
    <value>Dishwasher Team</value>
  </string>
  <string key="VillageTeamEnd">
    <value>Restaurant Team</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NeutralTeamEnd">
    <value>Neutral Team</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolfTeamEnd">
    <value>Competitor's Team</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SerialKillerTeamEnd">
    <value>Vengeful Customer Team</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultTeamEnd">
    <value>Vegan Team</value>
  </string>
  <string key="TannerTeamEnd">
    <value>Dishwasher Team</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultConvertWolf">
    <value>{0} tried to share their delicious vegan lunchbox with {1}, but soon after they returned - with a big smile in their face. They took off their chef's uniform and left the restaurant immediately!? Maybe they got a new job offer 🍔(🐺) at the competitor's restaurant...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotFuckedKilledPublic">
<!-- used when Harlot visit's SK's victim, and dies -->
<!--{0} = Harlot name, {1} = SK's victim name-->
<!--New Death Strings 05 DEC-->
    <value>{0} went to the back-alley to look for {1} for some chit-chat 🍒(💋). They were surprised to find {1} trembling on the floor with foam coming out of their mouth.... {0} felt a hand with a glove touch their neck, but before they could turn around to see who it was, the person left. Soon after, {0} also fainted on the floor with some foam from their mouth. Both of them were rushed to the hospital due to the serious allergic reaction they had ☠️(🔪).</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ApprenticeSeerEaten">
    <value>The staff found some blunt knives on the table in the common room next to a resignation letter written by 🥐(🙇), the Sous Chef. Seems {0} has crossed the street to join the competitor's restaurant after being given an attractive offer...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="BlacksmithKilled">
    <value>The staff were shocked to hear that {0}, the Event Manager 🎂(⚒), was sent to hospital due to an allergic reaction. Did they eat too much oysters from the big buffet or how did that happen?</value>
    <value>The staff were shocked to hear that {0}, the Event Manager 🎂(⚒), was sent to hospital due to an allergic reaction. Were they allergic to the goat's milk from the intriguing dessert served or how did that happen?</value>
    <value>The staff were shocked to hear that {0}, the Event Manager 🎂(⚒), was sent to hospital due to an allergic reaction. Did they ate stale sashimi from the wedding buffet or how did that happen?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultistKilled">
    <value>{0} was rushed to the hospital today after having their lunchbox. The staff are gossiping and saying that the vegan food found 🥑(👤) in their lunchbox was the cause of the allergy, although some believe that one of the spy chefs are responsible...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CupidKilled">
    <value>{0} the Barista ☕️(🏹) was rushed to the hospital in the middle of the day due to a serious allergic reaction. This puzzles everyone because we all know that {0} only drank coffee and ate tiramisu for their lunches...</value>
    <value>{0} the Barista ☕️(🏹) was rushed to the hospital in the middle of the day due to a serious allergic reaction. This puzzles everyone because we all know that {0} only drank coffee and ate mocha cheesecakes for their lunches...</value>
    <value>{0} the Barista ☕️(🏹) was rushed to the hospital in the middle of the day due to a serious allergic reaction. This puzzles everyone because we all know that {0} only drank coffee and ate chocolate truffles for their lunches...</value>
    <value>{0} the Barista ☕️(🏹) was rushed to the hospital in the middle of the day due to a serious allergic reaction. This puzzles everyone because we all know that {0} only drank coffee and ate cappuccino mousses for their lunches...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DrunkKilled">
    <value>The Sommelier 🍷(🍻) {0} was rushed to the hospital today. They were found on the floor of the wine cellar with a serious allergic reaction ☠️(🔪). Someone should replace those dirty wooden barrels before another person gets an allergy there... unless the barrels were not the cause.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardianAngelKilled">
    <value>The staff were disappointed to learn that {0}, the Safety Supervisor ⚠️(👼) was sent to the hospital due to an allergic reaction ☠️(🔪). Why are they giving lengthy talks about safety to everyone if they can't stay safe themselves?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GunnerKilled">
    <value>The Senior Chef 🧀(🔫) {0} was sent to the hospital today due to a serious allergic reaction. Given that {0} has held a perfect record of 20 years without having an accident in the kitchen, people were saying that someone else must have "caused" their allergies ☠️(🔪)...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MayorKilled">
    <value>The moustached Gordon Ramsay 🌟(🎖) {0} was rushed to the hospital along with a lot of paparazzi due to an allergic reaction ☠️(🔪). There is going to be a lot of bad press tomorrow as critics each give their own conspiracy theory how such an accident could have happened in this Michelin 3-star restaurant's kitchen!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PrinceKilled">
    <value>{0} the Bartender 🍹(👑) was sent to the hospital today, not because they have injured themselves (which they have done before, countless times...) again in a bottle throw, but because of an allergic reaction ☠️(🔪)!?!? I thought Bartenders aren't allowed to eat and drink until their shift is over...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SeerKilled">
    <value>Everyone is shocked to learn that {0} the Executive Chef 🥖(👳) was rushed to hospital after suffering a severe allergic reaction ☠️(🔪). Who's in charge of the kitchen now? The security guards must get to the bottom of this and see who is responsible for {0}'s allergies!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SorcererEaten">
    <value>The staff gathered in the common room and heard the swearing of a frustrated person leaving through the back door. It was {0}, who everyone thought was one of the Kitchen Porters running in the kitchen but was actually a Fake Customer 😛(🔮), a fan of the competitor's restaurant! Perhaps {0} was disappointed that the Talent Poachers 🍔(🐺) would be as stupid as to invite someone as suspicious and talentless as {0} to the competitor's restaurant.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WildChildEaten">
    <value>The Commis Chef 🧅(👶) {0} left the restaurant today, abandoning the wonderful mentorship opportunities this restaurant offered. One of the HR assistants say that it was because they had found a better job opportunity across the street 🍔(🐺)! Young cooks these days are so blunt and honest...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SerialKillerKilledCH">
<!--used when CH visits SK-->
    <value>The Butcher Chef 🍖(💂) {0} was rushed to the hospital today... their face was covered with a kitchen towel when the paramedics lifted them up because they had an allergic reaction on their face! Some chefs saw that {0} was trying to check the lunchbox of a suspicious chef ☠️(🔪), but as they opened the lunchbox they were sprayed with some weird, acidic substances. This will teach them about messing with other people's food.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultConvertWolfPublic">
<!--used when Cultists convert the wolves, only if wolves stayed home-->
    <value>{0} the Vegan Chef 🥑(👤) had resigned from their job today with a big smile on their face. Seems they were invited to a better job position across the street while they were trying to inspire someone 🍔(🐺) to try their vegan lunchbox!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultConvertKillerPublic">
<!--used when Cultists convert the SK-->
    <value>{0} the Vegan Chef 🥑(👤) was rushed to hospital today due to an allergic reaction. Their friends saw that they were trying to inspire someone to try their vegan lunchbox, but was slapped in the face afterwards. Soon, the slapped cheek was puffing up and their face started to spasm ☠️(🔪)... and for the rest I would not go into details...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GAGuardedKiller">
<!-- used when GA guards SK -->
    <value>{0} the Safety Supervisor ⚠️(👼) was just asking a chef not to touch other people with dirty hands... they were soon rushed to the hospital with a swollen face due to an allergic reaction ☠️(🔪). Maybe they should have been less strict with these newcomers...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GAGuardedWolf">
<!-- used when GA guards a wolf -->
<!--1vs1 finales-->
    <value>The staff were kind of happy to know that {0}, the strict Safety Supervisor ⚠️(👼) has resigned from their job today. As to why they did so - some saw {0} dragging a fellow staff into the back-alley for a lecturing, but soon returned to their station to pack their bags and leave the restaurant, perhaps because of an unrefusable job offer 🍔(🐺)!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterKillsWolfEnd">
<!--{0} = hunter's name, {1} = wolf's name-->
    <value>With one person left, {1} invited {0} to the back-alley and thought it would be easy to recruit them as well. What they didn't expect was the restaurant owner standing there alongside {0}, who was the Food Critic 🖋(🎯)! {0} knew what {1} was doing all this time and already told the owner about all the unethical things they did, so {1} was fired! {0} also agreed to stay to help the owner save the restaurant!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolfKillsHunterEnd">
<!--{0} = hunter's name, {1} = wolf's name-->
    <value>With one more staff to recruit, {1} invites {0} into the back-alley and thought it would be easy since everyone else had either left the restaurant or been recruited to work for the competitor... and it was! {0} revealed themselves to be the Food Critic 🖋(🎯), who felt very disappointed at the restaurant owner for letting all their experienced staff leave just like that. They agree to join the competitor's restaurant as a Guest Chef and the Talent Poachers have successfully dismantled this restaurant!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CHKillsCultistEnd">
<!--{0} = last cultist's name, {1} = CH's name -->
<!-- Extend time -->
    <value>Only {0} and {1} are left in the kitchen. {0} held out their vegan lunchbox 🥑(👤) with shaky hands, hoping that {1} would be inspired to try it and continue the legacy of this restaurant by working with them to plan a whole new vegan menu. Being the Butcher Chef 🍖(💂), not only did {1} refuse to try it, they grabbed a piece of uncooked lamb shank and smacked {0} in the head! {0} broke down into tears and ran away from the restaurant, leaving the {1} and the restaurant team as the victorious "survivors"!</value>
    <value>Only {0} and {1} are left in the kitchen. {0} held out their vegan lunchbox 🥑(👤) with shaky hands, hoping that {1} would be inspired to try it and continue the legacy of this restaurant by working with them to plan a whole new vegan menu. Being the Butcher Chef 🍖(💂), not only did {1} refuse to try it, they grabbed an uncooked tomahawk steak and smacked {0} in the head! {0} broke down into tears and ran away from the restaurant, leaving the {1} and the restaurant team as the victorious "survivors"!</value>
    <value>Only {0} and {1} are left in the kitchen. {0} held out their vegan lunchbox 🥑(👤) with shaky hands, hoping that {1} would be inspired to try it and continue the legacy of this restaurant by working with them to plan a whole new vegan menu. Being the Butcher Chef 🍖(💂), not only did {1} refuse to try it, they took a big red snapper and smacked {0} in the head! {0} broke down into tears and ran away from the restaurant, leaving the {1} and the restaurant team as the victorious "survivors"!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SecondsAdded">
<!-- 0 - Seconds added by /extend command -->
<!-- 1 - Total seconds remaining -->
    <value>Join time extended by {0} seconds!\n{1} left to Join the restaurant</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SecondsRemoved">
<!-- 0 - Seconds removed by /extend command -->
<!-- 1 - Total seconds remaining -->
    <value>Join time decreased by {0} seconds!\n{1} left to Join the restaurant</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CantExtend">
    <value>Only members of the Restaurant Discipline Council can extend the time more than once!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowExtendQ">
<!--{0} = "Allow" / "Disallow" string-->
    <value>Allow staff to extend join time?\nCurrent: {0} extending\nNote: Members of the Restaurant Discipline Council will always be able to extend</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowExtendA">
<!--{0} = "Allow" / "Disallow" string-->
    <value>{0} staff to extend join time</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MaxExtendQ">
    <value>Choose maximum number of seconds which can be added to joining timer by a single /extend command.\nDefault setting: {0}\nCurrent:{1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MaxExtendA">
    <value>Maximum extending time set to {0} seconds</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolvesEatDrunkBlockSecondKill">
    <value>Lucky for you, you were able to recruit {0} the Sommelier 🍷(🍻) to join the competitor's restaurant! Taking their keys to the wine cellar, you and your spymates spent the rest of the day taking sips from the valuable wine collection and feel a little bit tipsy now... which also means you will have no time left to recruit {1} as the second chef...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="JoinButton">
    <value>Join</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NotMember">
    <value>You can't work for this restaurant because you don't seem to be a member of {0}.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="JoinByButton">
    <value>Please don't use the commands to join. Use this button instead.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerVoteCounts">
    <value>{0} staff have voted, {1} total.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NoAutoJoin">
    <value>{0}, please remember that you will have to join with the button as well.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GroupNotFound">
<!--This string might need rewording from some native speaker-->
    <value>Couldn't find the group. Please run this command in the group you want to stop waiting for, or add link, id, or username next to the command.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DeletedFromWaitList">
    <value>You have been deleted from the wait list for {0}.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HaveJoined">
<!-- {0} = list of people who have joined -->
<!-- NOTE: No space between {0} and joined. It will be added in the code if necessary-->
    <value>{0}joined the restaurant in the last 30 seconds.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowCult">
    <value>Allow Vegan Chef (Cultist)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowTanner">
    <value>Allow Dishwasher (Tanner)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowFool">
    <value>Allow Chief of Operations (Fool)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="EnableSecretLynch">
    <value>Enable Secret Vote</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RandomMode">
    <value>Enable Random Mode</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowExtend">
    <value>Allow Extending Timer</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShowRolesDeath">
    <value>Show Roles on Leaving the Restaurant</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowFlee">
    <value>Allow Fleeing</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShowIDs">
    <value>Show IDs on joining</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShowIDsQ">
    <value>Show IDs of players while they join the restaurant?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShowIDsA">
    <value>{0} IDs</value>
  </string>
  <string key="All">
<!-- used when searching for groups in all the variants -->
    <value>All</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RandomModeQ">
    <value>Enable random mode?\nWhen random mode is enabled, Chaos, Secret Vote, Show Roles on Leaving the Restaurant, and Allow Vegan Chef / Chief of Operations / Dishwasher will be randomly determined every time someone opens a restaurant.\nCurrent:{0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RandomModeA">
    <value>Enabling of random mode set to: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowNSFW">
    <value>Allow NSFW Gif Packs</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowNSFWQ">
    <value>Allow players to have NSFW gif packs?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowNSFWA">
    <value>{0} NSFW Gifs</value>
  </string>
  <string key="TannerEnd">
<!-- 0 - Tanner name -->
    <value>~ Whoosh ~ Another beautiful day of work at this prestigious restaurant. {0} walks through the main door and is very pleased to see that there were no customers, no waiters, no bartenders and no chefs. The restaurant is empty and only {0}, the Dishwasher 🧽(👺), was left. There will be no dishes to clean! But also no money to be earned... If only those cooks had voted to fire {0}, they would have already earned 6 months of severance pay and perhaps spent a bit of that money enjoying a chicken pot pie in this restaurant!</value>
    <value>~ Whoosh ~ Another beautiful day of work at this prestigious restaurant. {0} walks through the main door and is very pleased to see that there were no customers, no waiters, no bartenders and no chefs. The restaurant is empty and only {0}, the Dishwasher 🧽(👺), was left. There will be no dishes to clean! But also no money to be earned... If only those cooks had voted to fire {0}, they would have already earned 6 months of severance pay and perhaps spent a bit of that money enjoying a pot au feu in this restaurant!</value>
    <value>~ Whoosh ~ Another beautiful day of work at this prestigious restaurant. {0} walks through the main door and is very pleased to see that there were no customers, no waiters, no bartenders and no chefs. The restaurant is empty and only {0}, the Dishwasher 🧽(👺), was left. There will be no dishes to clean! But also no money to be earned... If only those cooks had voted to fire {0}, they would have already earned 6 months of severance pay and perhaps spent a bit of that money enjoying a coq au vin in this restaurant!</value>
    <value>~ Whoosh ~ Another beautiful day of work at this prestigious restaurant. {0} walks through the main door and is very pleased to see that there were no customers, no waiters, no bartenders and no chefs. The restaurant is empty and only {0}, the Dishwasher 🧽(👺), was left. There will be no dishes to clean! But also no money to be earned... If only those cooks had voted to fire {0}, they would have already earned 6 months of severance pay and perhaps spent a bit of that money enjoying a glass of sparkling water in this restaurant!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SorcererEnd">
<!-- 0 - Sorcerer name -->
    <value>"Waiter! Anyone! I wish you could smell what I'm smellin!" {0} shouts out loudly while sitting in the middle of the restaurant. They have succeeded on their mission in helping the competitor tear down this restaurant. The 3 Michelin stars have been repealed for bad service, all the cooks have left, even all the food in the storage room was stolen by the homeless. However, the competitor's restaurant was also taken down after so many Talent Poachers were exposed for their unethical behaviour. {0} is now all alone, with no food to enjoy and no one to listen to their fake compliments 😛(🔮)!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WhatVariantVets">
    <value>What Variant?\nCurrent: {0}\nAs you have joined over 500 restaurants you can also join: </value>
  </string>
  <string key="Skip">
<!-- New Roles, April 2018 -->
    <value>Skip</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGTransformToLycan">
<!-- 0 - target's name -->
<!-- 1 - teammates' names -->
    <value>Because {0} has left the restaurant, you were assigned to replace them. On the way to work, one of the staff from the competitor's restaurant came to tell you that {0} was actually the Line Sabotager 🍩(🐺🌝), working next to the Talent Poachers 🍔(🐺) {1}. You are working for the competitor now!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NegSeerSees">
<!-- 0 - target's name -->
<!-- 1 - role that they are not -->
    <value>After spending a whole day working with {0} to expedite orders, although you still do not know their exact role, you are sure they are NOT {1}!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskSandman">
    <value>Would you like to announce a routine inspection for tomorrow?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SandmanSleepAll">
    <value>The in-house Food Inspector 🔍(💤), {0}, suddenly announced that there will be a routine inspection tomorrow. The restaurant will be closed during the day for {0} to check the quality of the fresh ingredients and for electricians to check the kitchen equipment. No one will be working during daytime, but they still have to return for the evening staff meeting.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SandmanNight">
    <value>~ Whoosh ~ The next day arrives and everyone is glad to enjoy a whole day of paid leave while the inspection 🔍(💤) was going on in the restaurant. They all return to the common room at the evening for the daily staff meeting.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowThiefQ">
    <value>Allow Busser (Thief) as a role option?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowThiefA">
    <value>Busser (Thief) as a role set to: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThiefFullQ">
    <value>Busser (Thief) can be used every night?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThiefFullA">
    <value>Busser (Thief) will play every night: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowThief">
    <value>Allow Busser (Thief)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThiefFull">
    <value>Busser (Thief) Full Game</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoWolfMan">
    <value>You are the Part-time Cook 🥔(👱🌚), who is often missing from work in the morning and only comes in for the afternoon shift and evening meeting. The Executive Chef 🥖(👳) may think that you are one of the Talent Poachers 🍔(🐺) because you are missing from duty every morning, while the Accountant 🕰(🕵️) will know who you are by checking your time-records.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolfMan">
    <value>the Part-time Cook 🥔(👱🌚)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutWolfMan">
    <value>You are the Part-time Cook 🥔(👱🌚), who often is missing from work in the morning and only comes in for the afternoon shift and evening meeting. The Executive Chef 🥖(👳) may think that you are one of the Talent Poachers 🍔(🐺) because you are missing from duty every morning, while the Accountant 🕰(🕵️) will know who you are by checking your time-records.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoLycan">
    <value>You are the Line Sabotager 🍩(🐺🌝). You help the Talent Poachers 🍔(🐺) recruit staff by causing trouble for other chefs, such as ordering the Prep Cooks to cut cherry tomatoes into cubes... The Executive Chef 🥖(👳) may be fooled by your fake leadership and think you are a real Line Cook 🧑‍🍳(👱)!</value>
    <value>You are the Line Sabotager 🍩(🐺🌝). You help the Talent Poachers 🍔(🐺) recruit staff by causing trouble for other chefs, such as ordering the Commis Chefs to crush black pepper by hand... The Executive Chef 🥖(👳) may be fooled by your fake leadership and think you are a real Line Cook 🧑‍🍳(👱)!</value>
    <value>You are the Line Sabotager 🍩(🐺🌝). You help the Talent Poachers 🍔(🐺) recruit staff by causing trouble for other chefs, such as ordering the Prep Cooks to gently massage the salmon filets... The Executive Chef 🥖(👳) may be fooled by your fake leadership and think you are a real Line Cook 🧑‍🍳(👱)!</value>
    <value>You are the Line Sabotager 🍩(🐺🌝). You help the Talent Poachers 🍔(🐺) recruit staff by causing trouble for other chefs, such as ordering the Commis Cooks to put exactly 100 grains of salt on the fries ... The Executive Chef 🥖(👳) may be fooled by your fake leadership and think you are a real Line Cook 🧑‍🍳(👱)!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Lycan">
    <value>the Line Sabotager 🍩(🐺🌝)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutLycan">
    <value>You are the Line Sabotager 🍩(🐺🌝). You help the Talent Poachers 🍔(🐺) recruit staff to join the competitor's restaurant by acting like a Line Cook. The Executive Chef 🥖(👳) may be fooled by your act and think you are a real Line Cook 🧑‍🍳(👱)!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoOracle">
    <value>You are the Expeditor ⏰(🌀), helping chefs to arrange and deliver orders to the right customer at the right time and in the best quality. Each day, you can supervise one person to teach them how to work as a team and get orders finished on time. However, because you are not familiar with cooking, you can only tell what role that person is NOT (the role you see will be the role of another staff in the kitchen)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Oracle">
    <value>the Expeditor ⏰(🌀)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutOracle">
    <value>You are the Expeditor ⏰(🌀). Each day you can supervise one person to ensure that they complete their work at the right time. You will be told that role that person is NOT (the role you see will be the role of another staff in the kitchen)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoSandman">
    <value>You are the Food Inspector 🔍(💤). Your job is to maintain the quality of the fresh ingredients in the kitchen and occasionally help the Sous Chef to check the electrical equipment. Once per season, you can announce an inspection to take place on the next day. Everyone will get a day of paid leave (Yay!) while your team of electricians enter the kitchen to check the equipment and you check the quality of the food in the storage room.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Sandman">
    <value>the Food Inspector 🔍(💤)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutSandman">
    <value>You are the Food Inspector 🔍(💤). Once per season, you can announce an inspection to take place on the next day. Everyone will get a day of paid leave (Yay!) while your team inspects the kitchen.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoPacifist">
    <value>You are the Pastry Chef 🍨(☮️), working hard to lead your team to bake delicious desserts and invent new ones. The restaurant owner is very generous and decided that once per season, you can bake a surprise treat for the staff. You can choose to reveal your treats at any evening meeting, which will make everyone very happy and forget about voting out a spy on that evening.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Pacifist">
    <value>the Pastry Chef 🍨(☮️)️</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutPacifist">
    <value>You are the Pastry Chef 🍨(☮️). Once per season, you can bake a surprise treat for the staff and choose to reveal your treats at any evening meeting, which will make everyone very happy and forget about voting out a spy on that evening.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoWiseElder">
    <value>You are the Visiting Chef 🦞(📚). You come from a renowned restaurant in Lima, Peru. You were invited as a visiting chef in this restaurant and are responsible for hosting the Chef's Tasting Menu event, where you serve up exotic Peruvian dishes. You don't speak English very well, so that when the Talent Poachers 🍔(🐺) try to invite you to visit the competitor's restaurant instead, you will not understand them the first time, but you would in the second time. If the Senior Chef or the Food Critic tries to accuse you for being an unwelcome visitor, you will leave the restaurant in great rage while the restaurant owner will punish them for being so disrespectful to you!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WiseElder">
    <value>the Visiting Chef 🦞(📚)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutWiseElder">
    <value>You are the Visiting Chef 🦞(📚), a famous chef from Peru. You don't speak English very well, so when the Talent Poachers 🍔(🐺) try to invite you to visit the competitor's restaurant, you will not understand them the first time, but you would in the second time. If the Senior Chef or the Food Critic tries to accuse you for being an unwelcome visitor, you will leave the restaurant in great rage while the restaurant owner will punish them for being so disrespectful to you!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoThief">
    <value>You are the Busser 🍽(😈), responsible for clearing and setting tables after each customer leaves. No one likes to take this job so the owner has decided that there will be no official position for it and the duty shall be rotated amongst staff. During the day, you can ask a staff member to replace you as the Busser with a game of rock-paper-scissors. If you win, you would take their role while they would become a Line Cook 🧑‍🍳(👱) with part-time bussing responsibilities.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoThiefFull">
    <value>You are the Busser 🍽(😈), responsible for clearing and setting tables after each customer leaves. No one likes to take this job so the owner has decided that there will be no official position for it and the duty shall be rotated amongst staff. During the day, you can ask a staff member to replace you as the Busser with a game of rock-paper-scissors. If you win, you would swap roles with them, while they would have to keep playing the game to pass on this mundane job.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Thief">
    <value>the Busser 🍽(😈)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutThief">
    <value>You are the Busser 🍽(😈). On the first day, you can ask a staff to replace you as the Busser with a game of rock-paper-scissors, after which you will take their role if you win while they will become a Line Cook with part-time bussing responsibilities.\nIn [Full Busser] mode, you will have 50% chance of winning and taking their role, in which they will become the new Busser and continue playing rock-paper-scissors with other staff to pass on this mundane job.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskPacifist">
    <value>Press this button when you are ready to show everyone the secret treats you prepared!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PacifistNoLynch">
<!-- {0} - Pacifist's name -->
<!-- {0} - Pacifist's name -->
    <value>Suddenly, a calming scent of vanilla wafts through the room. The Pastry Chef 🍨(☮️)️ {0} has prepared a special treat of coconut pandan panna cottas for everyone for their hard work! The staff dig into their rightfully deserved desserts and soon forgot that they had to vote today!</value>
    <value>Suddenly, a clean scent of lemon wafts through the room. The Pastry Chef 🍨(☮️) {0} has prepared a special treat of lemon meringue tarts for everyone for their hard work! The staff dig into their rightfully deserved desserts and soon forgot that they had to vote today!</value>
    <value>Suddenly, the lights of the room were turned off. The Pastry Chef 🍨(☮️) {0} appears in the middle of the room with their cart as they set their ladle of rum on fire and poured it over the big baked alaska that they have prepared as a special treat for everyone's hard work! The staff dig into their rightfully deserved desserts and soon forgot that they had to vote today!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PacifistNoLynchNow">
    <value>Everyone was too busy enjoying the treats prepared by the Pastry Chef 🍨(☮️) that they skipped the voting!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolvesTriedToEatWiseElder">
<!-- 0 - Wise Elder's name -->
    <value>The Talent Poachers tried to invite {0} to join the competitor's restaurant, but they seemed very confused at what you were saying... soon after you realised that they were the Visiting Chef 🦞(📚) from Peru! You retreated and you will do a better invitation next time (perhaps in Spanish!)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolvesAteWiseElderPM">
    <value>Some dubious chefs tried to invite you to another restaurant today, but you didn't understand why... maybe you didn't get what they were trying to say because of your limited English. You returned to work and quickly forgot about who these chefs were...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterKilledWiseElder">
<!-- {0} - Hunter's Name -->
<!-- {1} - Wise Elder's Name -->
    <value>The Food Critic 🖋(🎯) {0} had named and shamed {1} in their review. What they didn't know was {1} was actually the world-famous Peruvian Visiting Chef 🦞(📚). All the other experts in the culinary field agreed that {0}'s review was trash and that {0} should restart their career as a Line Cook 🧑‍🍳(👱) to learn how to be a humble person.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GunnerShotWiseElder">
<!-- {0} - Gunner's Name -->
<!-- {1} - Wise Elder's Name -->
    <value>The Senior Chef 🧀(🔫), {0}, wrongly accused the Visiting Chef 🦞(📚), {1}, of being a spy. The restaurant owner was very disappointed that despite all those years of experience, {0} couldn't even recognise a prominent figure in the culinary world, which is why {0} was immediately demoted to a Line Cook 🧑‍🍳(👱) - regretfully a more fitting role for them.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThiefStealFailed">
<!-- {0} - The name of the thief's target -->
    <value>"Rock, paper, scissors, shoot!" You lost your game with {0} and so you will continue to be the Busser... :(</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThiefStealDead">
<!-- {0} - The name of the thief's target -->
    <value>You wanted to play a game of "rock, paper, scissors" with {0}, but learnt that {0} has left the restaurant !?!</value>
  </string>
  <string deprecated="true" key="ThiefStoleYourRole">
<!-- {0} - The new role -->
    <value>The Busser 🍽(😈) played a game of "rock, paper, scissors" with you and you lost! You passed them your uniform and gave them your role, while you became {0}.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThiefStoleRole">
<!-- {0} - The name of the thief's target -->
    <value>"Rock, paper, scissors, shoot!" You have defeated {0} with your rock and took their role in the kitchen!</value>
    <value>"Rock, paper, scissors, shoot!" You have defeated {0} with your paper and took their role in the kitchen!</value>
    <value>"Rock, paper, scissors, shoot!" You have defeated {0} with your scissors and took their role in the kitchen!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThiefToMason">
<!-- 0 - old mason's name -->
<!-- 1 - new mason's name -->
    <value>{0} lost a game of Janken to the Busser 🍽(😈) {1} so that {0} is no longer a Sashimi Chef while {1} became one!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThiefTransformToMason">
<!-- 0 - mason colleagues' names -->
    <value>The other Sashimi Chefs (if any) are: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThiefToCult">
<!-- 0 - old cultist's name -->
<!-- 1 - new cultist's name -->
    <value>{0} lost a game of "rock, paper, scissors" to the Busser 🍽(😈) {1} so that {0} is no longer a Vegan Chef while {1} became one!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThiefToWolf">
<!-- 0 - old wolf's name -->
<!-- 1 - new wolf's name -->
    <value>{0} lost a game of "rock, paper, scissors" to the Busser 🍽(😈) {1} so that {0} is no longer a Talent Poacher while {1} became one!</value>
  </string>
  <string deprecated="true" key="ThiefTransformNewTeammates">
<!-- 0 - teammates' names -->
    <value>Your new teammates (if any) are: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThiefEnd">
<!-- 0 - Thief's name -->
    <value>What happened? {0} finds themselves having to clean tables for an eternity because everyone in the restaurant has left. There is no one to pass this dirty job to 🍽(😈)!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThiefStealChosen">
<!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>You have chosen to play a game of "rock, paper, scissors" with {0}.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskThief">
    <value>Who do you want to play "rock, paper, scissors" with today?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SecretLynchResultEach">
<!-- 0 - Number of votes -->
<!-- 1 - Player got lynched -->
<!-- 2 - A list of players who voted {1} -->
    <value>{0} votes went to {1}: {2}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SecretLynchResultFull">
<!-- 0 - A list of "SecretLynchResultEach" or "SecretLynchResultNumber" -->
    <value>The vote result for today:\n{0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SecretLynchResultNumber">
<!-- 0 - Number of votes -->
<!-- 1 - Player got lynched -->
    <value>{0} votes went to {1}.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SecretLynchShowVotes">
    <value>Secret: Votes Count</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SecretLynchShowVotesQ">
    <value>When secret vote is turned on, show the vote count at the end of the voting?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SecretLynchShowVotesA">
    <value>When secret vote is turned on, the vote count at the end of the vote will: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SecretLynchShowVoters">
    <value>Secret: Voters</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SecretLynchShowVotersQ">
    <value>When secret vote is turned on and the vote count is showing, show the voter's name for every voted player?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SecretLynchShowVotersA">
    <value>When secret vote is turned on and the vote count is showing, the voter's name for every voted player will: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultistBitten">
<!-- {0} - Cultist that was bitten by the Alpha Wolf -->
    <value>You realized that {0} returned their Vegan Chef uniform and got a new one. Did they transfer to another line?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Peace">
<!-- Used for Pacifist's button -->
    <value>Reveal your Treats!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="LynchPeaceTimeout">
<!-- Used in PM if the pacifist uses his ability during lynch phase -->
    <value>Everyone was too busy enjoying the treats prepared by the Pastry Chef 🍨(☮️) that they forgot to count the votes! No one gets fired in that case...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThiefStoleYourRoleThief">
    <value>Someone played a game of "rock, paper, scissors" with you today and you lost! You gave them your original role and you are now the Busser 🍽(😈), responsible for clearing and setting guest tables after each customer has finished their meal. No one really likes to take this job so the owner has decided that there is no official job position for it and the duty shall be rotated among the staff. Every day, you can ask a staff to replace you as the Busser with a game of rock-paper-scissors. If you win, you would take their role in the kitchen while they would become the new Busser and continue playing rock-paper-scissors with other staff to pass on this mundane job.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThiefStoleYourRoleVillager">
    <value>Someone played a game of "rock, paper, scissors" with you today and you lost! You gave them your original role and you are now just a Line Cook 🧑‍🍳(👱) (with some part-time bussing duties!).</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SerialKillerKilledYou">
    <value>You were just doing your job when you realised your hands and arm started puffing up... very soon you fainted and were rushed to the hospital because of a severe allergic reaction.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThiefTeamEnd">
    <value>Busser Team</value>
  </string>
  <string key="StealKiller">
    <value>You tried to play "rock, paper, scissors" with a dubious chef. You played rock while they played paper. As you sighed at your defeat, they grabbed your fist and shook it up and down. Minutes later, you started to feel light-headed and a shortness of breath...you were soon rushed to the hospital due to a severe allergic reaction ☠️(🔪)!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThiefStoleKiller">
<!-- used when Thief steals SK -->
    <value>The Busser 🍽(😈), {0}, was just trying to pass their mundane job to one of the chefs in the kitchen. They were later found unconscious on the floor with foam in their mouth, still having their tea towels tied to their apron... they were soon rushed to hospital for having a severe allergic reaction ☠️(🔪).</value>
  </string>
  <string key="BeholderSeerStolen">
<!-- New roles 28.12.2018 -->
    <value>{1} is no longer the Executive Chef 🥖(👳) because they have swapped roles with {0}, who was the Busser 🍽(😈). You will work closely with {0} to plan the daily menu from now on!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Troublemaker">
    <value>the Maître D' 🤯</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutTroublemaker">
    <value>You are the Maître D' 🤯. You collect all complaints from angry customers. You may choose to report all these complaints at any evening meeting to top management, after which they will be enraged and decide to fire two people at the end of that day.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoTroublemaker">
    <value>You are the Maître D' 🤯. As the head waiter, you are in charge of the dining room and will inform the top chefs if anything is going wrong. The service quality of the restaurant has been in decline ever since the Talent Poachers infiltrated the restaurant, and each day you receive many complaints which you collect in a booklet. You may choose to report all these complaints at any evening meeting to top management, after which they will be enraged and decide to fire two people at the end of that day.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskTroublemaker">
    <value>Do you want to report all customer complaints to top management today?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="TroublemakerDoubleLynch">
    <value>{0}, the Maître D' 🤯 just summarised all 126 complaints they have received over the last week to management, and the managers are very angry! Two people shall be fired today!!!</value>
    <value>{0}, the Maître D' 🤯 just summarised all 612 complaints they have received over the last week to management, and the managers are super duper angry! Two people shall be fired today!!!</value>
    <value>{0}, the Maître D' 🤯 just summarised all 621 complaints they have received over the last week to management, and the managers are incredibly angry! Two people shall be fired today!!!</value>
    <value>{0}, the Maître D' 🤯 just summarised all 6 complaints they have received over the last week to management, and the managers are not happy! Two people shall be fired today!!!</value>
    <value>{0}, the Maître D' 🤯 just summarised all 621,261 complaints they have received over the last week to management, and the managers' blood is boiling as hot as the sun! Two people shall be fired today!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="TroubleDoubleLynchNow">
    <value>The management is very angry today so another person shall be fired!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Chemist">
    <value>the Molecular Gastronomer 🧊(👨‍🔬)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutChemist">
    <value>You are the Molecular Gastronomer 🧊(👨‍🔬)! You serve up futuristic food for the VIP customers once every two days, so you can spend every other day inventing new dishes. After a dish is made, you can present your experimental dish to any staff member for a taste-test. Once they taste your dish, they will be so inspired that they immediately resign to go learn molecular gastronomy back at culinary school. If they refuse to taste your dish, your heart (made of glass) will shatter and you will resign to open your own molecular gastronomy lab elsewhere!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoChemist">
    <value>You are the Molecular Gastronomer 🧊(👨‍🔬)! You serve up futuristic food for the VIP customers once every two days, so you can spend every other day inventing new dishes. After a dish is made, you can present your experimental dish to any staff member for a taste-test. Once they taste your dish, they will be so inspired that they immediately resign to go learn molecular gastronomy back at culinary school. If they refuse to taste your dish, your heart (made of glass) will shatter and you will resign to open your own molecular gastronomy lab elsewhere!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ChemistBrewing">
    <value>You are off-duty today so you will spend the whole day inventing a new experimental dish... Einstein mode - activate!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskChemist">
    <value>Finally, your experimental dish is ready - who do you want to invite to taste-test your food?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ChemistTargetDead">
    <value>You plated your dish and covered it with a mysterious smoke cloche. As you were about to carry the dish to let {0} taste it, you learnt that they had just left the restaurant! Feeling disappointed, you returned to your station with your pretty dish.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ChemistVisitYouSK">
    <value>The Molecular Gastronomer 🧊(👨‍🔬) {0} invited you to taste their newest invention, but you had a better treat for them! You poured a little bit of your allergen into a spoon and shoved it in their mouth. They were initially fascinated by the taste of what you gave them... but very soon, their nose started bleeding and you feel blessed to hear the sound of them whimpering and suffering as they slowly fainted on the floor... MUAHAHAHA</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ChemistSK">
    <value>You tried to invite {0} to taste your newest invention, but they had also prepared something for you to try! It looks like a bit of green "fairy powder" on a spoon! As you tasted the powder, you feel a "spicy" sensation in your nose, and soon started bleeding and spasming... the last thing you remember was getting rushed to the hospital with the medics saying "allergic, allergic, allergic..." ☠️(🔪)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ChemistSKPublic">
    <value>The Molecular Gastronomy 🧊(👨🔬) {0} was just inviting someone to try their newest invention... but they fell on the floor and started bleeding from their nose instead!? They were immediately rushed to the hospital due to what seems to be an allergic reaction ☠️(🔪). Maybe the smoke from their smoke cloche got to them...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ChemistVisitYouSuccess">
    <value>You had the chance to taste the Molecular Gastronomer's 🧊(👨‍🔬) latest creation today. They left their experimental dish on your station and you thoroughly enjoyed the taste, mouthfeel, aroma - everything presented to you! You were so inspired that you decided to quit your job and return to culinary school to learn molecular gastronomy!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ChemistSuccess">
    <value>You left your latest creation at {0}'s station and came back an hour later to see that they savoured every bit of it! Someone even said they quit their job to learn molecular gastronomy at culinary school. It feels so good to have your fellow cooks validate your work. You shall invent something new tomorrow and get more recognition within this kitchen!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ChemistSuccessPublic">
<!-- {0} - Chemist's victim -->
<!-- {1} - Will be replaced by "(victim) was (role)" -->
<!-- {0} - Chemist's victim -->
<!-- {1} - Will be replaced by "(victim) was (role)" -->
    <value>{0} had the chance to taste the Molecular Gastronomer's 🧊(👨‍🔬) spherified olive oil today. They were so fascinated that they decided to quit their job and return to culinary school to learn molecular gastronomy! {1}</value>
    <value>{0} had the chance to taste the Molecular Gastronomer's 🧊(👨‍🔬) smoked pandan mousse today. They were so fascinated that they decided to quit their job and return to culinary school to learn molecular gastronomy! {1}</value>
    <value>{0} had the chance to taste the Molecular Gastronomer's 🧊(👨‍🔬) deconstructed coquilles saint jacques today. They were so fascinated that they decided to quit their job and return to culinary school to learn molecular gastronomy! {1}</value>
    <value>{0} had the chance to taste the Molecular Gastronomer's 🧊(👨‍🔬) iridescent apple pie today. They were so fascinated that they decided to quit their job and return to culinary school to learn molecular gastronomy! {1}</value>
    <value>{0} had the chance to taste the Molecular Gastronomer's 🧊(👨‍🔬) "fairy dust" freeze-dried berry crystals today. They were so fascinated that they decided to quit their job and return to culinary school to learn molecular gastronomy! {1}</value>
    <value>{0} had the chance to taste the Molecular Gastronomer's 🧊(👨‍🔬) soy sauce and yuzu ice cream today. They were so fascinated that they decided to quit their job and return to culinary school to learn molecular gastronomy! {1}</value>
    <value>{0} had the chance to taste the Molecular Gastronomer's 🧊(👨‍🔬) spherified red-wine bánh bèo today. They were so fascinated that they decided to quit their job and return to culinary school to learn molecular gastronomy! {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ChemistVisitYouFail">
    <value>You had the chance to taste the Molecular Gastronomer 🧊(👨‍🔬) {0}'s  latest creation today. They left their experimental dish on your station but you were a bit busy so you didn't try it in the end. Something tells you that won't get the chance to taste something that "haute cuisine" again...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ChemistFail">
    <value>You left your latest creation at {0}'s station and came back an hour later to see the dish was thrown to the trash! Are these people out of their minds? Can't they recognise art when they see one? In your rage, you decided to resign from the restaurant and open your private molecular gastronomy tasting lab elsewhere... some place where real foodies would come try your food.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ChemistFailPublic">
    <value>The Molecular Gastronomer 🧊(👨‍🔬) {0} invited a staff to taste their experimental dish, but was shocked to find the dish in the trash an hour later! Their heart shattered into a million pieces and with great resolute, they have resigned from the restaurant to open their own molecular gastronomy lab elsewhere 😢😢.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ChemistTargetEmpty">
    <value>You left your latest creation at {0}'s station, but very soon a chef came to tell you that {0} is not at their station right now. You wonder where they aren't and take the dish back so as to not waste it.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultistsList">
    <value>The Vegan Chefs are: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SnowWolf">
    <value>the Order Sabotager 🌶(🐺☃️)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoSnowWolf">
    <value>You are the Order Sabotager 🌶(🐺☃️). You work with the Talent Poachers 🍔(🐺) to recruit staff to join the competitor's restaurant. Instead of doing the talking, your role is to distract one staff member every day by tampering with the orders (in the computer system) assigned to them. They will be confused why their customer ordered 10 portions instead of 1, but will proceed to fulfill the order anyways. This will keep them busy for a while so that they cannot focus on their side tasks during the day!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutSnowWolf">
    <value>You are the Order Sabotager 🌶(🐺☃️). You can choose one staff member every day to distract by tampering with the orders (in the computer system) assigned to them. This will keep them busy for a while so that they cannot focus on their side tasks during the day! You cannot mess with the same staff on two consecutive days, because they would then realise the problem and report it to the restaurant owner!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskFreeze">
    <value>Whose orders do you want to tamper with today?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolfPackList">
    <value>The Talent Poachers 🍔(🐺) consists of {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolfPackSnowList">
    <value>The Talent Poachers 🍔(🐺) consists of {0} and the Order Sabotager 🌶(🐺☃️) {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGTransformToAlphaWithSnow">
    <value>Because {0} has left the restaurant, you were assigned to replace them. On the way to work, the boss of the competitor's restaurant came to tell you that {0} was actually the Manager of the Competitor's Restaurant 🍟(⚡️), who is working undercover together with the Talent Poachers 🍔(🐺) {1} and the Order Sabotager 🌶(🐺☃️) {2}. You feel like you have hit the jackpot and willingly take up your new, high-paying job!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGTransformToWolfCubWithSnow">
    <value>Because {0} has left the restaurant, you were assigned to replace them. On the way to work, one of the staff from the competitor's restaurant came to tell you that {0} was actually the Food Destroyer 🦴(🐶), working next to the Talent Poachers 🍔(🐺) {1} and the Order Sabotager 🌶(🐺☃️) {2}. You are working for the competitor now!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGTransformToWolfWithSnow">
    <value>Because {0} has left the restaurant, you were assigned to replace them. On the way to work, one of the staff from the competitor's restaurant came to tell you that {0} was actually a Talent Poacher 🍔(🐺), working next to the other Talent Poachers 🍔(🐺) {1} and the Order Sabotager 🌶(🐺☃️) {2}. You are working for the competitor now!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGTransformToLycanWithSnow">
    <value>Because {0} has left the restaurant, you were assigned to replace them. On the way to work, one of the staff from the competitor's restaurant came to tell you that {0} was actually the Line Sabotager 🍩(🐺🌝), working next to the Talent Poachers 🍔(🐺) {1} and the Order Sabotager 🌶(🐺☃️){2}. You are working for the competitor now!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGTransformToSnowWolf">
    <value>Because {0} has left the restaurant, you were assigned to replace them. On the way to work, one of the staff from the competitor's restaurant came to tell you that {0} was actually the Order Sabotager 🌶(🐺☃️) , working next to the Talent Poachers 🍔(🐺){1}. You are working for the competitor now!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGToSnowWolf">
    <value>The Management Trainee 🙇(🎭) {0} has taken up the position as the new Order Sabotager 🌶(🐺☃️)!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WildChildSnowTransform">
    <value>You cannot believe that your mentor, {0} has left the restaurant! Feeling disappointed, you walked across the street to the competitor's restaurant and applied to be their Talent Poacher 🍔(🐺), hoping that you can learn from a few of the chefs that you help recruit through your new job. The other Talent Poachers are: {1} and the Order Sabotager 🌶(🐺☃️) {2}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThiefToSnowWolf">
    <value>{0} lost a game of "rock, paper, scissors" to the Busser 🍽(😈) {1} so that {0} is no longer the Order Sabotager 🌶(🐺☃️) while {1} became one!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotFrozen">
    <value>You were about to invite someone for some chit-chat when the Maître D' came to ask why you didn't deliver the 15 mushroom soups that Table 13 ordered. You feel utterly confused as you remember already delivering a bowl of that soup to the table 5 minutes ago... did someone sabotage the orders 🌶(🐺☃️)? Anyways, you scurried to deliver the orders and forgot about the chit-chat.</value>
    <value>You were about to invite someone for some chit-chat when the Maître D' came to ask why you didn't deliver the 30 cream puffs that Table 46 ordered. You feel utterly confused as you remember already delivering a dozen of cream puffs to the table 5 minutes ago... did someone sabotage the orders 🌶(🐺☃️)? Anyways, you scurried to deliver the orders and forgot about the chit-chat.</value>
    <value>You were about to invite someone for some chit-chat when the Maître D' came to ask why you didn't deliver the 20 napkins that Table 7 ordered. You feel utterly confused as you remember already delivering several napkins to the table 5 minutes ago... did someone sabotage the orders 🌶(🐺☃️)️? Anyways, you scurried to deliver the orders and forgot about the chit-chat.</value>
    <value>You were about to invite someone for some chit-chat when the Maître D' came to ask why you didn't deliver the 86 caesar salads that Table 70 ordered. You feel utterly confused as you remember already delivering a bowl of that salad to the table 5 minutes ago... did someone sabotage the orders 🌶(🐺☃️)? Anyways, you scurried to deliver the orders and forgot about the chit-chat.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ChemistFrozen">
    <value>You were very excited to present your newest creation, but were cut short when suddenly, the Sous Chef came to ask you about the 10 liquid nitrogen ice cream orders that are on hold. That's funny, this dish is supposed to be served on weekends only... did someone sabotage the orders 🌶(🐺☃️)? Anyways, you scurry to the storage room to pick up some liquid nitrogen and make the dish from scratch, leaving behind your experimental dish for another day.</value>
    <value>You were very excited to present your newest creation, but were cut short when suddenly, the Sous Chef came to ask you about the 4 two-dimensional linguine orders that are on hold. That's funny, this dish is supposed to be served on Valentines' Day only... did someone sabotage the orders 🌶(🐺☃️)? Anyways, you scurry to the storage room to pick up some flour and make the dish from scratch, leaving behind your experimental dish for another day.</value>
    <value>You were very excited to present your newest creation, but were cut short when suddenly, the Sous Chef came to ask you about the 5 deconstructed fritto misto orders that are on hold. That's funny, this dish is supposed to be served during Autumn only... did someone sabotage the orders 🌶(🐺☃️)? Anyways, you scurry to the storage room to pick up some frozen seafood and make the dish from scratch, leaving behind your experimental dish for another day.</value>
    <value>You were very excited to present your newest creation, but were cut short when suddenly, the Sous Chef came to ask you about the 69 wasabi cube orders that are on hold. That's funny, this dish is supposed to be served in Weddings only... did someone sabotage the orders 🌶(🐺☃️)? Anyways, you scurry to the storage room to pick up some wasabi powder and make the dish from scratch, leaving behind your experimental dish for another day.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultistFrozen">
    <value>You were about to follow the other Vegan Chefs to inspire a chef when the Server came to ask why you when the 40 vegan onsen eggs that Table 42 ordered are ready. You feel utterly confused as you remember already finishing 10 of these eggs for the exact same table... did someone sabotage the orders 🌶(🐺☃️)? Anyways, you scurry to recreate the eggs while the other Vegan Chefs went ahead to share their hearty lunchbox.</value>
    <value>You were about to follow the other Vegan Chefs to inspire a chef when the Server came to ask why you when the 23 macaroni and peas that Table 76 ordered are ready. You feel utterly confused as you remember already finishing 6 of those baked macaronis for the exact same table... did someone sabotage the orders 🌶(🐺☃️)? Anyways, you scurry to recreate the baked dishes while the other Vegan Chefs went ahead to share their hearty lunchbox.</value>
    <value>You were about to follow the other Vegan Chefs to inspire a chef when the Server came to ask why you when the big vegetarian sashimi platter that Table 2, Table 5 and Table 19 ordered are ready. You feel utterly confused as you don't even remember receiving these orders... did someone sabotage the orders 🌶(🐺☃️)? Anyways, you panicked and started to assemble the big platters while the other Vegan Chefs went ahead to share their hearty lunchbox.</value>
    <value>You were about to follow the other Vegan Chefs to inspire a chef when the Server came to ask why you when the 3 grateful goddess lotus root dish that Table 33 ordered are ready. You feel utterly confused as you thought the Executive Chef removed this dish from the menu since last week... did someone sabotage the orders 🌶(🐺☃️)? Anyways, you took a deep breath and started to assemble the lotus-root goddess statues while the other Vegan Chefs went ahead to share their hearty lunchbox.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CHFrozen">
    <value>You were about to check someone's lunchbox when one of the Line Cooks came to ask you for 12 more baby-back ribs. Apparently, they have received 12 orders over the last minute and they are out of stock... did someone sabotage the orders 🌶(🐺☃️)? Anyways, you scurry to the storage room to fetch some ribs for butchering, and soon you forgot about what you wanted to do before...</value>
    <value>You were about to check someone's lunchbox when one of the Line Cooks came to ask you for 90 more squabs. Apparently, they have received 100 orders over the last minute and they are out of stock... did someone sabotage the orders 🌶(🐺☃️)? Anyways, you scurry to the storage room to fetch some squabs for prepping and soon you forgot about what you wanted to do before...</value>
    <value>You were about to check someone's lunchbox when one of the Line Cooks came to ask you for 45 more chicken thighs. Apparently, they have received 60 orders over the last minute and they are out of stock... did someone sabotage the orders 🌶(🐺☃️)? Anyways, you scurry to the storage room to fetch some spring chicken for butchering and soon you forgot about what you wanted to do before...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SeeingFrozen">
<!-- used for seer, fool, oracle and sorcerer -->
    <value>You were about to choose a staff when the Senior Chef came to tell you that there are 4 tables waiting for you to present today's signature dessert. Huh? Since when was that part of your job? And why would there be so many orders anyways... did someone sabotage the orders 🌶(🐺☃️)? Anyways, you rushed into the kitchen to supervise the chefs making this dessert and had no time left to do what you were doing.</value>
    <value>You were about to choose a staff when the Senior Chef came to tell you that there are 16 tables waiting for you to present today's steak au poivre. Huh? Since when was that part of your job? And why would there be so many orders anyways... did someone sabotage the orders 🌶(🐺☃️)? Anyways, you rushed into the kitchen to supervise the chefs making this main dish and had no time left to do what you were doing.</value>
    <value>You were about to choose a staff when the Senior Chef came to tell you that there are 20 VIP tables waiting for you to introduce today's menu. Huh? Since when was that part of your job? And why would there be so many orders anyways... did someone sabotage the orders 🌶(🐺☃️)? Anyways, you rushed into the dining room to work with the Host to introduce the menu, with no time left afterwards to do what you were doing.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GAFrozen">
    <value>As you were about to teach a staff a lesson about safety, the Bartender stops you to let you know that some Line Cooks have taken 10 bottles of rum because there are 40 new baked alaska orders that need to be flambéed. You are left dumbstruck, thinking how there could be so many of those orders... did someone sabotage the orders 🌶(🐺☃️)? Nevertheless, you stopped what you were doing and went with the Bartender to supervise those cooks as they light the baked alaskas on fire.</value>
    <value>As you were about to teach a staff a lesson about safety, the Bartender stops you to let you know that some Line Cooks have taken 10 bottles of Grand Marnier because there are 30 new Crêpes Suzette orders that need to be flambéed. You are left dumbstruck, thinking how there could be so many of those orders... did someone sabotage the orders 🌶(🐺☃️)? Nevertheless, you stopped what you were doing and went with the Bartender to supervise those cooks as they light the Crêpes Suzettes on fire.</value>
    <value>As you were about to teach a staff a lesson about safety, the Bartender stops you to let you know that some Line Cooks have taken 10 bottles of rum because there are 40 new Gundel Palacsinta orders that need to be flambéed. You are left dumbstruck, thinking how there could be so many of those orders... did someone sabotage the orders 🌶(🐺☃️)? Nevertheless, you stopped what you were doing and went with the Bartender to supervise those cooks as they light the Gundel Palacsintas on fire.</value>
    <value>As you were about to teach a staff a lesson about safety, the Bartender stops you to let you know that some Line Cooks have taken 10 bottles of brandy because there are 50 new cherries jubilee orders that need to be flambéed. You are left dumbstruck, thinking how there could be so many of those orders... did someone sabotage the orders 🌶(🐺☃️)? Nevertheless, you stopped what you were doing and went with the Bartender to supervise those cooks as they light the cherries jubilee on fire.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SKFrozen">
    <value>You were just about to leave some allergens on someone's station when a Line Cook stopped you and asked you to help with chopping up 100 jackfruits..... why would they need so much jackfruit? Did someone place 100 orders in the last minute or something 🌶(🐺☃️)? You abandoned your devious plans and got to work before someone noticed your dirty plan.</value>
    <value>You were just about to leave some allergens on someone's station when a Line Cook stopped you and asked you to help with slicing up 300 baguettes..... why would they need so much baguette? Did someone place 300 orders in the last minute or something 🌶(🐺☃️)? You abandoned your devious plans and got to work before someone noticed your dirty plan.</value>
    <value>You were just about to leave some allergens on someone's station when a Line Cook stopped you and asked you to help with chopping up 50 onions..... why would they need so much onions? Did someone place 50 orders in the last minute or something 🌶(🐺☃️)? You abandoned your devious plans and got to work before someone noticed your dirty plan.</value>
    <value>You were just about to leave some allergens on someone's station when a Line Cook stopped you and asked you to help with washing up 600 tomatoes..... why would they need so many tomatoes? Did someone place 100 orders in the last minute or something 🌶(🐺☃️)? You abandoned your devious plans and got to work before someone noticed your dirty plan.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThiefFrozen">
    <value>You were about to ask someone to take your position when the Server asked you to go clean the 25 uncleaned tables in the dining room! You go out and see that on each table is a clean tablecloth and a glass of half-full water... what happened, did the waiters put them there on purpose or did they get some fake orders 🌶(🐺☃️)? You hurried to clean them up before the owner notices, and soon forgot what you were planning to do before.</value>
    <value>You were about to ask someone to take your position when the Server asked you to go clean the 15 uncleaned tables in the dining room! You go out and see that on each table is a clean tablecloth and a plate of bread... what happened, did the waiters put them there on purpose or did they get some fake orders 🌶(🐺☃️)? You hurried to clean them up before the owner notices, and soon forgot what you were planning to do before.</value>
    <value>You were about to ask someone to take your position when the Server asked you to go clean the 19 uncleaned tables in the dining room! You go out and see that on each table is a clean tablecloth and a glass of watermelon amuse-bouche... what happened, did the waiters put them there on purpose or did they get some fake orders 🌶(🐺☃️)? You hurried to clean them up before the owner notices, and soon forgot what you were planning to do before.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DefaultFrozen">
<!-- used for all roles without (every-)night action -->
<!-- used for all roles without (every-)night action -->
    <value>You worked really hard today because there were a lot more orders than usual... It almost felt like someone had placed these as fake orders 🌶(🐺☃️) to keep you busy.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardBlockedSnowWolf">
    <value>You tampered with the orders assigned to {0} and chuckled. However, soon after you walked away, you noticed the Safety Supervisor ⚠️(👼) go to the order system and reassign all those fake orders you gave {0} to another chef! What are they doing? Maybe they thought {0} needed to have less tasks and pay more attention towards their safety...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SuccessfulFreeze">
    <value>You tampered with the orders assigned to {0} and chuckled. This would keep them busy for the day!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SnowFrozeKiller">
    <value>The Order Sabotager 🌶(🐺☃️) {0} tried to tamper with someone's orders again. The chef that was messed with was smart though and seems to have gotten "revenge". The staff walked into the common room to find {0} trembling on the floor with foam in their mouth. They were soon sent to the hospital for having an acute allergic reaction ☠️(🔪).</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SnowWolfTurnWolf">
    <value>All the fellow Talent Poachers have left the restaurant! You are the last resort option for the competitor and therefore you were promoted to be a Talent Poacher 🍔(🐺). Every day, you can persuade someone in the kitchen to join the competitor's restaurant.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SnowFrozeHunter">
<!-- 0 - target's name -->
<!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>The Order Sabotager 🌶(🐺☃️) {0} tried to give a chef 89 more dishes to prepare through the order system. However, they were actually the Food Critic 🖋(🎯), who was smart enough to see that someone tampered with the orders and asked the security officers to check CCTV footage. {0} was exposed for their work and immediately fired by the restaurant owner!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Lang">
    <value>Change Language</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Mode">
    <value>Change Restaurant Mode</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MaxPlayer">
    <value>Set Max Staff Number</value>
  </string>
  <string key="EndRoles">
    <value>Show Roles At Game End</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MaxExtend">
    <value>Set Max Extend Time</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DayTimer">
    <value>Set Evening Meeting Timer</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NightTimer">
    <value>Set Day Timer</value>
  </string>
  <string key="LynchTimer">
    <value>Set Voting Timer</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleConfig">
    <value>Role Configuration</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Mechanics">
    <value>Game Mechanics</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GroupSettings">
    <value>Group Settings</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Timers">
    <value>Game Timers</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Done">
    <value>Done!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Back">
    <value>Back</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShufflePlayerList">
    <value>Shuffle Staff List</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShufflePlayerListQ">
    <value>Shuffle staff list every time? Current: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShufflePlayerListA">
    <value>Staff list will be shuffled every time: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutGraveDigger">
    <value>You are the HR Manager 😠(☠️). You do exit interviews and referrals in the back-room of the office. Chefs cannot find you during the day, but if they tried, you may hear them and punish them for slacking off or being suspicious. If you had to interview more people, the staff (and spies) are more likely to find you. If no one left the previous day, you would be in the kitchen helping out the Expeditor and everyone can find you.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoGraveDigger">
    <value>You are the HR Manager 😠(☠️). When someone leaves the restaurant, you have to do an exit interview with them and try to refer them to a job in another branch(no talent goes to waste!). You do this in the back-room of the office so most chefs cannot find you during the day. If they tried to find you, you may hear their footsteps and punish them for slacking off or being suspicious. If you had to interview more people, the staff (and spies) are more likely to find you. If no one left the previous day, you would be in the kitchen helping out the Expeditor and everyone can find you.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GraveDigger">
    <value>the HR Manager 😠(☠️)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DigNoGraves">
<!--{0}: list of people who died since last grave-->
<!--{0}: list of people who died since last grave-->
    <value>No one left the restaurant yesterday, so you decided to help out in the kitchen today by assisting the Expeditor to organise the orders. Let's hustle!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DigGraves">
    <value>Today, you conducted the exit interview with {0}. Hopefully they will get back to you soon whether or not they are interested in those jobs available in the branch restaurants!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GraveDiggerFrozen">
<!--{0}: grave digger-->
<!--{0}: grave digger-->
    <value>The Expeditor came running into your office and begged for you to help them. Apparently, there were 500 orders placed in the last hour and they cannot handle it alone anymore. Where are all these orders coming from 🌶(🐺☃️)? Wasting no time, you postponed the exit interviews (if any) and went into the kitchen to help. Let's hustle!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GraveDiggerNotHome">
<!--{0}: grave digger, {1}: wolf who fell into the grave-->
<!--{0}: grave digger, {1}: wolf who fell into the grave-->
    <value>The Talent Poachers tried hard to find {0}, but they were nowhere to be found in the kitchen or the back-alley! Do you suppose they were hiding in that secret back-room in the office?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolfFellWolves">
<!--{0}: the wolf who fell into the grave-->
<!--{0}: the wolf who fell into the grave-->
    <value>The Talent Poachers have found where {0} is! They were in the secret back-room of the office. The door was left open, perhaps because {0} went for a quick toilet break. {1} took a peek at {0}'s idle computer screen, gasped loudly and immediately fled the restaurant. What was that for? Did they see an irresistible job offer or something 😠(☠️)?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolfFell">
<!--{0}: grave digger-->
<!--{0}: grave digger-->
    <value>It was a busy day today and you spent an hour around lunchtime to slack-off in the toilet (no one will suspect the HR manager for slacking off!). You returned to your secret back-room and soon got a message from {0}. Not only did they submit their resignation, they also submitted their CV to apply for one of the jobs in a branch restaurant... Mmm, you wonder how they learnt about that job before their exit interview.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="KillerStumbled">
<!--{0}: intended victim, {1}: actual victim-->
<!--{0}: intended victim, {1}: actual victim-->
    <value>It took you a while to find {0}'s station, but once you arrived at their secretive office, you gave them a firm handshake and the job was done - they soon fainted and started foaming on the floor. A minute later, you were shocked to realise that {0} was the HR manager 😠(☠️)! You had to check with them every day where a staff was stationed to do your devious job. Now that you've caused an allergic reaction on them, who are you going to check with tomorrow?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="KillerRandomKill">
<!--{0}: victim-->
<!--{0}: victim-->
    <value>You wanted to leave some allergens on {0}'s station, but with the HR Manager 😠(☠️) gone, you have no one to check with to see where their station is. Whatever..... you went to one of the stations in front of you (which seems to be {1}'s station) and left some of your allergic powder there. It's going to be {1}'s lucky day!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardBlockedRandomKiller">
<!--{0}: grave digger-->
<!--{0}: grave digger-->
    <value>You went to {0}'s station and left some of your allergic powder there. A minute later, you saw the Safety Supervisor ⚠️(👼) walk in to clean their station. What are they doing!!! You just wasted today's portion of allergic powder...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterFell">
<!--{0}: cult hunter-->
<!--{0}: cult hunter-->
    <value>You tried to check {0}'s lunchbox but was very soon caught by them. They were the HR Manager 😠(☠️)! You are in so much trouble. You have no words to explain what you were doing and they decided that you should be fired.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterFellDigger">
<!--{0}: cultist-->
<!--{0}: cultist-->
    <value>It was lunchtime and you were about to reheat your lunchbox when you caught {0} taking a peek into it. You suspect that they were one of those pesky spies and confronted them. They were at a loss of words... so busted! You immediately went to tell the restaurant owner that {0} should be fired &gt;:)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultFell">
<!--{0}: cultist who fell, {1}: grave digger-->
<!--{0}: cultist who fell, {1}: grave digger-->
    <value>Seems {0} tried to visit your office while you were on a toilet break. You came back to find a memo next to your notebook - seems {0} was very interested in that job position in the branch restaurant that you had on the browser of your computer. The memo also said that they would soon submit their resignation letter...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultConvertGraveDigger">
<!--{0}: grave digger-->
<!--{0}: grave digger-->
    <value>You and {0} tried to inspire {1} to try your vegan lunchbox 🥑(👤) today. After some searching, you found {1}'s secretive room at the back of the office. {0} took a peek at {1}'s idle computer screen, gasped loudly, left a memo on their desk and immediately fled the restaurant. What was that for? Did they see an irresistible job offer or something 😠(☠️)?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ChemistFell">
<!--{0}: chemist-->
<!--{0}: chemist-->
    <value>You tried to share your experimental dish with {0}, but as you arrived at the door of their office, you realised that {0} was actually the HR Manager 😠(☠️)! You left in a hurry to your station, but an hour later you were approached by the restaurant owner saying you were FIRED! Maybe the HR Manager heard your footsteps and the sound of your plate and thought you were the one trying to incite allergies around the kitchen!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ChemistFellDigger">
<!--{0}: grave digger-->
<!--{0}: grave digger-->
    <value>{0} tried to share some "food" with you while you were working inside your room. You heard them stop at the door and then hurry back into the kitchen. Did they forget that you have ultrasensitive ears? You opened the door to confirm that it was {0}, and then carefully cleaned the door-knobs in case they were the ones leaving deadly allergens around the kitchen. Afterwards you reported the case to the restaurant owner to have them FIRED! Better luck next time, spy!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotFell">
<!--{0}: harlot-->
<!--{0}: harlot-->
    <value>You went into the office to find {0}'s secretive back room. Just as you were able to knock on the door, you realised they were the HR Manager 😠(☠️), and you cannot be caught slacking off! So you hurried back into the dining room. Sadly, it seems you have been caught by {0}'s sensitive ears, as you were soon approached by the restaurant owner who said you were FIRED!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotFellDigger">
<!--{0}: grave digger-->
<!--{0}: grave digger-->
    <value>You heard some giggles outside of your room today so you went to take a peek. The last thing you saw was {0} running back to the dining room. Are they one of those spies who helped the competitor poach all our talented chefs? You immediately reported the case to the restaurant owner and suggested to have {0} FIRED!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotVisitDigger">
<!--{0}: grave digger-->
<!--{0}: grave digger-->
    <value>You went into the office to find {0}'s secretive back room. Just as you were able to knock on the door, you realised they were the HR Manager 😠(☠️), and you cannot be caught slacking off! Using your smooth maneuvering skills, you tip-toed back into the dining room without getting discovered.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GAFell">
<!--{0}: guardian angel-->
<!--{0}: guardian angel-->
    <value>You tried to finish your job early today by following {0} to their station and planning to give them a talking as soon as they do something unsafe. However, you followed {0} into the secretive back room of the office and that is when you realised they were the HR Manager 😠(☠️)! You hurried back into the kitchen, trying not to be discovered by them. Sadly, it seems you have been caught by {0}'s sensitive ears, as you were soon approached by the restaurant owner, who said you are FIRED!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GAFellDigger">
<!--{0}: grave digger-->
<!--{0}: grave digger-->
    <value>Your sensitive ears helped you again as you heard some nervous breathing outside your room this morning. As you creaked open the door, you saw {0} running back to the kitchen. Are they one of those spies who helped the competitor poach all our talented chefs? You immediately reported the case to the restaurant owner and suggested to have {0} FIRED!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThiefFell">
<!--{0}: thief-->
<!--{0}: thief-->
    <value>You found {0} outside the toilet today and asked them for a game of "rock, paper, scissors". Instead, they asked you to follow them... into the secretive back room of the office. Shit! They were the HR Manager 😠(☠️)! Since you were discovered trying to pass your mundane job to someone else, you know that you will be fired very soon... (*sobs*)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThiefFellDigger">
<!--{0}: grave digger-->
<!--{0}: grave digger-->
    <value>A funny thing happened today as {0} caught you during one of your long toilet breaks and even asked to play a game of "rock, paper, scissors" with you. First, they seem to be slacking off with these stupid games. Second, they caught you when you were having your own slack-off session! You made sure that they won't tell anyone about this by immediately reporting to the restaurant owner that {0} was one of the spies. Hopefully they would agree to have {0} fired! Haha!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ArsonistFell">
<!--{0}: arsonist-->
<!--{0}: arsonist-->
    <value>As you went into their room to tinker with their computer, you noticed the HR Manager 😠(☠️) standing at the door of the room with another chef. They were just about to start an exit interview when they caught you red-handed! You are soon going to be fired not only from this restaurant but from the whole culinary world!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ArsonistFellDigger">
<!--{0}: person that died, {1}: "(person) was (role)"-->
<!--{0}: person that died, {1}: "(person) was (role)"-->
    <value>You invited the next person into your room for your exit interview. As you both stood at the open door, you saw a dubious chef {0} tinkering at your computer. Looks like you caught a spy, trying to steal information from the restaurant this time! You immediately reported the case to the restaurant owner and asked to have {0} FIRED.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DefaultFellPublic">
<!--{0}: harlot-->
<!--{0}: harlot-->
    <value>{0} was caught snooping around the HR Manager's 😠(☠️) room, after which the HR Manager accused them of being a spy to the restaurant owner. Of course, they were not given a second chance and were immediately FIRED! {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotFellPublic">
<!--{0}: cultist who died-->
<!--{0}: cultist who died-->
    <value>{0} was caught snooping around the HR Manager's 😠(☠️) room, after which the HR Manager accused them of being a spy to the restaurant owner. Of course, they were not given a second chance and were immediately FIRED! {0} was the Server 🍒(💋) </value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultistFellPublic">
<!--{0}: thief-->
<!--{0}: thief-->
    <value>The Vegan Chef 🥑(👤) {0} has resigned in the middle of the day with a big smile on their face. Some heard that they were going to apply for the new Vegan Executive Chef position in one of the branches of this restaurant. Where did they learn about such a position? From the HR Manager 😠(☠️) maybe?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThiefFellPublic">
<!--{0}: wolf who died, {1}: "(person) was (role)" to specify what kind of wolf-->
<!--{0}: wolf who died, {1}: "(person) was (role)" to specify what kind of wolf-->
    <value>The Busser 🍽(😈) {0} tried to play "rock, paper, scissors" with the HR Manager's 😠(☠️). The HR Manager liked their current job very much so they decided to fire {0} for trying to pass their mundane job to someone else!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolfFellPublic">
    <value>{0} was caught snooping around the HR Manager's 😠(☠️) room, after which the HR Manager accused them of being a spy to the restaurant owner. Of course, they were not given a second chance and were immediately FIRED! {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SerialKillerSpottedYou">
<!--{0}: grave digger-->
<!--{0}: grave digger-->
    <value>You were tidying up your documents when suddenly your door burst open and a dubious chef ☠️(🔪) came in to grab your hand. Soon, you felt dizzy and fell to the floor, foam spewing from your nostrils and your mouth...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SerialKillerSpotted">
    <value>You feel great having taken down another "victim". As you walked across the office, you noticed that there was a secretive back-room and wondered if that's where all the security officer and their surveillance footage were kept. You decide to burst into that office and poison {0} as well, who was actually the HR Manager 😠(☠️)!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolvesSpottedYou">
<!--{0}: grave digger-->
<!--{0}: grave digger-->
    <value>Someone walked into your room today uninvited. As you were about to call security, they stopped you and told you about a rare job opportunity in the competitor's restaurant! They want YOU to be their managing director? For real? You didn't think twice as you resigned, did an exit interview with yourself and left the restaurant!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolvesSpotted">
<!--{0}: grave digger-->
<!--{0}: grave digger-->
    <value>The Talent Poachers noticed that the secret back-room of the HR Manager 😠(☠️) {0} was unlocked and decided to give a bold attempt in persuading them to join the competitor's restaurant. Who would've thought that {0} would be tricked into believing that the competitor wanted them to be the new managing director? They resigned immediately and ran across the street!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolvesSpottedDiggerPublic">
<!--{0}: grave digger-->
<!--{0}: grave digger-->
    <value>The staff learnt that even {0}, the HR Manager 😠(☠️) resigned today. The Talent Poachers 🍔(🐺) must be really talented themselves to be able to convince and refer {0} to a job in the competitor's restaurant.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="KillerSpottedDiggerPublic">
    <value>{0} was found in their secret back-room, unconscious on the floor with foam spewing from their mouth... They were immediately rushed to the hospital after the first-aiders say they had a serious allergic reaction ☠️(🔪).</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowArsonist">
<!--{0}: Allow/Disallow-->
<!--{0}: Allow/Disallow-->
    <value>Allow Disabled Chef (Arsonist)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowArsonistQ">
<!--{0}: Allow/Disallow-->
<!--{0}: Allow/Disallow-->
    <value>Allow Disabled Chef (Arsonist)? Current: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowArsonistA">
    <value>Disabled Chef (Arsonist) is now set to {0}.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="BurningOverkill">
<!--{0}: Allow/Disallow-->
<!--{0}: Allow/Disallow-->
    <value>Explosion Overkill</value>
  </string>
  <string key="BurningOverkillQ">
<!--{0}: Allow/Disallow-->
<!--{0}: Allow/Disallow-->
    <value>Allow Disabled Chef (Arsonist) and Vengeful Customer (Serial Killer) to be in same game? Might be deadly! 😈 Current: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="BurningOverkillA">
    <value>Disabled Chef (Arsonist) and Vengeful Customer (Serial Killer) in same game are now {0}.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutArsonist">
    <value>You are the Disabled Chef 💣(🔥). You lost your leg in this restaurant and are now back with your artificial limb to take revenge. Every day, you can tinker with the equipment at the station of any staff (if there are no talent poachers left, you can tinker another station at evening). Once one or more stations are tinkered with, you can choose to trigger an explosion on the next day and injuring them all (plus unlucky staff that happen to be next to the equipment! Except the Server 🍒(💋)) You win when you are the last one in the restaurant.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoArsonist">
    <value>You are the Disabled Chef 💣(🔥). A few years ago, you were brutally injured by a stovetop explosion while working in this restaurant. You even lost your leg, but the restaurant didn't bother to compensate you well and just fired you. You are now back with your artificial limb to take revenge. Every day, you can tinker with the equipment at the station of any staff (if there are no talent poachers left, you can tinker another station at evening). Once one or more stations are tinkered with, you can choose to trigger an explosion on the next day and injuring them all (plus unlucky staff that happen to be next to the equipment! Except the Server 🍒(💋)) You win when you are the last one in the restaurant.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Arsonist">
    <value>the Disabled Chef 💣(🔥)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskArsonist">
<!--{0}: arsonist-->
    <value>Whose station's equipment do you want to tinker with? Or do you want to trigger an explosion event today?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ArsonistVisitKiller">
    <value>Seems {0} tried to tinker with the station of the wrong chef 💣(🔥)... not only were they knocked unconscious on the floor, they were also found with rashes all over their body from their head to their toes... They were rushed to hospital due to this severe allergic reaction ☠️(🔪).</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Spark">
<!--{0}: person whose house was doused-->
<!--{0}: person whose house was doused-->
    <value>Click to trigger explosion(s)!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Doused">
    <value>You successfully tinkered with the equipment at {0}'s station!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardSavedYouFromFire">
<!--{0}: saved person-->
<!--{0}: saved person-->
    <value>You were dragged into the back-alley again by the Safety Supervisor ⚠️(👼) because you almost walked into a pile of broken glass on the floor. When you returned, you were shocked to see that your station was blown to pieces - seems like a small explosion happened 💣(🔥)! You were so grateful that the Safety Supervisor "saved your life" with that lecture. You will never forget the lesson they taught you today.</value>
    <value>You were dragged into the back-alley again by the Safety Supervisor ⚠️(👼) for forgetting to wash your hands. When you returned, you were shocked to see that your station was blown to pieces - seems like a small explosion happened 💣(🔥)! You were so grateful that the Safety Supervisor "saved your life" with that lecture. You will never forget the lesson they taught you today.</value>
    <value>You were dragged into the back-alley again by the Safety Supervisor ⚠️(👼) because left your bags on the kitchen counter. When you returned, you were shocked to see that your station was blown to pieces - seems like a small explosion happened 💣(🔥)! You were so grateful that the Safety Supervisor "saved your life" with that lecture. You will never forget the lesson they taught you today.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardSavedFromFire">
<!--{0}: person whose house was cleaned-->
<!--{0}: person whose house was cleaned-->
    <value>You caught {0} being unsafe and all in the kitchen so you dragged them to the back-alley for another lengthy lecture. As you returned with {0}, you were surprised to see that their station was blown to pieces from what seemed a tiny explosion 💣(🔥). {0} thanked you over and over for having "saved their life" - well that is your job after all!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CleanDoused">
<!--{0}: list of people who died in the flames-->
<!--{0}: list of people who died in the flames-->
    <value>You went to inspect {0}'s station and heard a suspicious buzzing sound. It seems the equipment at their station was tampered with and left unchecked by the technicians. You immediately called the technicians to replace this faulty piece of equipment before a fire (or worst, an explosion 💣(🔥)) breaks out!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Burning">
    <value>During the day, the equipment at some of the staff's stations exploded 💣(🔥)! Holy guacamole! These staff members were all injured badly and rushed to the hospital:\n{0}</value>
    <value>During the day, the equipment at some of the staff's stations exploded 💣(🔥)! Holy mother of mackerel! These staff members were all injured badly and rushed to the hospital:\n{0}</value>
    <value>During the day, the equipment at some of the staff's stations exploded 💣(🔥)! What the duck! These staff members were all injured badly and rushed to the hospital:\n{0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ArsonistWins">
    <value>The Disabled Chef 💣(🔥) stands in the kitchen alone among the ruins of exploded stovetops and crushed counters. They have successfully taken their revenge on the restaurant!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Burn">
    <value>You were just taking a short break when the equipment at your station exploded 💣(🔥)! Now you are on your way to the hospital because your body is severely burnt...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Augur">
<!--{0}: role that is not part of the village-->
<!--{0}: role that is not part of the village-->
    <value>the Recruiting Manager 🤝(🦅)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AugurSees">
    <value>You studied the information shared by HR and Marketing and posted a job posting for {0} - because there is no one who is {0} in the restaurant!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutAugur">
    <value>You are the Recruiting Manager 🤝(🦅). Each day, you will be told a staff role that is not in the restaurant at the moment, so that you can publish a job posting online. The same role will not be told twice.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoAugur">
    <value>You are the Recruiting Manager 🤝(🦅). You work closely with HR and Marketing to recruit new chefs and staff for the kitchen, based on which lines are short on people or what the customers want to eat. Each day, you will be told a staff role that is not in the restaurant at the moment, so that you can publish a job posting online. The same role will not be told twice.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AugurSeesNothing">
<!--{0}: chosen victim, {1}: wolf who died in flames-->
<!--{0}: chosen victim, {1}: wolf who died in flames-->
    <value>Strangely, you cannot think of any job to post today because you have made job postings for all possible roles...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolvesVisitBurn">
<!--{0}: person who died because they visited a burning house, {1}: "(person) was (role)"-->
<!--{0}: person who died because they visited a burning house, {1}: "(person) was (role)"-->
    <value>{1} and the Talent Poachers 🍔(🐺) tried to recruit {0} to join the competitor's restaurant. However, as {1} was talking to {0}, their station suddenly exploded 💣(🔥)! Both {0} and {1} were brutally injured while the rest of the Talent Poachers escaped to safety...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DefaultVisitBurn">
<!--{0}: wolf who died, {1}: "(wolf) was (role)" to specify what kind of wolf it is-->
<!--{0}: wolf who died, {1}: "(wolf) was (role)" to specify what kind of wolf it is-->
    <value>Instead of working at their own stations, {0} was standing next to the explosion 💣(🔥) and was gravely injured too! {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolfVisitBurn">
    <value>One of the Talent Poachers, {0} were standing next to the explosion 💣(🔥) and got gravely injured! That is good news (in a sense, am I right?)... {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ChemistKillWiseElder">
    <value>Although the Molecular Gastronomer 🧊(👨‍🔬) themself was very happy they were able to inspire the older generation, the restaurant owner was not glad at all. After all, this is a traditional Michelin 3-star restaurant and those fancy futuristic dishes are only supposed to be desserts for VIP guests or for special tastings. To establish their status and remind everyone the direction this restaurant is going, that Molecular Gastronomer has been demoted to a Line Cook 🧑‍🍳(👱). No more experimentation for them...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ArsonistWinsOverpower">
    <value>Only {0} and {1} are left in the kitchen... With a confident smile, {0} pressed a button and the stoves behind {1} exploded 💣(🔥), with the roof crashing down and the faucets spraying water. {0} laughed as they strode out while the restaurant slowly collapsed... The Disabled Chef has taken their revenge!!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ArsonistTeamEnd">
    <value>Disabled Chef (Arsonist) Team</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotVisitNotHome">
    <value>You tried to have some chit-chat with {0}, but they were nowhere to be found!?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Validate">
<!-- Used for the button in the role selection menu -->
<!-- Used for the button in the role selection menu -->
    <value>‼ Validate ‼</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Valid">
<!-- Used for the button in the role selection menu -->
<!-- Used for the button in the role selection menu -->
<!-- Info for translators: Look at the <string key="Valid"> for the bottom left button's text after the validation succeeded -->
    <value>✅ Valid ✅</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleConfigValid">
    <value>The position configuration is valid! It's enabled and will be used now!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleConfigInvalid">
    <value>The position configuration is invalid! Please try turning on more roles to allow the bot to create balanced games!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GroupIdleCount">
<!-- {0} - Idle count in the last 24 hours in the current group -->
<!-- This string is appended to the "IdleCount" string, make sure this string fits as next sentence after "IdleCount" -->
<!-- {0} - Idle count in the last 24 hours in the current group -->
<!-- This string is appended to the "IdleCount" string, make sure this string fits as next sentence after "IdleCount" -->
    <value>{0} of those kills were in this group.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NewDGRoleModel">
<!-- 0 - target's name -->
<!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>You have become the Management Trainee 🙇(🎭). You will assume {0}'s position after they leave the restaurant.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleConfigInfo">
<!-- Info for translators: Look at the <string key="Valid"> for the bottom left button's text after the validation succeeded -->
    <value>Which positions would you like to use in the restaurant?\n\nConfiguration Tutorial:\n\n✅ = Position enabled\n❌ = Position disabled\n\nAfter selecting the positions, you need to use the VALIDATE button in the bottom left corner to validate and enable your position selection! If you don't validate your selection, it will be ignored and all positions will be used!\n\nIf you disable too many positions, the bot will be unable to create a balanced restaurant and the validation will fail! In that case, just enable more positions and validate again.\n\nIf the validation succeeded, the bottom left button says ✅ Valid ✅ and your position configuration will be used!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="EnableAllRoles">
    <value>Enable All</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DisableAllRoles">
    <value>Disable All</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CHHuntedYou">
    <value>Today you tried to enjoy your time in the kitchen, cutting avocados and decorating salads. The sky came tumbling down when you found out that someone had put meat 🍖(💂) inside your lunchbox!! How could this have happened️? You were so enraged that you immediately resigned and left the restaurant.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ExitAnonymousMode">
    <value>You can't use this bot as anonymous admin! Please exit the anonymous mode (or ask the admin who promoted you to do so) and try again!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskArsonistNoDoused">
    <value>Whose station's equipment do you want to tinker with?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AlreadyDousedList">
    <value>\nYou have already tinkered with the equipment at the stations of: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DoppelgangerEnd">
    <value>Everyone who used to work for this restaurant has left, but the Management Trainee 🙇(🎭) {0} still could not take up a valid job position. How could this be? Perhaps it was because they were a failed student, or that they did such a terrible job at school that they never graduated...</value>
  </string>
</strings>
<!-- credits to ebichu or twenty seven for proofreading -->