<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<strings>
  <language name="English - NSFW" base="English" variant="Not Safe For Work"/>
  <string key="NotInGame">
    <value>You don't appear to be in any games right now...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerStartedGame">
    <value>{0} has started an NSFW game! Use /join to get in on the naughty fun... and probably die :P</value>
    <value>A new NSFW game has been started by {0}! Use /join to be eaten!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerStartedChaosGame">
    <value>{0} has started an NSFW chaos game! Use /join to get in on the fun... and probably die :P</value>
    <value>A new NSFW chaos game has been started by {0}! Use /join to be eaten!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NoJoinGameRunning">
    <value>You can't join now! The game is already running.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AlreadyJoined">
    <value>You've already joined!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MinuteLeftToJoin">
    <value>1 minute left to /join</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SecondsLeftToJoin">
    <value>{0} seconds left to /join</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NotEnoughPlayers">
    <value>Not enough players, cancelling game!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="StartingGameWait">
    <value>Game is starting, please wait while I assign roles and update the database.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="BannedForExploit">
    <value>{0} is banned for attempting an exploit (no names starting with /)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ChangeNameToJoin">
    <value>{0}, please change your name to join</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerLimitReached">
    <value>Sorry, max player limit has been reached!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerJoined">
    <value>{0} has joined the game. {1} dirty-minded motherfuckers, {2} minimum, {3} max</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PMTheBot">
    <value>{0} Please click the start button below or {1} and start me, so I can PM you your role.  If you do not, you will be removed from the game.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DeadFlee">
    <value>You can't run away! YOU'RE DEAD!  Get back in the ground...  jeez, zombies these days.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Flee">
    <value>{0} has buggered off, possibly to avoid being buggered again.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerRoleWas">
    <value>{0} was {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CountPlayersRemain">
    <value>{0} players remain.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DidntAsk">
    <value>Hey I didn't ask you anything yet!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NotPlaying">
    <value>You don't seem to be playing...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NoPlayerName">
    <value>I can't find a player by that name!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AnswerNonValid">
    <value>This answer is not valid!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolfVotedKill">
    <value>{0} has voted to eat {1}.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerVotedLynch">
    <value>{0} has voted to lynch {1}.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="IdleKill">
    <value>{0} has not voted for 2 nights in a row.  The forces of good have seen this as a terrible crime, and {0} suddenly falls, dead. {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="TraitorTurnWolf">
    <value>You traitor!!! You are now the wolf...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ChoiceAccepted">
    <value>Choice accepted.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="BeholderSeer">
    <value>\nThe seer is {0}.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ApprenticeNowSeer">
    <value>{0} was the seer. As the apprentice, you step up to become the new seer.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="BeholderNewSeer">
    <value>{0} was an apprentice, and has now stepped up to fill {1}'s place as the new Seer.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SeerSees">
    <value>You see {0} is {1}!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskLynch">
    <value>Who do you want to lynch?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskDetect">
    <value>Who do you want to detect?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskShoot">
    <value>Who do you want to shoot? {0} bullet(s) remain.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskVisit">
    <value>Who do you want to visit?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskSee">
    <value>Who do you want to see?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskGuard">
    <value>Who do you want to guard?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskEat">
    <value>Who do you want to eat?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskHunt">
    <value>Who do you want to hunt?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskRoleModel">
    <value>Who is your role model?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskConvert">
    <value>Who do you want to convert to your order?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DiscussWith"><!--Leave the leading spaces here please-->
    <value>  Make sure you discuss with {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="And"> <!--this is paired with "DiscussWith".  again, leave the spaces!-->
    <value> and </value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoCursed">
    <value>You are cursed. You are a villager at this time, but if the wolves choose to kill you, you will become a werewolf yourself.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoDetective">
    <value>You are the detective. During the day, you may choose a player to reveal their role.  However - in doing so, your role could be revealed to the wolves! (40% chance)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoDrunk">
    <value>Congrats! You're the village drunk! (and really, everyone knows it...)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoGuardianAngel">
    <value>You are the Guardian Angel. Each night, you may choose a player to save.  However, if you choose a wolf, there is a 50% chance you will die.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoGunner">
    <value>You are the gunner.  You have two bullets.  During the day, you may choose to shoot another player. Everyone will hear the shots, and know you are the gunner (not a wolf).</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoHarlot">
    <value>You are the village slut, you are the village Harlot! During the night, you may choose to go fuck another player, to verify that they are not a wolf.  However--if you visit a wolf, or visit someone killed by the wolf, you will die a hot death.  If you do go to visit though, and the wolf tries to kill you at your home, you will survive and be satisfied.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoTraitor">
    <value>Traitor! For now, you are a villager, but once all the wolves die, you will become a werewolf.  If the seer looks to you, you may or may not be identified as a wolf.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoWolf">
    <value>YOU ARE A WOLF!! XD (good on ya) Each night you can choose to kill someone.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoSeer" >
    <value >You are the seer.  Each night, you may choose a player to 'see', and their role will be revealed to you.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoVillager" >
    <value >You are a lowly villager, doomed to spend your days in a field and possibly eaten, and not in a good way.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoTanner" >
    <value >You are the tanner.  If you get lynched, you win automatically!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoWildChild" >
    <value >You are a wild child! Pick a player to be your 'role model' - if they die, you become a werewolf.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoBeholder" >
    <value >You are the beholder, you will be told who the actual seer is - that is your only function.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoApprenticeSeer" >
    <value >You are the apprentice seer.  If the (real) seer dies, you will take their place as the seer.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoCultist" >
    <value >You are a cultist.  Every night, you may choose a player to convert to your cult of fanatical tentacle-worshipers. If all remaining living players at the end are cultists, they win.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoCultistHunter" >
    <value >You are the Cultist Hunter, trying to stop the cult in town from converting everyone to fanatical tentacle-worshipers!  Each night, choose a player.  If they are a cultist, they die.  If the cult tries to convert you, the cult's newest member dies.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="LynchTime" >
    <value >
      Dusk draws near, and the villagers gather to decide who they are lynching this evening...\nEveryone now has {0} seconds to vote!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DayTime" >
    <value >It is now day time.  All of you have {0} seconds to make your accusations, defenses or rub one out in public.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NightTime" >
    <value >Night has fallen.  Everyone heads to bed, weary after another stressful day.  Night players: you have {0} seconds to use your actions!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="LynchKill" >
    <value >The villagers have cast their votes, amid doubts and suspicions. {0} is dead. {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="LynchTie" >
    <value >Unable to come up with a proper decision on who to lynch, the mob returns to their homes for the night, frustrated and horny.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NoLynchVotes" >
    <value >Something is fishy, as no one voted!  No lynch mob tonight...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DetectiveEaten" >
    <value >The villagers gather in the morning, but do not see {0}.  They wander over to the house, to find {0} disemboweled, an old badge shoved down their throat.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardianEaten" >
    <value >Morning comes, and to everyone's dismay, sodomized with the church's cross is {0}, the Guardian Angel.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GunnerEaten" >
    <value >As everyone comes out of their houses, they find pieces of a shotgun strewn about... then legs... then fingers... then the body of {0}, floating in the fountain in the town square, dead from a werewolf attack.  You have lost your gunner.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SeerEaten" >
    <value >The villagers wake in the morning to find the disemboweled remains of {0} hunched over an ouija board and tarot cards.  The Seer is dead.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DrunkEaten" >
    <value >Everyone wakes to the smell of burning alcohol and wood (heh heh, wood)...  the pub is on fire!!!!  After putting the fire out, the crispy remains of {0} are found, torn apart...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="FoolEaten" >
    <value >As the sun rises above the village, they find {0} sitting over an Ouija board with a deck of.... Bicycle playing cards??? WHAT A FOOL!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DefaultEaten" >
    <value>As everyone rises in the morning, they smell a terrible stink.  They follow the smell to find {0} shredded apart in the pig pen, head missing.  NOMNOMNOMNOM\n{1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterKilledCultist">
    <value>A noticeable stench is coming from {0}'s house...  the village inspects it to find a body lying in front of a dark altar, with dildos shoved in every orifice...  a cultist has been killed by the hunter!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NoAttack" >
    <value >The villagers gather the next morning in the village center, to sighs of relief -- it appears there was no attack the previous night.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CursedBitten" >
    <value >You have been killed by the wolves.  As you were cursed, you have now become a wolf!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolfTeam">
    <value>Your wolf counterpart(s): {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CursedBittenToWolves" >
    <value >{0} was bitten....  but was cursed and became a werewolf! Congrats on your new teammate!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolvesEatYou" >
    <value >Oh no!  The wolves eated you. NOMNOMNOMNOM</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolvesEatDrunk" >
    <value >Oh no! {0} was a drunk!  Now you are drunk, and can't attack tomorrow night...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardWolf" >
    <value >You tried to guard a wolf!  The wolf has eaten you.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardSaved" >
    <value >You have saved {0}'s life!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardNoAttack" >
    <value >{0} was not attacked, so you didn't do much of anything.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardEmptyHouse">
    <value>You went to guard {0}, but they weren't home!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardSavedYou" >
    <value >A guardian angel was watching over you last night, and fought off the wolves!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotEaten" >
    <value >The harlot chose the wrong night to stay home and pleasure herself.  {0} has been eaten by the wolves!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotNotHome" >
    <value >What a surprise... {0} went out for a ride tonight!  No dinner for you, but I am sure someone else is very satisfied.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotFuckWolf" >
    <value >You slip into {0}'s house for some cock, only to be confronted by a wolf instead.  You get face fucked and drowned in cum.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotFuckedWolfPublic" >
    <value >{0} got whipped a little too hard last night! Their bridled, gagged, cum-stained remains are found pinned to the church doors... how sad :(</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotFuckedVictimPublic" >
    <value >{0} crawled into {1}'s bedroom, ready to be a slave. Instead, the harlot found a werewolf choking {1} with its massive cock!  The werewolf quickly turns on {0} and destroys their leather ass.  {0} is dead.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotVisitNonWolf" >
    <value >You see {0} is not a wolf, as you got fucked good and hard all night long!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotVisitYou" >
    <value >You wake up blindfolded and feel the harlot fucking your brains out. Both of you climax, then they slip back out silently.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DetectiveCaught" > 
    <value >You caught {0} snooping about! That must be the detective!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DetectiveSnoop" >
    <value >Your snooping has shown you that {0} is {1}.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotShot" >
    <value >Looks like {0} came back positive after a night with the Harlot. You should all get tested, because that bitch has herpes! The gunner got revenge after one last ride. {1} is dead.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DefaultShot" >
    <value >Suddenly, a shot rings out.  The village turns to see {0} standing over {1}'s body, smoke coming from the gun still aimed at {1}'s head. {2}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolfWins" >
    <value >The werewolf has won!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolvesWin" >
    <value >The werewolves have won!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="VillageWins" >
    <value >The villagers have won! All of the wolves have died...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="TannerWins" >
    <value >Oh no! You lynched the Tanner!  The Tanner wins the game, silly.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RemainingPlayersEnd">
    <value>Remaining living players, roles, and team:</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultistVotedConvert" >
    <value >{0} has voted to convert {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultConvertCultHunter">
    <value>{0} was sent to do your dirty work, and convert {1}... however, they were the cult hunter! {0} is dead!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultHunterKilledCultVisit">
    <value>{0} came to your house last night, ready to convert you...  but you shoved your sword right through the evil cultist. {1} cultist(s) remain!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultConvertYou">
    <value>The cult has converted you to their order!  You are now a fanatical tentacle-worshiping cultist.  Every night, you will have a chance to convert another player, in between bouts of orgiastic tentacle worship..</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultTeam">
    <value>Cultists: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultJoin">
    <value>{0} has joined the cult!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultVisitEmpty">
    <value>{0} was sent to do your dirty work, and convert {1}... but no one was home!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultWins" >
    <value >All the wolves have died, and the only people left standing have all been converted to cultists.  The cult has won!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterVisitDead">
    <value>You went to hunt {0}, but they are already dead!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterFindCultist">
    <value>You go into {0}'s house, and find them praying before an altar to some unknown god...  You quickly slide your sword right through the evil cultist.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterFailedToFind">
    <value>You go to {0}'s house, but there is no mysterious chanting.  They are not a cultist, so you return home.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WildChildToWolves">
    <value>{0}'s role model just died!  In their rage, they have become a werewolf!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WildChildTransform">
    <value>{0} has died! In your rage, you have become a werewolf! Your new teammates are: {1}</value>
  </string>
  <!-- Villager, Drunk, Harlot, Seer, Traitor, GuardianAngel, Detective, Wolf, Cursed, Gunner, Tanner, Fool, WildChild, Beholder, ApprenticeSeer, Cultist, CultistHunter-->
  <string key="Villager">
    <value>a Villager 👱</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Drunk">
    <value>the Drunk 🍻</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Harlot">
    <value>the Harlot 💋</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Seer">
    <value>the Seer 👳</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Traitor">
    <value>the Traitor 🖕</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardianAngel">
    <value>the Guardian Angel 👼</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Detective">
    <value>the Detective 🕵</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Wolf">
    <value>a Werewolf 🐺</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Cursed">
    <value>the Cursed 😾</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Gunner">
    <value>the Gunner 🔫</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Tanner">
    <value>the Tanner 👺</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Fool">
    <value>the Fool 🃏</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WildChild">
    <value>the Wild Child 👶</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Beholder">
    <value>the Beholder 👁</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ApprenticeSeer">
    <value>the Apprentice Seer 🙇</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Cultist">
    <value>a Cultist 👤</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultistHunter">
    <value>the Cultist Hunter 💂</value>
  </string>
  <!-- These are for the player list -->
  <string key="RanAway">
    <value>Ran away</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Dead">
    <value>💀 Dead</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Alive">
    <value>🙂 Alive</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayersAlive">
    <value>Players Alive</value>
  </string>
  <!-- New strings 4 MAY 2016-->
  <string key="Mason">
    <value>a Mason 👷</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoMason">
    <value>You are a Mason.  If there are any other masons, you will know who they are.  Otherwise, you are a villager.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MasonEaten">
    <value>As everyone rises, they find the body of {0} shoved into a pile of stone, blood splattered everywhere.  One of your masons has died!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MasonTeam">
    <value>  The masons are: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <!-- new strings May 6 2016-->
  <string key="CultTargetDead">
    <value>Your newest member heads over to {0}'s house to convert them, but instead finds the house a complete wreck, blood everywhere, and bits of wolf fur snagged on the doorway...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardBlockedWolf">
    <value>The pack heads to {0}'s house to eat them, but they are met by a tall dark figure, armed to the teeth. The Guardian Angel fights everyone off, and they head back defeated.</value>
  </string>
  <!-- new strings May 9 2016-->
  <string key="CultUnableToConvert">
    <!-- 0 - newest  -->
    <!-- 1 - target's name -->
    <value>You send {0} to try to convert {1}, however their belief was too strong, and you were unable to convert them :(</value>
  </string>
  <!-- new string May 12 2016-->
  <string key="NameExists">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <!-- 1 - name -->
    <value>@{1}, a player with the name {0} has already joined.  Please change your name to join.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotDiscoverCult">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>You slipped into {0}'s house for a bit of fun... but as you are leaving, you happen to notice a strange altar, poorly hidden off in a side room, with a strange glowing coming from it...</value>
  </string>
  <!-- new string May 13 2016-->
  <string key="Was">
    <value>was</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GenericDeathNoReveal">
    <!-- 0 - Dead's name -->
    <value>Everyone wakes up in the morning, and notices that {0} is not around...   They check the house to find the remains of {0}.</value>
    <value>As the villagers gather as the sun rises, the find the remains of {0}, who died somehow last night...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MasonConverted">
    <!-- 0 - mason's name -->
    <value>Odd.... {0} didn't show up for the masons meeting this morning... O.o</value>
  </string>
  <!-- new string May 16 2016-->
  <string key="FleeDisabled">
    <value>Fleeing while the game is running has been disabled by the group admin!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="IsDead">
    <!-- used when gunner shoots a player -->
    <value>is dead</value>
  </string>

  <!-- MORE STRINGS May 16, 2016 -->
  <string key="AdminAdded">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>{0} added to admin list. Use /config to change group settings.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AlreadyInGame">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>You are already in a game! ({0})</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MultipleGames">
    <value>Your group has managed to start multiple games...  Killing extras.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GroupQueue">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <!-- 1 - target's name -->
    <value>Your group is currently in the queue.  Position: {0} / {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MaintBreak">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>Sorry, I'm about to start a short maintenance break, you can't start a game right now.\nWaiting on {0} games to end...\nGo to @werewolfdev for more information</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MaxGames">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <!-- 1 - target's name -->
    <value>Sorry, max concurrent games has been reached ({0}).  \nPosition in queue: {1} / {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SkipQueue">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>{0} is a preferred group, and has skipped the queue!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NoGame">
    <value>There is no game running.  Start a new game with /startgame or start a chaos game with /startchaos</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GroupAdminOnly">
    <value>Only a group admin can run this command.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShuttingDown">
    <value>After this game, I am shutting down for maintenance.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShuttingDownUpdate">
    <value>After this game, I am shutting down momentarily for an update (automated).</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NullIdAdmin">
    <value>UserId was null.  Are you sure you sent this as a reply?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AlreadyAdmin">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>{0} is already an admin!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NotAdmin">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>{0} is not an admin!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AdminRemoved">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>{0} removed from admin list.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="LanguageSet">
    <!-- 0 - language's name -->
    <value>Language set to {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NoSeer">
    <value>No seer!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="TimesUp">
    <value>Time's up!</value>
  </string>
  <!-- new strings june 10 2016 -->
  <string key="RoleInfoCupid">
    <value>You are Cupid. Sent to Earth with only underpants, a bow and two arrows, you get to choose two players to love each other for eternity. If one of them dies, the other one dies of sorrow.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoDoppelganger">
    <value>You are a Doppelgänger. Legend has it that your ancestors were metamorphs, and could choose any form they wanted. You have inherited some of their capacities. Choose a player, when that player dies, you will take on their role.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoHunter">
    <value>You are the town Hunter. You do not sleep well, and you would never go to bed without your rifle. If you die, you can choose someone else to kill. If you are eaten, you have a chance to take a werewolf down, but will not be able to choose a player to kill.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoSerialKiller">
    <value>You are the serial killer. Recently escaped from the local asylum, your goal is for everyone else to die. Every night, you can add a player's body to your collection.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CupidChosen">
    <value>You have been struck by love. {0}'s memory will never fade in your heart. Your goal is for both of you to survive. If one of you dies, the other one will die out of sorrow.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterLynchedChoice">
    <value>The village has chosen to hang you! This is your last chance, choose to shoot someone as you go down!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterNoChoiceLynched">
    <value>{0} fumbles for their pistol as the noose tightens, but cannot get it in time, and falls to their death with a loud snap of their neck...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterSkipChoiceLynched">
    <value>{0} whips out their pistol and looks at the crowd... and cannot make a decision on who to shoot. They fall to their death, accepting their fate...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterKilledFinalLynched">
    <!-- 0 - hunter's name -->
    <!-- 1 - target's name -->
    <!-- 2 - target's role -->
    <value>As the noose tightens, {0} whips out a pistol, takes aim, and shoots {1} as the floor drops out! {1} falls over, dead.  {2}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterShotChoice">
    <value>You've been murdered!  In your last moments, you have the chance to shoot someone... make it quick!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterNoChoiceShot">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>The blow to {0} was too much, so much that they couldn't even reach for their sidearm, as they lay in a pool of blood...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterSkipChoiceShot">
    <!-- 0 - hunter's name -->
    <value>As {0} lays there, gasping for their final breaths, they can't decide who to shoot... and accept their fate.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterKilledFinalShot">
    <!-- 0 - hunter -->
    <!-- 1 - target's name -->
    <!-- 2 - target's role -->
    <value>Dying, {0} falls to the ground.... but not without grasping their pistol, and firing upon {1}, who takes a bullet right between the eyes. {2}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultConvertSerialKiller">
    <value>{0} sneaks over to {1}'s house, pops open the door, and is immediately greeted by a crazed maniac with a knife!!! {1} plunges the knife deep into {0}'s organs in alphabetical order, cackling the entire time! {0} is dead D:</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterShotWolfMulti">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>The wolves tried to attack the hunter last night, but the hunter was able to take one down with them as he died! {0} has died (wolf)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterShotWolf">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>The wolf tried to attack the hunter last night, but the hunter was able to take the wolf {0} down with their rifle!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SerialKillerKilledWolf">
    <value>The wolves attempted to have a nice late night snack, but were instead greeted by a crazed murderer! {0} was killed in the fight!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DefaultKilled">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <!-- 1 - target's role -->
    <value>It seemed a quiet enough night for {0}, but they were wrong.  The villagers gather in the morning to find {0} split from head to toe, but oddly the liver was missing...  The serial killer has struck again! {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardBlockedKiller">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>You tried to collect {0}'s body for your collection, but you were fought off by the guardian angel! No kill for you tonight...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultConvertHunter">
    <!-- 0 - Youngest Cultist's name -->
    <!-- 1 - target's name -->
    <value>The cult sends {0} to try to convert {1}, but instead a shot rings out and {0}'s body comes flying out of the window! {0} is dead....</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultConvertSerialKiller">
    <!-- 0 - Youngest Cultist's name -->
    <!-- 1 - target's name -->
    <value>The cult sends {0} to try to convert {1}, but instead a {0}'s body comes flying out of the window, knives pushed into every part of their body! WHAT A PSYCHO! {0} is dead....</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardKiller">
    <value>You tried to guard the serial killer, but they came out and stabbed you 89 times! You are dead...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotFuckKiller">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>You slip into {0}'s house, blindfold them, and start having a little fun.  All seems great until {0} pulls out a knife and starts stabbing you, laughing like a maniac!  You have died....</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotFuckKillerPublic">
    <value>The village was surprised last night hearing {0} scream like the sex hadn't been so sweaty, so hard, so rude before. The village goes to {0}'s house to ask for the kinky details, only to find the Serial Killer came over {0} and then covered it all with the blood of the harlot vowels.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGToMason">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>The doppelganger {0} has now become a mason, just like you!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGTransformToMason">
    <!-- 0 - dead mason's name -->
    <!-- 1 - mason collegues's name -->
    <value>{0} has died, and you transform into a mason.  Your teammates (if any) are: {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGToCult">
    <!-- 0 - new cultist's name -->
    <value>The doppelganger {0} has now become a cultist, just like you!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGTransformToCult">
    <!-- 0 - role's name -->
    <!-- 1 - teammates's name -->
    <value>{0} has died, and you transform into a cultist.  Your teammates (if any) are: {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGToWolf">
    <!-- 0 - DG's name -->
    <value>The doppelganger {0} has now become a wolf, just like you!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGTransformToWolf">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <!-- 1 - teammates's name -->
    <value>{0} has died, and you transform into a wolf.  Your teammates (if any) are: {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SerialKillerWins" isgif="true">
    <value>The only person left standing is the serial killer! They have won!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskKill">
    <value>Who do you want to kill tonight?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="LoverDied">
    <!-- 0 - dead's name -->
    <!-- 1 - lover's name -->
    <!-- 2 - roles -->
    <value>With {0}'s dying breath, {1} rushes over and falls, crying.  They cannot stand the loss of their loved one, and shoot themselves with the nearest pistol they can find. {2}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskDoppelganger">
    <value>Who do you want to become if they die?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskCupid1">
    <value>Who do you want the lovers to be? Choose the first player</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskCupid2">
    <value>Who do you want the lovers to be? Choose the second player</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Hunter">
    <value>the Hunter 🎯</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Cupid">
    <value>Cupid 🏹</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SerialKiller">
    <value>the Serial Killer 🔪</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Doppelgänger">
    <value>the Doppelgänger 🎭</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CupidChosen">
    <!-- 0 - lover's name -->
    <value>Cupids arrow has struck you! You are madly in love with {0}!  If they die, you will die too.  If you both make it to the end, you will both win.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NewWCRoleModel">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>You have become the wild child.  You role model is {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="LoversWin">
    <value>True love endures! The lovers have won!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterKilledVisiter">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <!-- 1 - role -->
    <value>In the middle of the town square, everyone finds the body of {0}, multiple shots to the body.  Looks like they tried to sneak up on the Hunter! {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultAttempt">
    <value>A hooded figure tried to convert you to their cult, but your faith was too strong</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AlreadyOnWaitList">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>You are already on the wait list for {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AddedToWaitList">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>You have been added to the wait list for {0}.  I will PM you when the next game is starting.\nWhile waiting, why not browse the store? https://teespring.com/stores/werewolf-for-telegram</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NotifyNewGame">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>A new game is starting in {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SerialKillerWinsOverpower">
    <!-- 0 - SK's name -->
    <!-- 1 - target's name -->
    <value>Morning comes, and the remaining two villagers walk out to the town square.  {0} takes a look at {1}, gets a big grin on their face, pulls out a knife, and takes {1} out.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NoWinner" isgif="true">
    <value>Everyone in the village has died...  there's nothing but bodies left.  No one wins this round, except the vultures...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SKHunterEnd">
    <!-- 0 - SK's name -->
    <!-- 1 - Hunter's name -->
    <value>As the sun rises, {0} and {1} walk out into the village.  {0} pulls out their knife, and jumps at {1}.  {1} pulls out a pistol and fires a shot into {0}'s face as {0} lands, plunging the knife deep into {1}.  Both are dead, the village is empty, there is no winner...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleModelChosen">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>You failed to make a choice, so the moderator has chosen for you: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Won">
    <value>Won</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Lost">
    <value>Lost</value>
  </string>
  <string key="IdleCount">
    <!-- 0 - player's name -->
    <!-- 1 - idle count -->
    <value>Player {0} has been killed for not voting {1} times in the past 24 hours.</value>
  </string>
  <!--New strings 7th of July-->
  <string key="AboutVG">
    <value>Your role is simple - try to survive. Each day, you will have a chance to lynch the werewolf.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutSeer">
    <value>You are the Seer. In this role, each night, you may choose a player, and have their role revealed to you. Admit to your role wisely: If you reveal you are the seer, the wolves will try to kill you!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutWw">
    <value>You get to have fun! Each day, you will attempt to decieve your fellow players. However, each night, you will get to pick a player to kill! Note:if you attack the drunk, you yourself will become drunk, and will be unable to attack the next night as you sleep off your hangover! If you attack the cursed, they will become a wolf like yourself! Hooray friends!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutHarlot">
    <value>As the harlot (you slut...) you will be given the chance to 'visit' another player each night. If they are not the wolf, you will be told so (because you live!). If you visit a wolf, you will be killed. If you visit the player the wolves have chosen to kill, you will be killed as well. However - If you are visiting a player, and the wolves choose to kill you, you will survive (you weren't home)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutDrunk">
    <value>You drunken bastard! As the drunk, you are still just a villager. BUT! If the wolves kill you, they will become disabled for the next night, as they are drunk off your insanely high BAC.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutCursed">
    <value>As the cursed, you are a normal villager... until the wolves kill you. Once they do, you will become a wolf as well! Free to hunt in the night..... XD</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutTraitor">
    <value>You are a traitorous bastard. If you survive long enough for all the wolves to die, you will become a werewolf, ready to kill your former teammates in the night!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutGA">
    <value>You are the Guardian Angel! Each night, you may choose a player to watch over. Be careful however - if you choose to watch over a wolf, there is a 50% chance you will be killed.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutDetective">
    <value>You old sleuth. Each day, you will have the chance to investigate another player. Use this carefully however, for these is a 40% chance the werewolves will detect you!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutGunner">
    <value>A bit trigger happy are we? As the gunner, you are given 2 silver bullets at the beginning of the game. Each day, you will have the chance to shoot another player. Once you do, everyone will know you are the gunner! Be careful though, you only have 2 bullets!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutTanner">
    <value>The Tanners goal is simple: Get Lynched. If the Tanner gets lynched, he wins, period. Everyone else loses.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutFool">
    <value>he fool is told they are the seer.... when they choose to see someone's role at night, they are told a random role.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutCult">
    <value>As a cultist, it is your goal to convert all other players (except wolves) to your cult. If at the end of the game, all living players are cultist - the cult wins</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutCH">
    <value>Your job is to hunt the Cult. If the cult attacks you, their newest member will die. Each night you may pick a player to 'hunt' - if they are a cultist, they will die.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutWC">
    <value>At the beginning of the game, you will choose someone to be your 'role model'. If they die, you become a werewolf.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutAppS">
    <value>For now, you are a normal villager. However, if the seer dies, you will become the new seer</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutBH">
    <value>You will be told who the seer is (the real one, not the fool)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutMason">
    <value>A mason's job is simple - they automatically know who the other masons are. Otherwise, they are a simple villager.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutDG">
    <value>
      Your ancestors had the ability to metamorph into others... while you don't have their full abilities, you can pick a player at the start of the game. If that player dies, you will become what they were.
      Note: If the player was converted to cult, you will take on their original role. All other normal rules apply: If they were Wild Child and their role model died, you will become a wolf. Otherwise, you will inherit their role model.
      The cult cannot convert the Doppelgänger (but can after the doppelganger switches roles). Also - the Doppelgänger can NOT win unless they have transformed. If at the end of the game, the Doppelgänger is still the same, they lose (exception: lover)
    </value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutCupid">
    <value>
      Love is in the air. As Cupid, you will choose two players at the start of the game. These two players will become madly in love! If one of them dies, the other will die of sorrow :(
      Note: Lovers will know who each other are, but not be told their roles. If the lovers are the last two alive, they win, regardless of teams. If the lovers are on different teams (villager + wolf), and one team wins (wolf), the lover (villager) wins as well. TL;DR if both lovers are alive at the end, and at least one of them was on the winning team, they both win together
    </value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutHunter">
    <value>
      A trigger happy, vindictive player. As the hunter, you try to keep to yourself. However, when others come to visit you, they may find themselves dead, as your paranoia takes hold and you shoot. If the wolves attack you, you have a chance to take one of them with you. Otherwise, if you die, you will get a chance to shoot someone as you die.
      Note: For wolf attacks, the chance starts at 30%. If there is one wolf, the hunter has a 30% chance to kill the wolf (and survive). For each additional wolf, add 20% (2 wolves = 50%, 3 = 70%, etc). However - if there are multiple wolves, while you may kill one of them, you will still be outnumbered and killed.
      If the cult tries to convert you, they have a 50% chance to fail. If they fail, you have a 50% chance to kill one of them!
    </value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutSK">
    <value>That asylum was silly anyways. What a joke. You are free now however, back to business as usual - killing! The serial killer is a lone player, on their own team. They can win only if they are the last player alive (exception: lovers). As the serial killer, you can kill ANYONE - wolves, hunters, gunners, guardian angels, whatever. If the wolves try to attack you, you will kill one of them (random), and live.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutPara">
    <value>Para is a silly developer that likes to bark at people.  Maybe he's been messing with werewolves too long....Messing with werewolves is a very bad idea.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="EndTime">
    <value>Game Length: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <!--New strings, July the 8th -->

  <string key="Day">
    <!--0 - Day -->
    <value>Day {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NodeShutsDown">
    <value>An error has occured, and this node has shut down :/</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SentPrivate">
    <value>I have sent you a PM</value>
  </string>
  <string key="StartPM">
    <value>Please send me a pm so I can PM you: @werewolfbot</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PMTrue">
    <value>Thanks for starting me! I can PM you now.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MustReplySmite">
    <value>You must reply to the user you want to smite</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WhatToDo">
    <value>What would you like to do?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="JoinFromGroup">
    <value>You must join a game from within a group chat!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="StartFromGroup">
    <value>You must start a game from within a group chat!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PingInfo">
    <value>Time to receive ping message: {0}\nCurrent CPU Usage: {1}%\nMessages per second: {2}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WhatLang">
    <value>What Language?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WhatVariant">
    <value>What Variant?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="LangSet">
    <value>Language set to {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GetLang">
    <value>Get which language file?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NoNodes">
    <value>There are no nodes online right now, please try again in a few seconds</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GroupCommandOnly">
    <value>You must run this command in a group</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NotGlobalAdmin">
    <value>You aren't a global admin...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NotPara">
    <value>You aren't Para!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Yes">
    <value>Yes</value>
  </string>
  <string key="No">
    <value>No</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Allow">
    <value>Allow</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Disallow">
    <value>Disallow</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Show">
    <value>Show</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Hide">
    <value>Hide</value>
  </string>
  <!-- Game Mode Choices-->
  <string key="NormalOnly">
    <value>Normal Only</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ChaosOnly">
    <value>Chaos Only</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerChoice">
    <value>Player Choice</value>
  </string>

  <!-- Show Roles on End Game -->
  <string key="ShowNone">
    <value>Don't show any</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShowLiving">
    <value>Show only living players</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShowAll">
    <value>Show all players</value>
  </string>

  <string key="Cancel">
    <value>Cancel</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowFleeQ">
    <!-- note, there is NO space after {0}.  This is on purpose -->
    <value>Do you want to allow fleeing once the game has started?\nNote: players can still flee during join phase\nCurrent: {0} fleeing</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowFleeA">
    <!-- note, there is NO space after {0}.  This is on purpose -->
    <value>{0} fleeing after game start</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MaxPlayersQ">
    <value>How many players would like to set as the maximum?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MaxPlayersA">
    <value>Max players set to {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShowRolesDeathQ">
    <value>Show or Hide roles on death?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShowRolesDeathA">
    <value>Roles will be {0} on death.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GameModeQ">
    <value>What game mode will the group be?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GameModeA">
    <value>Game mode set to {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShowRolesEndQ">
    <value>How do you want roles to be shown at the end?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShowRolesEndA">
    <value>Roles shown at end set to: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SetDayTimeQ">
    <value>Choose the base time (in seconds) for day time.   This will still be modified based on number of players.\nMinimum time added based on players is 60 seconds.  Default setting: {0}\nCurrent: {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SetDayTimeA">
    <value>Base day time set to {0} seconds</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SetNightTimeQ">
    <value>Choose the time (in seconds) for night time. Default setting: {0}\nCurrent:{1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SetNightTimeA">
    <value>Night time set to {0} seconds</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SetLynchTimeQ">
    <value>Choose the time (in seconds) for lynch voting. Default setting: {0}\nCurrent:{1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SetLynchTimeA">
    <value>Lynch voting time set to {0} seconds</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowFoolQ">
    <value>Allow fool as a role option?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowFoolA">
    <value>Fool as a role set to: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowTannerQ">
    <value>Allow tanner as a role option?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowTannerA">
    <value>Tanner as a role set to: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowCultQ">
    <value>Allow cult as a role option?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowCultA">
    <value>Cult as a role set to: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThankYou">
    <value>Thank you, have a good day :)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WhatLangGroup">
    <value>What language do you want to look for a group to play in?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HereIsList">
    <value>Here are the groups for {0}:</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Members">
    <value>Members</value>
  </string>
  <string key="StartMe">
    <value>Please start me so I can PM you</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerNoPM">
    <value>{0} failed to start the bot, and has been removed from the game!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="LatestList">
    <value>Here is the latest list</value>
  </string>
  <string key="UnableToGetList">
    <value>Unable to get latest list</value>
  </string>
  <string key="YouJoined">
    <!-- 0 - Group Name -->
    <value>You have successfully joined the game in {0}</value>
  </string>
</strings>
