<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<strings>
  <language name="Furry - SFW (ish)" base="English" variant="Furry SFW(ish)" owner="Evandill"/>
  <string key="NotInGame">
    <value>Sorry. You don't appear to be in any games right now.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerStartedGame">
    <value>*{0}* has started a game! use /join to get in and get this game started!</value>
    <value>A new game has been started by {0}! Use /join to get eated maybe!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerStartedChaosGame">
    <value>{0} has started a chaos game! use /join to get in on the randomness!</value>
    <value>A new chaos game has been started by {0}! Use /join to get chaotic!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NoJoinGameRunning">
    <value>Sorry, You're going to have to wait in line, and watch patiently until this round is done.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AlreadyJoined">
    <value>You're already here! You can't be here twice you sill fuzzball</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MinuteLeftToJoin">
    <value>1 minute left to /join</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SecondsLeftToJoin">
    <value>{0} seconds left to /join</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NotEnoughPlayers">
    <value>Not enough players, cancelling game!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="StartingGameWait">
    <value>Game is starting, wait while I assign roles, update the database, zip up all the fursuits and queue up "Try Everything".</value>
  </string>
  <string key="BannedForExploit">
    <value>{0} is banned for attempting an exploit (no names starting with /)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ChangeNameToJoin">
    <value>{0}, change your name to join.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerLimitReached">
    <value>Sorry, max player limit has been reached!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerJoined">
    <value>{0} has joined the game. {1} furballs, {2} minimum, {3} max</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PMTheBot">
    <value>{0} click this: {1}, then click start.  Until you do, I cannot tell you what your role is.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DeadFlee">
    <value>You can't run away! YOU'RE DEAD!  Get back in the ground! Crazy furries...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Flee">
    <value>{0} has fled in terror! How dare they!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerRoleWas">
    <value>{0} was {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CountPlayersRemain">
    <value>{0} perverted fleabags remain.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DidntAsk">
    <value>Hey, I didn't ask you anything yet!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NotPlaying">
    <value>You... don't seem to be playing...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NoPlayerName">
    <value>I can't find a player by that name!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AnswerNonValid">
    <value>This answer is not valid!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolfVotedKill">
    <value>{0} has voted to go after {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerVotedLynch">
    <value>{0} has voted to lynch {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="IdleKill">
    <value>*{0}* has not voted 2 nights in a row. The forces of good have seen this as a terrible crime, and as a result *{0}* gets put to the noose as an example to the rest *{1}*</value>
  </string>
  <string key="TraitorTurnWolf">
    <value>You traitor!!! You are now able to get in on the mayhem as a wolf..</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ChoiceAccepted">
    <value>Choice accepted</value>
  </string>
  <string key="BeholderSeer">
    <value>\nThe owl is {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ApprenticeNowSeer">
    <value>{0} was the owl. As the apprentice, you step up to become the new owl.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="BeholderNewSeer">
    <value>{0} was an apprentice, and has now stepped up to fill {1}'s place as the new owl.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SeerSees">
    <value>You see {0} is {1}!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskLynch">
    <value>Who do you want to lynch?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskDetect">
    <value>Who do you want to snoop on, ?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskShoot">
    <value>Who do you want to burn? {0} fireball(s) remain</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskVisit">
    <value>Who do you want to get it on with?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskSee">
    <value>Who do you want to peek at?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskGuard">
    <value>Who do you want to guard?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskEat">
    <value>Who do you want to eat?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskHunt">
    <value>Who do you want to hunt?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskRoleModel">
    <value>Who is your role model?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskConvert">
    <value>Who do you want to convert to your order?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DiscussWith"><!--Leave the leading spaces here please-->
    <value>  Make sure you discuss with {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="And"> <!--this is paired with "DiscussWith".  again, leave the spaces!-->
    <value> and </value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoCursed">
    <value>You are a Husky (cursed). You are a villager at this time, but if the wolves choose to go for you, you will instead become a wuff yourself..</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoDetective">
    <value>You are the rat (detective). During the day, you may choose a player to try to find out their role.  However - in doing so, your role could be revealed to the wolves! (40% chance)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoDrunk">
    <value>Congrats! You're the poisonous frog(drunk)! If the wolves eat you they trip out out for a whole night!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoGuardianAngel">
    <value>You are the Tiger(guardian angel). Each night, you may choose a player to save.  However, if you choose a wolf, there is a 50% chance you will die.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoGunner">
    <value>You are the Dragon(gunner). You have two fireballs.  During the day, you may choose to burn the clothes off of another player and knock them out of the game. Everyone will see you do it, and know you are the dragon (not a wolf).</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoHarlot">
    <value>You slut!(harlot) You are the fox. During the night, you may choose to read your fanfics another player, to verify if they are not a wolf.  However - if you visit a wolf, or visit someone killed by the wolf, you will die.  If you do go out though, and the wolf tries to kill you at your home, you will survive.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoTraitor">
    <value>Traitorous Mongrel!(traitor...duh.) For now, you are a villager, but once all the wolves die, you will become a werewolf.  If the owl looks to you, you may or may not be identified as a wolf.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoWolf">
    <value>XD YOU ARE A WOLF!! (good on ya) Each night you can choose someone to nom on!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoSeer" >
    <value >You are the Owl(seer).  Each night, you may choose a player to 'see', and reveal their role to you.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoVillager" >
    <value >You are a lowly bunny(villager), doomed to spend your days plowing a field and probably getting nommed on.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoTanner" >
    <value >You are the hyena(tanner).  If you get lynched, you win automatically!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoWildChild" >
    <value >You are a lemur(wild child)! Pick a player to be your 'role model' - if they die, you freak out and become a werewolf.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoBeholder" >
    <value >You are the Raven(beholder), you will be told who the (real) seer is - that is your only function.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoApprenticeSeer" >
    <value >You are the owlet(apprentice seer). If the (real) seer dies, you will take their place as the seer.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoCultist" >
    <value >You are a snake(cultist). Every night, you may choose a player to convert to a cultist. If all remaining living players at the end are cultists, they win.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoCultistHunter" >
    <value >There is a cultist in the town, trying to convert everyone! Each night, choose a player. If they are a cultist, you capture and kill them.  If the cult tries to convert you, the newest member gets taken out.(Cult Hunter)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="LynchTime" >
    <value >
      Dusk draws near, and the villagers gather to decide who they are lynching this evening...
      Everyone now has {0} seconds to vote! Make it count.
    </value>
  </string>
  <string key="DayTime" >
    <value >It is now day time.  All of you have {0} seconds to make your accusations / defenses / talk.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NightTime" >
    <value >Night has fallen.  Everyone heads to bed, weary after another stressful day. Night players: you have *{0}* seconds use your actions!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="LynchKill" >
    <value >The villagers have cast their votes, amid doubts and suspicions. {0} gets tied to the lynching post and hung for all to see. {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="LynchTie" >
    <value >Unable to come up with a proper decision on who to lynch, the mob returns to their homes for the night, frustrated...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NoLynchVotes" >
    <value >I guess everyone spent so much time pointing that nobody voted.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DetectiveEaten" >
    <value >The villagers gather in the morning, but do not see *{0}*.  They wander over to the house, to find *{0}* missing. All that remains is an old *badge* along with several other bloodstained notes.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardianEaten" >
    <value >Morning comes, and to everyone's dismay; *{0}* is in the center of town, impaled on top of their own spear. Very, very much dead. You have lost your *tiger*.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GunnerEaten" >
    <value >As everyone comes out of their houses, they find signs of a struggle, some scales strewn about and markings of fire in the town square, and far off in the distance you hear a familiar roar of *{0}*. You have lost your *dragon*.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SeerEaten" >
    <value >The villagers awake in the morning, to find that *{0}* is missing. Their ouija board and tarot cards, both torn by clawmarks and doused in blood.  The *Owl* is dead.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DrunkEaten" >
    <value >Everyone wakes to find *{0}* missing. Checking the pub and find cups strewn about, some broken, some filled with barf, but more of them filled with blood and fur.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="FoolEaten" >
    <value >As the sun rises above the village, they find *{0}* missing. Their ouija board has been torn by giant claws and covered in blood, but their deck of... bicycle playing cards? happens to be visible, though still essentially useless. WHAT A *FOOL*!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DefaultEaten" >
    <value>As everyone rises in the morning, they smell a terrible stink.  They follow the smell to find *{0}* lying in in the pig pen, torn apart by giant claws. Going through their things, it's clear that: \n*{1}*</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterKilledCultist">
    <value>A noticeable stench is coming from *{0}'s* house...  the village inspects it to find a dark altar, still faintly glowing with dark power...  a *cultist* has been captured by the hunter!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NoAttack" >
    <value >The villagers gather the next morning in the village center, to sighs of relief - it appears there was no attack the previous night, everyone seems accounted for!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CursedBitten" >
    <value >You have been bitten. As the husky, you get to join them, becoming a wolf!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolfTeam" >
    <value>Your wolf counterpart(s): {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CursedBittenToWolves" >
    <value >{0} was bitten....  but was cursed, and became a werewolf! Congrats on your new teammate!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolvesEatYou" >
    <value >Oh no! The wolves got to you and tore you apart!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolvesEatDrunk" >
    <value >Oh no! {0} was a drunk!  Now you are tripping and barfing, and can't attack tomorrow night...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardWolf" >
    <value >You tried to guard a wolf, and for your efforts get bitten and killed.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardSaved" >
    <value >You have saved {0}'s life!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardNoAttack" >
    <value >{0} was not attacked, so you didn't do much of anything.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardEmptyHouse" >
    <value>You went to guard {0}, but they weren't home!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardSavedYou" >
    <value >The Tiger was watching over you last night, and fought off the wolves!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotEaten" >
    <value >The harlot decided to take the wrong night for deciding to recover and write some new fanfics.  *{0}* has been eaten by the wolves</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotNotHome" >
    <value >Damn... {0} was not home!  No dinner for you.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotFuckWolf" >
    <value >You slip into *{0}'s* house for a little fun, but only to be confronted by a wolf and the wolf doesn't seem up for hearing about your ships.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotFuckedWolfPublic" >
    <value >*{0}* slipped into the wrong house last night! All that's found of them is their handcuffs tied to the church doors, bloodstains from over the night, and a notebook torn to pieces on illicit pairings. The fox is dead.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotFuckedVictimPublic" >
    <value >*{0}* slips into *{1}'s* house, ready to have a little fun.  However, they instead find a werewolf tearing *{1}* limb from limb!  The werewolf quickly and forcibly drags *{0}* in to add them to the  bloody mess. *{0}* is dead.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotVisitNonWolf" >
    <value >You see {0} is not a wuffer, as you were able to read to them all your lewd fanfics.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotVisitYou" >
    <value >Either because of how dark it was when they did their deeds, or because they blindfolded you during the whole thing, you couldn't see exactly what the fox(harlot) did to you. Whatever it was, you do remember something about an OTP? </value>
  </string>
  <string key="DetectiveCaught" >
    <value >You caught {0} snooping about! They are the Rat!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DetectiveSnoop" >
    <value >Your snooping has shown you that {0} is {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotShot" >
    <value >Looks like {0} came back positive after a night with the Harlot! The gunner got revenge. {1} is dead.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DefaultShot" >
    <value >Suddenly, a loud roar sounds in the village.  The village turns to see *{0}* spitting fire at *{1}* burning them to ash and cinders. A *{2}*</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolfWins" >
    <value >With that, the wolf leaps onto the remaining villager, delighting in their last meal. The *werewolf* has won!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolvesWin" >
    <value >With that, the wolves grab and leap upon the remaining villagers, enjoying their last, bloody meal... The *werewolves* have won!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="VillageWins" >
    <value >With that, you see the last of the wolves killed off, the corpse shifting into a much bigger and bulkier wolf as confirmation. The *villagers* have won!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="TannerWins" >
    <value >Oh no! You lynched the *Hyena*!  Their laugh keeps going on within the town even as they're dead, basically meaning they win the game, silly.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RemainingPlayersEnd">
    <value>Remaining living players, roles, and team:</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultistVotedConvert" >
    <value >{0} has voted to convert {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultConvertCultHunter">
    <value>{0} was sent to do your dirty work, and convert {1}... however, they were the cult hunter! {0} is dead!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultHunterKilledCultVisit">
    <value>{0} came to your house last night, ready to convert you....  but you managed to lock them up below your house, taking care of one cultist. {1} remain!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultConvertYou">
    <value>The cult has converted you to their order!  You are now a Snake (cultist).  Every other night, you will have a chance to convert another player...  When you're not, you're too busy praying to a dark god beyond space.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultTeam">
    <value>Snakes: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultJoin">
    <value>{0} has joined the cult!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultVisitEmpty">
    <value>{0} was sent to do your dirty work, and convert {1}... but no one was home!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultWins" >
    <value>All the wolves have died, and the only bunnies left standing have all been converted to cultists... in celebration they open a ritual bringing forth the ender of days /n The *cult* has won!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterVisitDead">
    <value>You went to hunt {0}, but they are already dead!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterFindCultist">
    <value>You go into {0}'s house, and find them praying before an altar to some unknown god. You interrupt their chant by stabbing them through the chest.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterFailedToFind">
    <value>You go to {0}'s house, but there is no mysterious chanting or weird altars.  They are not a cultist, so you return home.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WildChildToWolves">
    <value>{0}'s role model just died! In their butthurt rage, they have become a werewolf!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WildChildTransform">
    <value>{0} has died! In your butthurt rage, you have become a werewolf! Your new teammates are: {1}</value>
  </string>
  <!-- Villager, Drunk, Harlot, Seer, Traitor, GuardianAngel, Detective, Wolf, Cursed, Gunner, Tanner, Fool, WildChild, Beholder, ApprenticeSeer, Cultist, CultistHunter-->
  <string key="Villager">
    <value>a Rabbit (Villager) 👱</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Drunk">
    <value>the Poison Frog (Drunk) 🍻</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Harlot">
    <value>the Fox (Harlot) 💋</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Seer">
    <value>the Owl (Seer) 👳</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Traitor">
    <value>the Mongrel (Traitor) 🖕</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardianAngel">
    <value>the Tiger (Guardian Angel) 👼</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Detective">
    <value>the Rat (Detective) 🕵</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Wolf">
    <value>a Werewolf 🐺</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Cursed">
    <value>the Husky (Cursed) 😾</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Gunner">
    <value>the Dragon (Gunner) 🔫</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Tanner">
    <value>the Hyena (Tanner) 👺</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Fool">
    <value>the Derp (Fool) 🃏</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WildChild">
    <value>the Lemur (Wild Child) 👶</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Beholder">
    <value>the Raven (Beholder) 👁</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ApprenticeSeer">
    <value>the Owlet (Apprentice Seer) 🙇</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Cultist">
    <value>a Snake (Cultist) 👤</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultistHunter">
    <value>the Weasel (Cultist Hunter) 💂</value>
  </string>
  <!-- These are for the player list -->
  <string key="RanAway">
    <value>Ran away</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Dead">
    <value>💀 Dead</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Alive">
    <value>🙂 Alive</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayersAlive">
    <value>Players Alive</value>
  </string>
  <!-- New strings 4 MAY 2016-->
  <string key="Mason">
    <value>an Otter (Mason) 👷</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoMason">
    <value>You are an Otter(Mason). If there are any other Otters, you will know who they are. Otherwise, you are a villager.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MasonEaten">
    <value>As everyone rises, they find the body of {0} shoved into a pile of stone, blood splattered everywhere.  One of your otters has died!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MasonTeam">
    <value>  The otters are: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <!-- new strings May 6 2016-->
  <string key="CultTargetDead">
    <value>Your newest member heads over to {0}'s house to convert them, but instead finds the house a complete wreck, blood all over, and bits of wolf fur snagged on the doorway...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardBlockedWolf">
    <value>The pack heads to {0}'s house to eat them, but they are met by white growling tiger, Who snarls and fights everyone off, and you have to head back defeated.</value>
  </string>
  <!-- new strings May 9 2016-->
  <string key="CultUnableToConvert">
    <value>You send {0} to try to convert {1}, however their belief was too strong, and you were unable to convert them :(</value>
  </string>
  <!-- new string May 12 2016-->
  <string key="NameExists">
    <value>@{1}, a player with the name {0} has already joined.  Change your name to join.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotDiscoverCult">
    <value>You slipped into {0}'s house for a bit of fun, and you end up getting your fill; but as you are leaving you happen to notice a strange altar, poorly hidden away in a side room, a strange glowing coming from it...</value>
  </string>
  <!-- new string May 13 2016-->
  <string key="Was">
    <value>was</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GenericDeathNoReveal">
    <value>Everyone wakes up in the morning, and notices that {0} is not around.... The villagers look around and find {0}; torn apart, and nothing to identify them by.</value>
    <value>As the villagers gather as the sun rises, the find that {0} is missing; somehow leaving, or getting dragged away last night...</value>
  </string>
<string key="MasonConverted">
    <value>Odd.... {0} didn't show up for the daily underwater swim this morning.</value>
  </string>
  <!-- new string May 16 2016-->
  <string key="FleeDisabled">
    <value>Fleeing while the game is going on has been disabled by the group admin!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="IsDead"> <!-- used when gunner shoots a player -->
    <value>is dead</value>
  </string>
  <!-- MORE STRINGS May 16, 2016 -->
  <string key="AdminAdded">
    <value>{0} added to admin list. Use /config to change group settings.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AlreadyInGame">
    <value>You are already in a game elsewhere! (probably not as fun as ours though) ({0})</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MultipleGames">
    <value>Your group has managed to start multiple games...  Killing extras. Stop it.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GroupQueue">
    <value>Your group is currently in the queue.  Position: {0} / {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MaintBreak">
    <value>I'm about to start a  maintenance break, No games right now. \nWaiting on {0} games to end...\nGo to @greywolfdev for more information</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MaxGames">
    <value>Sorry, max concurrent games has been reached ({0}).  \nPosition in queue: {1} / {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SkipQueue">
    <value>{0} is too awesome for queues, and has skipped the line!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NoGame">
    <value>There is no game going on. Feel free to request me to start a new game with /startgame or start a chaos game with /startchaos</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GroupAdminOnly">
    <value>Only a group admin can run this command.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShuttingDown">
    <value>After this game, I am shutting down for maintenance.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShuttingDownUpdate">
    <value>After this game, I am shutting down momentarily for an update (automated).</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NullIdAdmin">
    <value>UserId was null.  Are you sure you sent this as a reply?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AlreadyAdmin">
    <value>{0} is already an admin!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NotAdmin">
    <value>{0} is not an admin!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AdminRemoved">
    <value>{0} removed from admin list.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="LanguageSet">
    <value>Language set to {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NoSeer">
	<value>No seer! Sorry, but good luck!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="TimesUp">
	<value>Too late. Time's up!</value>
  </string>
  <!-- new strings june 10 2016 -->
  <string key="RoleInfoCupid">
    <value>You are the lovebird(Cupid). You're a dirty shipper who can can sneak into peoples houses and get them attracted to each other's smell. Choose two players who will become addicted to each other's scent. If one of them dies, the other one dies of sorrow.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoDoppelganger">
    <value>You are a chameleon(Doppelgänger). Choose a player, when that player dies, you will take on their role.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoHunter">
    <value>You are the bear(Hunter). It's not hibernation time, so you don't sleep well and are kinda cranky. If you die, you can choose someone else to kill. If you are eaten, you have a chance to take a werewolf down, but will not be able to choose a player to kill.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoSerialKiller">
    <value>You are the Wasp(Serial Killer). Recently escaped from the local asylum, your goal is for everyone else to die. Every night, you can add a player's body to your collection.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CupidChosen">
    <value>You have been struck by love.. and a small addiction to {0}'s smell. Mostly the second one. Your goal is for both of you to survive. If one of you dies, the other one will die out of sorrow.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterLynchedChoice">
    <value>The village has chosen to hang you! This is your last chance, choose to kill someone as you go down!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterNoChoiceLynched">
    <value>{0} fumbles for a moment as they fight against the noose tightening, but cannot get it in time, and falls to their death with a loud snap of their neck...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterSkipChoiceLynched">
    <value>{0} breaks free before they're finished being hung...but then they can't make a decision on what to do, so they accept their fate...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterKilledFinalLynched">
    <value>As the noose starts to tighten around {0} they break free before they're finished being killed and with what strength they can muster go to beat {1} into the ground just before being forcibly sentenced to death! {1}.  {2}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterShotChoice">
    <value>Someone has attempted to take you out! In your last moments, you have the chance to take someone with you.... make it quick!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterNoChoiceShot">
    <value> {0} starts to stumble out of their house looking around but before they can make a decision they let out a groan and give in to their wounds afflicted on them by their attacker.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterSkipChoiceShot">
    <value>{0} starts to stumble out of their house looking around but they can't decide who to  go after.... and accept the fate given...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterKilledFinalShot">
    <value> {0} starts to stumble out of their house looking around before turning to {1} and shoving them to the floor making sure to use the last of their rage to pulverize {1}. {2}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultConvertSerialKiller">
    <value>{0} sneaks over to {1}'s house, pops open the door, to introduce them to the wonderful world of space gods; and is immediately greeted by a crazed maniac with a stinger! {1} plunges the knife deep into {0}'s organs in alphabetical order, cackling the entire time! {0} is dead.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterShotWolfMulti">
    <value>The wolves tried to attack the hunter last night, but the hunter was able to take one down with them as they died! {0} has died</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterShotWolf">
    <value>The wolf tried to attack the hunter last night, but the hunter was able to take the wolf {0} down!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SerialKillerKilledWolf">
    <value>The wolves attempted to have a nice late night snack, but were instead greeted by a crazy person! {0} was stung to their doom!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DefaultKilled">
    <value>It seemed a quiet enough night for {0}, but they were wrong.  The villagers gather in the morning to find {0} dead with several puncture wounds all over.  The serial killer has struck again! {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardBlockedKiller">
    <value>You tried to collect {0}'s body for your organ collection, but you were fought off by the guardian angel! No kill for you tonight....</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultConvertHunter">
    <value>The cult sends {0} to try to convert {1}, but instead {0}'s body get thrown out the window, bruised and bloodied! {0} is dead....</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultConvertSerialKiller">
    <value>The cult sends {0} to try to convert {1}, but instead a {0}'s body comes flying out of the window, knives pushed into every part of their body! WHAT A PSYCHO! {0} is dead....</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardKiller">
    <value>You tried to guard the serial killer, but they came out to thank you with stabbings.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotFuckKiller">
    <value>You slip into {0}'s house, and start having a little fun; it seems great until {0} starts introducing more knives to your fanfics... and to your body.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotFuckKillerPublic">
    <value>don't worry about this string for now!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGToMason">
    <value>The chameleon(Doppelganger) {0} has now become a mason, just like you!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGTransformToMason">
    <value>{0} has died, and you transform into an otter.  Your teammates (if any) are: {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGToCult">
    <value>The doppelganger {0} has now become a snake(Cult), just like you!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGTransformToCult">
    <value>{0} has died, and you transform into a snake(Cult).  Your teammates (if any) are: {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGToWolf">
    <value>The chameleon (Doppelganger) {0} has now become a wolf, just like you!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGTransformToWolf">
    <value>{0} has died, and you transform into a wolf.  Your teammates (if any) are: {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SerialKillerWins" isgif="true">
    <value>The only one left is the wasp! They win, atop a pile of orgasming sluts!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskKill">
    <value>Who do you want to kill tonight?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="LoverDied">
    <value>With {0}'s dying breath, {1} rushes over and falls, crying.  They cannot stand the loss of their loved one, and shoot themselves with the nearest pistol the can find. {2}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskDoppelganger">
    <value>Who do you want to become if they die?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskCupid1">
    <value>Who do you want the lovers to be? Choose the first player</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskCupid2">
    <value>Who do you want the lovers to be? Choose the second player</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Hunter">
    <value>the Bear(Hunter) 🎯</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Cupid">
    <value>the Lovebird(Cupid) 🏹</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SerialKiller">
    <value>the Hornet(Serial Killer) 🔪</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Doppelgänger">
    <value>the Chameleon(Doppelganger) 🎭</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CupidChosen">
    <value>the musk of {0} has struck you! You are madly in love with the smell of {0}!  If they die, you will die too.  If you both make it to the end, you will both win.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NewWCRoleModel">
    <value>You have become the Lemur(wild child).  You role model is {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="LoversWin">
    <value>True love endures! The lovers have won! The lovers celebrate by skipping town.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterKilledVisiter">
    <value>In the middle of the town square, everyone finds the body of {0}, multiple impact marks to the body.  Looks like they tried to sneak up on the Hunter! {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultAttempt">
    <value>A hooded figure tried to convert you to their cult of tentacles, but your faith was too strong.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AlreadyOnWaitList">
    <value>You are already on the wait list for {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AddedToWaitList">
    <value>You have been added to the wait list for {0}.  I will let you know when the next game is starting. Try not to blow too many loads in the meantime.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NotifyNewGame">
    <value>Hey, A new game is starting in {0} get in that game.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SerialKillerWinsOverpower">
    <value>Morning comes, and the remaining two villagers walk out to the town square.  {0} takes a look at {1}, gets a big grin on their face, and stabs {1} 37 times with their stinger.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NoWinner" isgif="true">
    <value>Everyone in the village has been killed in one shape or another  No one wins this round, except the vultures.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SKHunterEnd">
    <value>As the sun rises, {0} and {1} walk out into the village. Noticing that they're the only two left {0} goes over to sting  {1}. They both struggle and fight for control, though both end up getting plenty of wounds before ending up killing each other./n The village is empty , there is no winner!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleModelChosen">
    <value>You failed to make a decision, so I had to choose for you: {0}. Pay Attention.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Won">
    <value>Won</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Lost">
    <value>Lost</value>
  </string>
<string key="IdleCount">
    <!-- 0 - player's name -->
    <!-- 1 - idle count -->
    <value>This furball: {0} has been killed for not voting {1} times in the past 24 hours.</value>
  </string>
  <!--New strings 7th of July-->
  <string key="AboutVG">
    <value>Your role is simple - try to survive. Each day, you will have a chance to lynch the werewolf/Serial Killer/Cultists.Rolenames: Villager/Bunny.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutSeer">
    <value>You are the Seer/Owl. In this role, each night, you may choose a player, and have their role revealed to you. Admit to your role wisely: If you reveal you are the seer, the wolves will try to kill you!Rolenames: Seer/owl</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutWw">
    <value>You get to have fun! Each day, you will attempt to deceive your fellow players. However, each night, you will get to pick a player to kill! Note:if you attack the drunk/poison frog, you yourself will become drunk, and will be unable to attack the next night as you sleep off your hangover! If you attack the cursed/husky, they will become a wolf like yourself! Hooray friends!Rolenames: Werewolf/Wuffer</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutHarlot">
    <value>As the harlot/fox, you will be given the chance to 'visit' another player each night. If they are not the wolf, you will be told so (because you live!). If you visit a wolf, you will be killed. If you visit the player the wolves have chosen to kill, you will be killed as well. However - If you are visiting a player, and the wolves choose to kill you, you will survive (you weren't home)Rolenames: Harlot/Fox</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutDrunk">
    <value>You drunken, poisonous bastard! As the drunk, you are still just a villager. BUT! If the wolves kill you, they will become disabled for the next night, as they are tripping off your weird fluids.Rolenames: Drunk/Poison Frog</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutCursed">
    <value>As the cursed/husky, you are a normal villager... until the wolves kill you. Once they do, you will become a wolf as well! Free to hunt in the night..... XD Rolenames: Cursed/Husky.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutTraitor">
    <value>You are a traitorous mongrel. If you survive long enough for all the wolves to die, you will become a werewolf, ready to kill your former teammates in the night! Rolenames: Traitor/Mongrel.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutGA">
    <value>You are the Guardian Angel/White Tiger! Each night, you may choose a player to watch over. Be careful however - if you choose to watch over a wolf, there is a 50% chance you will be killed. Rolenames: Guardian Angel/WhiteTiger</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutDetective">
    <value>You snooping rat.. Each day, you will have the chance to investigate another player. Use this carefully however, for these is a 40% chance the werewolves will detect you! Rolenames: Detective/Rat</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutGunner">
    <value>A bit trigger happy are we? As the gunner/dragon, you are given 2 fireballs at the beginning of the game. Each day, you will have the chance to shoot another player. Once you do, everyone will know you are the gunner/dragon! Be careful though, you only have 2 shots! Rolenames: Gunner/Dragon.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutTanner">
    <value>The Tanners/hyena's goal is simple: Get Lynched. If the Tanner gets lynched, he wins, period. Everyone else loses.Rolenames: Tanner/Hyena.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutFool">
    <value>The fool/derp is told they are the seer.... when they choose to see someone's role at night, they are told a random role.Rolenames: Fool/Derp.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutCult">
    <value>As a cultist/snake, it is your goal to convert all other players (except wolves) to your cult. If at the end of the game, all living players are cultist - the cult wins. Rolenames: Cult/Snake.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutCH">
    <value>Your job is to hunt the Cult. If the cult attacks you, their newest member will die. Each night you may pick a player to 'hunt' - if they are a cultist, they will die. Rolenames: Cult Hunter/Weasel</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutWC">
    <value>At the beginning of the game, you will choose someone to be your 'role model'. If they die, you become a werewolf. Rolenames: Wild Child/Lemur</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutAppS">
    <value>For now, you are a normal villager. However, if the seer dies, you will become the new seer. Rolenames: Apprentice Seer/Owlet</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutBH">
    <value>You will be told who the seer is (the real one, not the fool) Rolenames: Beholder/Raven.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutMason">
    <value>A masons job is simple - they automatically know who the other masons are. Otherwise, they are a simple villager. Rolenames: Mason/Otter.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutDG">
    <value>
      Your ancestors had the ability to metamorph into others... while you don't have their full abilities, you can pick a player at the start of the game. If that player dies, you will become what they were.
      Note: If the player was converted to cult, you will take on their original role. All other normal rules apply: If they were Wild Child and their role model died, you will become a wolf. Otherwise, you will inherit their role model.
      The cult cannot convert the Doppelgänger (but can after the doppelganger switches roles). Also - the Doppelgänger can NOT win unless they have transformed. If at the end of the game, the Doppelgänger is still the same, they lose (exception: lover) Rolenames: Doppelganger/Chameleon
    </value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutCupid">
    <value>
      Love is in the air. As Cupid, you will choose two players at the start of the game. These two players will become madly in love! If one of them dies, the other will die of sorrow :(
      Note: Lovers will know who each other are, but not be told their roles. If the lovers are the last two alive, they win, regardless of teams. If the lovers are on different teams (villager + wolf), and one team wins (wolf), the lover (villager) wins as well. TL;DR if both lovers are alive at the end, and at least one of them was on the winning team, they both win together. Rolenames: Cupid/Lovebird
    </value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutHunter">
    <value>
      A trigger happy, vindictive player. As the hunter, you try to keep to yourself. However, when others come to visit you, they may find themselves dead, as your paranoia takes hold and you shoot. If the wolves attack you, you have a chance to take one of them with you. Otherwise, if you die, you will get a chance to shoot someone as you die.
      Note: For wolf attacks, the chance starts at 30%. If there is one wolf, the hunter has a 30% chance to kill the wolf (and survive). For each additional wolf, add 20% (2 wolves = 50%, 3 = 70%, etc). However - if there are multiple wolves, while you may kill one of them, you will still be outnumbered and killed.
      If the cult tries to convert you, they have a 50% chance to fail. If they fail, you have a 50% chance to kill one of them! Rolenames: Hunter/Bear
    </value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutSK">
    <value>That asylum was silly anyways. What a joke. You are free now however, back to business as usual - killing! The serial killer is a lone player, on their own team. They can win only if they are the last player alive (exception: lovers). As the serial killer, you can kill ANYONE - wolves, hunters, gunners, guardian angels, whatever. If the wolves try to attack you, you will kill one of them (random), and live. Rolenames: Serial Killer/Wasp</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutPara">
    <value>Para is a silly developer that likes to bark at people.  Maybe he's been messing with werewolves too long....Messing with werewolves is a very bad idea.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="EndTime">
    <value>Game Length: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <!--New strings, July the 8th -->

  <string key="Day">
    <!--0 - Day -->
    <value>Day {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NodeShutsDown">
    <value>Mistakes have been made. An error has occurred and this node has shut down :C</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SentPrivate">
    <value>I have PMed you the things.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="StartPM">
    <value>Send me a pm so I can PM you: @werewolfbot</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PMTrue">
    <value>Thanks for starting me up!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MustReplySmite">
    <value>You must reply to the user you want to smite.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WhatToDo">
    <value>What do? How do you wanna do this?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="JoinFromGroup">
    <value>There's no point to joining in a singleplayer game of werewolf! </value>
  </string>
  <string key="StartFromGroup">
    <value>No point in playing a singleplayer game. You must start a game from within a group chat!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PingInfo">
    <value>Reply process time: {0}\nCurrent CPU Usage: {1}%\nMessages per second: {2}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WhatLang">
    <value>What Language?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WhatVariant">
    <value>What Variant?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="LangSet">
    <value>Language set to {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GetLang">
    <value>Which language file do you want?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NoNodes">
    <value>There are no nodes online right now, please try again in a few seconds</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GroupCommandOnly">
    <value>That doesn't work here. You must run this command in a group.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NotGlobalAdmin">
    <value>Absolutely not. You aren't a global admin.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NotPara">
    <value>Stop it! You aren't Para!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Yes">
    <value>Sure.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="No">
    <value>No.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Allow">
    <value>Allowed</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Disallow">
    <value>Forbidden</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Show">
    <value>Show</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Hide">
    <value>Hide</value>
  </string>
  <!-- Game Mode Choices-->
  <string key="NormalOnly">
    <value>Normal Only</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ChaosOnly">
    <value>Chaos Only</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerChoice">
    <value>Player Choice</value>
  </string>

  <!-- Show Roles on End Game -->
  <string key="ShowNone">
    <value>Don't show any</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShowLiving">
    <value>Show only living players</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShowAll">
    <value>Show all players</value>
  </string>

  <string key="Cancel">
    <value>Cancel</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowFleeQ">
    <!-- note, there is NO space after {0}.  This is on purpose -->
    <value>Do you want to allow fleeing once the game has started?\nNote: players can still flee during join phase\nCurrent: Players can {0}flee</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowFleeA">
    <!-- note, there is NO space after {0}.  This is on purpose -->
    <value>Players will {0}be allowed to flee after game start</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MaxPlayersQ">
    <value>How many players would like to set as the maximum?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MaxPlayersA">
    <value>Max players set to {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShowRolesDeathQ">
    <value>Show or Hide roles on death?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShowRolesDeathA">
    <value>Roles will be {0} on death.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GameModeQ">
    <value>What game mode will the group be?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GameModeA">
    <value>Game mode set to {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShowRolesEndQ">
    <value>How do you want roles to be shown at the end?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShowRolesEndA">
    <value>Roles shown at end set to: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SetDayTimeQ">
    <value>Choose the base time (in seconds) for day time.   This will still be modified based on number of players.\nMinimum time added based on players is 60 seconds.  Default setting: {0}\nCurrent: {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SetDayTimeA">
    <value>Base day time set to {0} seconds</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SetNightTimeQ">
    <value>Choose the time (in seconds) for night time. Default setting: {0}\nCurrent:{1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SetNightTimeA">
    <value>Night time set to {0} seconds</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SetLynchTimeQ">
    <value>Choose the time (in seconds) for lynch voting. Default setting: {0}\nCurrent:{1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SetLynchTimeA">
    <value>Lynch voting time set to {0} seconds</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowFoolQ">
    <value>Allow fool as a role option?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowFoolA">
    <value>Fool as a role set to: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowTannerQ">
    <value>Allow tanner as a role option?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowTannerA">
    <value>Tanner as a role set to: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowCultQ">
    <value>Allow cult as a role option?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowCultA">
    <value>Cult as a role set to: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThankYou">
    <value>Thanks for the assistance. Have fun.</value>
  </string>
<string key="WhatLangGroup">
    <value>What language do you want to look for a group to play in?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HereIsList">
    <value>Here are the groups for {0}:</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Members">
    <value>Members</value>
  </string>
  <string key="StartMe">
    <value>Please start me so I can PM you</value>
  </string>
</strings>
