<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<!-- WEREWOLF FOR TELEGRAM: SINGAPORE (PUBLIC HOUSING) Language Pack. Learn more about Singapore from our language pack and the little references we have put in, for laughs! -->
<!-- Version 1.00: Created proudly by Donavan, Holypanda, Kylor, Darryl, Klinsmann, Kopi, Ian and Cyril! Moral support and vetting from Jayjay, Kaykay and Risa! -->
<!-- Version 1.01: Edited "serial killer" from KUMAR to Pontianak. Also language changes. -->
<!-- Version 1.02: Multiple values for many common strings. Adding a bit of variety. -->
<!-- Version 1.03: new strings.-->
<!-- Version 1.04: new death strings in line with the english.xml file.-->
<!-- This will be updated in tandem with the English language pack as far as possible. -->
<!-- If you would like to contribute to this language pack for more Singaporean flavour, please contact @donavancheah to see how it can be infused into the pack! -->
<strings>
  <language name="English - Singapore" base="English" variant="Singapore Version"/>
  <string key="NotInGame">
    <value>You don't appear to be in any HDB flats right now...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerStartedGame" isgif="true">
    <!-- 0 - Player name -->
    <value>{0} has started a game! Use /join to buy a HDB flat, and probably be chased out! :P</value>
    <value>A new BTO exercise has been started by {0}! Use /join to buy a HDB flat!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerStartedChaosGame" isgif="true">
    <!-- 0 - Player name -->
    <value>{0} has started a chaos game! Use /join to buy a HDB flat. and probably be chased out! :P</value>
    <value>A new chaotic BTO exercise has been started by {0}! Use /join to buy a HDB flat!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NoJoinGameRunning">
    <value>You can't join now! Next round of build-to-order (BTO) flats, please! </value>
  </string>
  <string key="AlreadyJoined">
    <value>You've already joined the queue!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MinuteLeftToJoin">
    <value>1 minute left to /join</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SecondsLeftToJoin">
    <!-- 0 - remaining seconds (number) -->
    <value>{0} seconds left to /join</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NotEnoughPlayers">
    <value>Not enough players, cancelling BTO exercise!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="StartingGameWait">
    <value>Game is starting, please wait while I assign roles and update the database.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="BannedForExploit">
    <!-- 0 - Player name -->
    <value>{0} is banned for attempting an exploit (no names starting with /)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ChangeNameToJoin">
    <!-- 0 - Player name -->
    <value>{0}, please change your name to partake in the build-to-order (BTO) exercise!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerLimitReached">
    <value>Sorry, the block is already full of residents!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerJoined">
    <!-- 0 - Player name -->
    <!-- 1 - current players -->
    <!-- 2 - Minimum players -->
    <!-- 3 - Maximum players -->
    <value>{0} has signed up for the build-to-order (BTO) flats! {1} in queue! Min. queue {2}, max. queue {3}.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PMTheBot">
    <!-- 0 - Player name -->
    <!-- 1 - bot username -->
    <value>{0} Please click the start button below or {1} and start me, so I can PM you your role. You may not stay in this estate until you do.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DeadFlee">
    <value>No point fleeing; you've already fled the estate!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Flee">
    <!-- 0 - Player name -->
    <value>{0} has sold his/her HDB flat! A new flat is now available!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerRoleWas">
    <!-- 0 - Player name -->
    <!-- 1 - Player role -->
    <value>{0} was {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CountPlayersRemain">
    <!-- 0 - Number of players -->
    <value>{0} residents remain.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DidntAsk">
    <value>Hey I didn't ask you anything yet!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NotPlaying">
    <value>You don't seem to be in this HDB flat...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NoPlayerName">
    <value>I can't find a resident by that name!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AnswerNonValid">
    <value>This answer is not valid!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolfVotedKill">
    <!-- 0 - wolf teammate name -->
    <!-- 1 - Victim name -->
    <value>{0} has voted to evict {1}.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerVotedLynch">
    <!-- 0 - Voter name -->
    <!-- 1 - Target name -->
    <value>{0} has voted to chase {1} away.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="IdleKill">
    <!-- 0 - player name -->
    <!-- 1 - player role -->
    <value>{0} was so busy {0} forgot to vote two nights in a row. Apparently, {0} has made it rich, and {0}'s would be moving to a condominium tomorrow! The rest of the residents glare at him with jealous stares. {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="TraitorTurnWolf">
    <value>You jealous resident!!! You are now the HDB agent.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ChoiceAccepted">
    <value>Choice accepted.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="BeholderSeer">
    <!-- 0 - seer name -->
    <value>\nThe hacktivist is {0}.</value>
    <value>\nAs far as you know, only {0} the hacktivist could have been of real help to the residents.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ApprenticeNowSeer">
    <!-- 0 - seer name -->
    <value>{0} was the hacktivist. Wanting to prove your degree's worth, you graduate to become the new hacktivist.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="BeholderNewSeer">
    <!-- 0 - apprentice name -->
    <!-- 1 - seer name -->
    <value>{0} has already graduated from his/her Computer Science course, and has now stepped up to fill {1}'s place as the new Hacktivist.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SeerSees">
    <!-- 0 - player name -->
    <!-- 1 - player role -->
    <value>You see {0} is {1}!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskLynch">
    <value>Who do you want to chase away from the HDB block?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskDetect">
    <value>Whose HDB unit do you want to fly your drone to?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskShoot">
    <!-- 0 - bullet count -->
    <value>Who do you want to shoot? {0} bullet(s) remain.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskVisit">
    <value>Who do you want to sell laksa to?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskSee">
    <value>Whose network do you want to hack into?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskGuard">
    <value>Whose illegal business do you want to defend?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskEat">
    <value>Who do you want to evict?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskHunt">
    <value>Who do you suspect of being a Money Lending Member (MLM)? Time to con somebody!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskRoleModel">
    <value>Who are your foster parents?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskConvert">
    <value>Who do you want to recruit as the newest Money Lending Member (MLM)?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DiscussWith">
    <!--Leave the leading spaces here please-->
    <!-- 0 - teammate names -->
    <value> Make sure you discuss with {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="And">
    <!--this is paired with "DiscussWith". again, leave the spaces!-->
    <value> and </value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoCursed">
    <value>You are a coward (cursed 😾). If the HDB agents (wolves) ever try to evict you, you will turn over a new leaf and start evicting those you used to work with in illegal enterprise!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoDetective">
    <value>You are the drone operator (detective 🕵). During the day, you may fly a drone to snoop on a resident (no nude pictures!). However, there is a 40% chance of the HDB agents (wolves) noticing an illegal drone outside!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoDrunk">
    <value>You are the drunkard (drunk 🍻). If the HDB agents (wolves) must trail you all the way to Bedok Reservoir (while drowning your sorrows at losing huge bets due to José Mourinho), the HDB agents will still need to visit your house the next night to clean it up.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoGuardianAngel">
    <value>You are the "啰哩啰嗦" (longwinded) auntie (Guardian Angel 👼). Each night, you may want to discuss with another resident the prospect of a joint collaboration. If the HDB agents (wolves) find you, your exceptionally fantastic mouth allows you to outspeak the HDB agent to the point that they simply give up and leave you and your friend alone. However, if you try pitching this idea to the HDB agents there is a 50% chance they will evict you because you have definitely broken the law! And don't think about the Pontianak (serial killer); you know better than to anger the resident ghost...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoGunner">
    <value>You are the shady NSF (gunner 🔫)! You somehow managed to smuggle SAF parts home, only to resell them through Tor (to supplement your pathetic allowance). If you hate someone for being noisy (up to 2), you could just go to their flat and shoot them in the head, but the lack of a suppressor means the whole block would hear the gunshot.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoHarlot">
    <value>You are the makcik (Malay for auntie) (harlot 💋). You sell laksa from your home illegally. The residents are more than happy to pay $2.50 for your laksa bowl, but if you try to sell it to the HDB agent (wolf), the law will ensnare you! If the HDB agent visits you while you are not at home, no one will know of your large industrial laksa cauldron, and nothing will happen to you.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoTraitor">
    <value>You are the jealous resident (traitor🖕). When all the HDB agents (wolves) have given up, you take over their job as the next-in-line. The hacktivist (seer) may identify you as either an unhappy envious resident or a HDB agent, so beware!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoWolf">
    <value>YOU ARE AN HDB AGENT (WOLF 🐺)!! XD It's time to decide, once per night, who you want to evict! Down with all the illegal activities in this HDB estate!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoSeer" >
    <value >You are the hacktivist (seer 👳). Each night, you may compromise a resident's network, knowing what the resident's real life is.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoVillager" >
    <value>You are one of those sad residents (villager 👱) who merely gambles away your salary on 4D and being envious over your other residents’ illegal HDB enterprises, but your knowledge of their illegal activity is enough to risk eviction!</value>
    <value>You were hoping to be a good businessman? Nah, you're really just a sad resident (villager 👱) who hopes to make it big in TOTO someday... dan gu gu! (wait long long!)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoTanner" >a
    <value >You are the attention seeker (tanner 👺). If majority of the HDB block wants to chase you away, you spread a conspiracy and plunge the flat prices of your ex-residents!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoWildChild" >
    <value >You are the orphan (wild child 👶). You never quite knew about your origins, except that your foster parents claimed you were picked up from the rubbish bin. However, if they ever leave someday, you'll be abandoned, and may have no choice but to join the HDB to feed yourself!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoBeholder" >
    <value >You are the network snooper (beholder 👁). You know who the real hacktivist is, as opposed to the script kiddie who does not do real damage.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoApprenticeSeer" >
    <value >You are the rogue Computer Science student (apprentice seer 🙇). Someday, if the resident hacktivist (seer) is gone, you must take over to help your fellow residents intercept the goody-two-shoes before they start evicting everyone.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoCultist" >
    <value >You are a Money Lending Member (MLM) (Cultist 👤). Sometimes businesses just need that little more "oomph". Knowing how desperate the estate is for "easy money", the MLM is who they go to, for money, only to be sucked into a pit of no return. (tl;dr: you're just a bloody ah long (loanshark) with a fancy title.)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoCultistHunter" >
    <value >You are the fake CPIB officer (Cultist Hunter 💂). Scaring the MLM is an extremely effective way to earn money. Only the MLM gets frightened with your antics, though; the makcik, hacktivist, among others know better than to fall for your fake CPIB badge.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="LynchTime" >
    <!-- 0 - number of seconds -->
    <value>
      Dusk draws near, and the residents gather to decide who they are chasing away this evening.
      Everyone now has {0} seconds to vote!
    </value>
  </string>
  <string key="DayTime" >
    <!-- 0 - number of seconds -->
    <value>It is now day time. All of you have {0} seconds to pretend to nurture the kampung spirit, or just ignore and buy 4D, hoping to retire early.</value>
    <value>It is now day time. Maybe it's time to make peace with your neighbours. {0} seconds before dusk hits!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NightTime" >
    <!-- 0 - number of seconds -->
    <value>Night has fallen. Everyone heads to bed, weary after another stressful day of work. Night players: you have {0} seconds to use your actions!</value>
    <value>Night has fallen. Everyone heads to bed, praying that no more strange things will happen to this estate. Night players: you have {0} seconds to use your actions!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="LynchKill" >
    <!-- 0 - player name -->
    <!-- 1 - player role -->
    <value>The residents have cast their votes, amid doubts and suspicions. {0} has been chased away with a broomstick! {1}</value>
    <value>The residents have voted for their choice of candidate, {0}. {0} has been swiftly glared at, and {0} knows to leave automatically, before the rotten eggs, tomatoes and cabbage gets thrown. {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="LynchTie" >
    <value>It looks like the gossip was in vain; nobody was chased away tonight! Everyone still has a flat!</value>
    <value>NATO (No action, talk only) SIA! Can't even decide who to evict? Everyone goes home, feeling pissed that the "chao betrayer" hasn't been fished out.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NoLynchVotes" >
    <value >Something is fishy, for no one voted! No angry aunties chasing the scum of the HDB block out!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DetectiveEaten" >
    <!-- 0 - victim name -->
    <value>Where's {0}? They find {0}'s drone smashed on the covered walkway, with traces of an eviction notice for illegal flying.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardianEaten" >
    <!-- 0 - victim name -->
    <value >Morning comes, strangely abandoned along the roadside with her marketing trolley is {0}, the 啰哩啰嗦 (Long-winded) Auntie (Guardian Angel). The HDB agents must have evicted her, and all she had left was her one week's worth of groceries.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GunnerEaten" >
    <!-- 0 - victim name -->
    <value >Morning comes, only to reveal an eviction notice and an SAF notice charging the shady NSF (gunner), {0}, in court, for his smuggling enterprise! {0} has been evicted!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SeerEaten" >
    <!-- 0 - victim name -->
    <value >Night-time comes, and a notice was pasted at {0}'s door. The Hacktivist (seer) was caught working over-time! Some wire tappers and an old monitor were left in the bulk refuse chute, testament that he was being evicted.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DrunkEaten" >
    <!-- 0 - victim name -->
    <value>The eerie silence spooked the loudest auntie, who woke everyone up, in fears that there were ghosts. Indeed, {0}, the drunkard (drunk) had been caught and evicted. No more smashed Tiger Beer bottles, but also no more regular customer at the Singapore Pools outlet.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="FoolEaten" >
    <!-- 0 - victim name -->
    <value>The residents wakes up to the smell of burning plastic, only to see the unit of {0} burnt down from an electrical overload ! The stupid script kiddie (fool) DDoS-ed himself while the HDB agents were visiting! The HDB agents quickly evicted him on counts of misconduct.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DefaultEaten" >
    <!-- 0 - victim name -->
    <!-- 1 - victim role -->
    <value>As everyone rises in the morning, they see an eviction notice pasted on {0}'s house.\n{1}</value>
    <value>OH NO! {0}'s house is now empty! All that remains is an eviction notice! the illegal business which {0} used to run has ceased! \n{1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterKilledCultist">
    <!-- 0 - victim name -->
    <value>A noticeable stench of rotten pig is coming from the trash bin near {0}'s house! A Money Lending Member (cultist) has been "busted" by the fake CPIB officer (cultist hunter), and his pigs' heads disposed in the trash! Ah Long say Ah Long lah! Simi money-lending member? (Don't say you are a money-lending member when you are just a loanshark!)</value>
    <value>Morning comes, and it seems that an MLM, {0}, has left the HDB estate in shame! The "CPIB" has performed a raid and all the neighbours now know the one responsible for the pigs' heads and random blood trails. Ah Long say Ah Long lah! Simi money-lending member? (Don't say you are a money-lending member when you are just a loanshark!)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NoAttack" >
    <value>The residents gather the next morning at the void deck, to sighs of relief - it appears there no one lost their home. Praise the HDB for their magnanimity.</value>
    <value>HENG ARH! (Lucky us!) Nobody seems to have been evicted last night.</value>
    <value>Someone volunteers to perform a headcount. Everyone seems to be present, which is good. Maybe the estate isn't so spooky after all, considering how this place is well-known for "mysterious" evictions.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CursedBitten" >
    <value>You have been visited by the HDB agents (wolves) for eviction. As you were the coward (cursed), you silently admitted your guilt, promising to work with the HDB agents (wolves) in exchange for your "safety"!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolfTeam">
    <!-- 0 - teammate names -->
    <value>Your HDB agent colleague(s): {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CursedBittenToWolves" >
    <!-- 0 - victim name -->
    <value >{0} was visited... but admitted to her illegal deeds! You felt that he would make a great HDB agent (wolf)! Congratulations on your new colleague!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolvesEatYou" isgif="false" >
    <value>Oh no! The HDB agents (wolves) have evicted you!</value>
    <value>Unlucky day for you! The HDB agents (wolves) have evicted you!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolvesEatDrunk" >
    <!-- 0 - victim name -->
    <value >Oh no! {0} was a drunkard (drunk)! Evicting him took far longer than expected because his house was a fire hazard! You must re-visit his house tomorrow night just to clear the crates of Tiger Beer he was trying to resell!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardWolf" >
    <value >You tried to defend an HDB agent's (wolf's) "business"! Of course it was legal, and you were running the illegal business! You have been evicted.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardSaved" >
    <!-- 0 - saved player name -->
    <value >You have defended {0}'s from the HDB agents (wolves) and/or Pontianak (serial killer)!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardNoAttack" >
    <!-- 0 - player name -->
    <value >No one wanted to evict {0}, wasting your precious time when you could have been coaching your daughter for the PSLE.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardEmptyHouse">
    <!-- 0 - player name -->
    <value>You visited {0}, but perhaps they were out!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardSavedYou" >
    <value>A 啰哩啰嗦 (long-winded) Auntie (Guardian Angel) squabbled with the HDB agents (wolves) without you opening the door! All you heard was an unrecognisable string of "colourful" words. Who cares? As long as you can keep your flat, you're happy!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotEaten" >
    <!-- 0 - player name -->
    <value>The makcik (harlot) chose the wrong night to QC her laksa cauldron! The HDB agents have discovered her illegal business! {0} has been evicted!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotNotHome" >
    <!-- 0 - player name -->
    <value>Odd... {0} was not home! How to evict someone who is not at home?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotFuckWolf" >
    <!-- 0 - player name -->
    <value>You send some freshly made laksa to {0}, only to be confronted by an HDB agent (wolf). The HDB agent evicts you for your illegal laksa business.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotFuckedWolfPublic" >
    <!-- 0 - player name -->
    <value>Makcik (Harlot) visited the HDB agent last night. Her illegal business was discovered and had to be wound up! {0} has been forcibly evicted from the HDB flat.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotFuckedVictimPublic" >
    <!-- 0 - harlot name -->
    <!-- 1 - victim name -->
    <value>Makcik (Harlot) visited her best friend {1}, only to see an HDB agent (wolf) evicting {1}. Noticing makcik's illegal laksa, the HDB agent also turned on {0} and evicted her as well!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotVisitNonWolf" >
    <!-- 0 - target name -->
    <value>You see {0} enjoyed your laksa so much, both of you finished up an entire cauldron of it! There goes your diet! At least this wasn't the HDB agent (wolf).</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotVisitYou" >
    <value>Weird... you clearly remembered makcik (harlot) selling her premium laksa, but you couldn't quite remember who the makcik was. Maybe Alzheimer's has set in.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DetectiveCaught" >
    <!-- 0 - detective name -->
    <value>You caught {0}'s drone! That must be the drone operator (detective)!</value>
    <value>You hear the buzzing of {0}'s drone! Obviously that's the drone operator (detective)!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DetectiveSnoop" >
    <!-- 0 - target name -->
    <!-- 1 - target role -->
    <value>Your drone has taken a 4k picture of {0}; that's the {1}.</value>
    <value>The lens of your drone was a little clouded, but it revealed {0} to be the {1}.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotShot" >
    <!-- 0 - gunner's name -->
    <!-- 1 - Harlot's name -->
    <value>Makcik’s (Harlot's) laksa caused the shady NSF (gunner), {0}, diarrhoea, forcing him to take MC and not be able to smuggle parts. The shady NSF got revenge and the makcik, {1} is shot.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DefaultShot" >
    <!-- 0 - Gunner's name -->
    <!-- 1 - target name -->
    <!-- 2 - Target's revealed name ( Target was a role) -->
    <value>Suddenly, a SAR-21 was fired. The block turns to see {0} standing over {1}'s body, the SAR-21 still aimed at the head. {2}</value>
    <value>The SAR-21 suddenly goes off! {1} lies in a pool of blood, with {0} standing over the dead soul, the SAR-21 still aimed at the head. {2}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolfWins" isgif="false" >
    <value>Enough with the conniving residents! The HDB agent has won!</value>
    <value>The HDB agent has outsmarted the residents! The HDB agent has won!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolvesWin" isgif="false" >
    <value>Enough with the conniving residents! The HDB agents have won!</value>
    <value>The HDB agents have outsmarted the residents! The HDB agent has won!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="VillageWins" isgif="true" >
    <value>All the pesky HDB agents have been dealt with! The residents have won and can continue their illegal enterprises!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="TannerWins" isgif="false" >
    <value>Oh no! You chased the Attention Seeker out! HardwareZone and EDMW are now full of conspiracy articles such as paranormal spottings, plunging the value of the HDB flat!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RemainingPlayersEnd">
    <value>Remaining players in the flat, roles, and team:</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultistVotedConvert" >
    <!-- 0 - Voter's name -->
    <!-- 1 - target name -->
    <value >{0} has voted to renegotiate with and recruit {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultConvertCultHunter">
    <!-- 0 - Yougest Cultist (killed)'s name' -->
    <!-- 1 - CultHunter's name -->
    <value>{0} was provided a pig's head, the negotiation forms, and went to recruit {1}, but they were the fake CPIB agent! RUN! Gosh, we lost {0} to the "CPIB"!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultHunterKilledCultVisit">
    <!-- 0 - Youngest Cultist's name -->
    <!-- 1 - Number of cultists left -->
    <value>{0} came to your house last night, ready to recruit you, but you managed to catch the slowest-running MLM and scare {0}'s wits; {1} remain! Clearly that ah long (loanshark) was too new!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultConvertYou">
    <value>The Money Lending Members (MLM) (cultists) have recruited you, because you could not repay their debts! Once per night, you will be sent to hang a pig's head demanding for repayment... or a "job offer" with you! (Just your luck you are now an ah long (loanshark) with a pretty name, that's all!)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultTeam">
    <!-- 0 - Number of cultists -->
    <value>Cultists: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultJoin">
    <!-- 0 - new cultist's name -->
    <value>{0} has become a Money Lending Member!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultVisitEmpty">
    <!-- 0 - Newest cultist's name -->
    <!-- 1 - target name -->
    <value>{0} was sent to do your dirty work, and recruit {1}... but no one was home! All you could do was to hang a "notice".</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultWins" isgif="true">
    <value>All the HDB agents have been busted, and the only people left standing are all Money-Lending Members! The MLM has won!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterVisitDead">
    <!-- 0 - target name -->
    <value>On a lead, you wanted to "bust" {0}, but the flat seemed empty: were they already evicted?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterFindCultist">
    <!-- 0 - target name -->
    <value>You go into {0}'s house and find them drying their pigs' heads and counting dirty cash. You quickly put on your "CPIB badge" and cleanse the house of all its valuables. The MLM feared the "CPIB" so much that the MLM went on the run the next morning. After all, he's really just an ah long (loanshark), don't keng (pretend) to be a financial institute!</value>
  </string>
  <!-- 0 - target name -->
  <string key="HunterFailedToFind">
    <value>You go to {0}'s house, but there is no pigs' head. You return home, convinced that {0} is not a MLM, but disappointed that you could not put your "CPIB badge" to good use.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WildChildToWolves">
    <!-- 0 - Werechild's name -->
    <value>{0}'s foster parents are gone! In their desperation to survive, they have been employed as an HDB agent!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WildChildTransform">
    <!-- 0 - role's name -->
    <!-- 1 - teamate's names -->
    <value>{0}, your foster parents, are gone! To survive, you sign up on Careers@Gov to be an HDB agent! Your new teammates are: {1}</value>
  </string>
  <!-- Villager, Drunk, Harlot, Seer, Traitor, GuardianAngel, Detective, Wolf, Cursed, Gunner, Tanner, Fool, WildChild, Beholder, ApprenticeSeer, Cultist, CultistHunter-->
  <!-- Do NOT change the emoji's, even if you are translating werewolf in a non-standard mode! -->
  <string key="Villager">
    <value>a Sad Resident (a Villager) 👱</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Drunk">
    <value>the Drunkard (the Drunk) 🍻</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Harlot">
    <value>the Makcik (the Harlot) 💋</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Seer">
    <value>the Hacktivist (the Seer) 👳</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Traitor">
    <value>the Jealous Resident (the Traitor) 🖕</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardianAngel">
    <value>the 啰哩啰嗦 (Long-winded) Auntie (the Guardian Angel) 👼</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Detective">
    <value>the Drone Operator (the Detective) 🕵</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Wolf">
    <value>an HDB Agent (a Werewolf) 🐺</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Cursed">
    <value>the Coward (the Cursed) 😾</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Gunner">
    <value>the Shady NSF (the Gunner) 🔫</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Tanner">
    <value>the Attention Seeker (the Tanner) 👺</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Fool">
    <value>the Script Kiddie (the Fool) 🃏</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WildChild">
    <value>the Orphan (the Wild Child) 👶</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Beholder">
    <value>the Network Snooper (the Beholder) 👁</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ApprenticeSeer">
    <value>the Rogue Computer Science Student (the Apprentice Seer) 🙇</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Cultist">
    <value>a Money-Lending Member (MLM) (a Cultist) 👤</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultistHunter">
    <value>the Fake CPIB Officer (the Cultist Hunter) 💂</value>
  </string>
  <!-- These are for the player list -->
  <string key="RanAway">
    <value>离家出走 (Ran Away From Home)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Dead">
    <value>😭 No Longer Living Here</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Alive">
    <value>🙂 A Grateful Resident</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayersAlive">
    <value>Players Alive</value>
  </string>
  <!-- New strings 4 MAY 2016-->
  <string key="Mason">
    <value>a Gossip Auntie (a Mason) 👷</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoMason">
    <value>You are a Gossip Auntie (a Mason) 👷. You kao-pei (complain) so much about the HDB that you may now have a band of aunties (if there are, they will be stated) with common interests. </value>
  </string>
  <string key="MasonEaten">
    <!-- 0 - dead man's name -->
    <value>As everyone rises, they find the eviction notice AND a Forum opinion article in the Straits Times defaming the HDB. {0}, one of your gossip aunties, has been evicted!</value>
    <value>Looks like the HDB agents were too kiasi (Hokkien for afraid to die)! {0}, one of the gossip aunties, was named, shamed and lambasted on a Forum opinion article in the Straits Times! Eviction quickly happened to {0}!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MasonTeam">
    <value> The other gossip aunties are: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <!-- new strings May 6 2016-->
  <string key="CultTargetDead">
    <!-- 0 - Youngest cultists name -->
    <value>Your newest MLM heads over to {0}'s house to recruit them, but instead finds a ghostly house, scaring your wits. Maybe the HDB agents (wolves) beat you to it... eh? Or perhaps the owner was just enjoying a crass joke.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardBlockedWolf">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>The HDB agents head to {0}'s house to evict them, but they are met by an auntie who squabbled with you for the entire night! Unable to win the auntie's "rojak" (mix) of English, Malay, Chinese, Tamil, with a pinch of Hokkien vulgarities, the HDB agents gave up, returned to their homes, unable to fulfil their KPI.</value>
  </string>
  <!-- new strings May 9 2016-->
  <string key="CultUnableToConvert">
    <!-- 0 - newest  -->
    <!-- 1 - target's name -->
    <value>You send {0} to try to renegotiate with and recruit {1}, however they were unconvinced by your high interest rates. :(</value>
  </string>
  <!-- new string May 12 2016-->
  <string key="NameExists">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <!-- 1 - name -->
    <value>@{1}, a player with the name {0} has already applied for a BTO flat. Please change your name to join.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotDiscoverCult">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>You send some freshly made laksa to {0}, but upon leaving, you question why there was a fresh pig’s head in the kitchen sink. You wonder if your neighbour has been paying you with dirty money, and greatly suspect the MLM is roaming around.</value>
    <value>Did you just serve freshly-made laksa to {0}, the money-lending member who really is an ah long (loanshark)? Maybe you should inform the estate...</value>
  </string>
  <!-- new string May 13 2016-->
  <string key="Was">
    <value>was</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GenericDeathNoReveal">
    <!-- 0 - Dead's name -->
    <value>Everyone wakes up in the morning, and notices that {0} is not around. They check the house to find the eviction notice pasted on {0}'s door.</value>
    <value>As the residents gather as the sun rises, they find {0} missing, who was evicted somehow last night.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MasonConverted">
    <!-- 0 - mason's name -->
    <value>{0} didn't show up for the daily gossip session. How strange...</value>
  </string>
  <!-- new string May 16 2016-->
  <string key="FleeDisabled">
    <value>Selling your flat while the game is running has been disabled by the group admin!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="IsDead">
    <!-- used when gunner shoots a player -->
    <value>is a goner.</value>
    <value>is now called "ex-neighbour".</value>
  </string>

  <!-- MORE STRINGS May 16, 2016 -->
  <string key="AdminAdded">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>{0} added to admin list. Use /config to change group settings.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AlreadyInGame">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>You are already in a BTO exercise! ({0})</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MultipleGames">
    <value>Your group has managed to do extra BTOs. Killing extras.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GroupQueue">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <!-- 1 - target's name -->
    <value>Your group is currently in the queue. Position: {0} / {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MaintBreak">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>Sorry, I'm about to start a short maintenance break, you can't start a game right now.\nWaiting on {0} games to end...\nGo to @werewolfdev for more information</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MaxGames">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <!-- 1 - target's name -->
    <value>Sorry, max concurrent games has been reached ({0}). \nPosition in queue: {1} / {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SkipQueue">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>{0} is a preferred group, and has skipped the queue!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NoGame">
    <value>There is no BTO ongoing. Start a new BTO with /startgame or start a chaos BTO with /startchaos</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GroupAdminOnly">
    <value>Only a group admin can run this command.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShuttingDown">
    <value>After this game, I am shutting down for maintenance.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShuttingDownUpdate">
    <value>After this game, I am shutting down momentarily for an update (automated).</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NullIdAdmin">
    <value>UserId was null. Are you sure you sent this as a reply?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AlreadyAdmin">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>{0} is already an admin!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NotAdmin">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>{0} is not an admin!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AdminRemoved">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>{0} removed from admin list.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="LanguageSet">
    <!-- 0 - language's name -->
    <value>Language set to {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NoSeer">
    <value>No hacktivist!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="TimesUp">
    <value>Time's up!</value>
    <value>Too slow!</value>
  </string>
  <!-- new strings june 10 2016 -->
  <string key="RoleInfoCupid">
    <value>You are the Matchmaker (cupid 🏹)! Although a dying trade, parents still approach you to matchmake their kids. Choose 2 unwilling parties to wed and satisfy their parents (and your pockets), so that they can get a BTO and stop pissing their parents off!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoDoppelganger">
    <value>You are the imitator (doppelganger 🎭). The MOE has taught you well. You have learnt to memorise the 词语手册 (book of phrases) back and forth and remembered every single organic chemistry reaction. However, you dream of actually living a life. What better than to imitate someone whom you always looked up to, so that you can live that person’s life when that person no longer lives in the estate!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoHunter">
    <value>You are the tape-recording auntie (hunter 🎯). Everyone fears talking to you because they don't know whose scandal may be exposed, and so no one really likes talking to this auntie. Even the MLM fears you for fear that they will be exposed. If an HDB agent comes by, there is a chance she will dig out sordid information on Tor on the number of mistresses the HDB agent has in JB, causing the HDB agent himself to leave in shame!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoSerialKiller">
    <value>You are the PONTIANAK!!! (serial killer 🔪) Everyone else is human, but humans fear ghosts! Every night, you may scare someone! The only exception is if you encounter someone who is speaking to the rambly auntie, who will then turn on you and rant so much that you give up!t</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CupidChosen">
    <value>You have been forced by your parents to wed. {0} is even worse than Patricia Mok or Mark Lee, but you accept that you need to get a BTO after all. Your goal is for both of you to survive. If one of you disappears (dies, gets evicted, gets scared out of your wits, chased away), the other one will no longer be eligible for a BTO under age 35, and hence commit suicide (even if illegal).</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterLynchedChoice">
    <value>The residents has chosen to chase you away! This is your last chance, choose to expose someone's scandal and be chased away together!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterNoChoiceLynched">
    <value>{0} fumbles for her iPhone containing scandals of everyone, but cannot get it in time, and was chased away with a broomstick.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterSkipChoiceLynched">
    <value>{0} grabs her iPhone, only to realise, being such an auntie, she forgot her unlock password.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterKilledFinalLynched">
    <!-- 0 - hunter's name -->
    <!-- 1 - target's name -->
    <!-- 2 - target's role -->
    <value>Just before the Irritated Auntie (hunter) was chased away, {0} spills the beans on {1} having an extra-marital affair, and was chased away as well! {2}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterShotChoice">
    <value>You've been hit! In your last moments, you have the chance to expose someone's dirty secret!</value>
    <value>You've been hit! With your dying breath, which neighbour's secrets do you want to expose?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterNoChoiceShot">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>The blow to {0} was too much, so much that she could not decide who to inflict karma on...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterSkipChoiceShot">
    <!-- 0 - hunter's name -->
    <value>As {0} lays there, gasping for their final breaths, she babbles incoherently about scandals, but all they heard was "scandal" and "visits to JB".</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterKilledFinalShot">
    <!-- 0 - hunter -->
    <!-- 1 - target's name -->
    <!-- 2 - target's role -->
    <value>Dying, {0} falls to the ground.... but not without exposing the dirty secrets of {1}, who the residents than chased out as well! {2}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultConvertSerialKiller">
    <value>{0} sneaks over to {1}'s house, pops open the door, and is immediately greeted by the Pontianak!!! {1} frightens {0} so badly {0} swore to leave the HDB estate with immediate effect! D:</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterShotWolfMulti">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>The HDB agents (wolves) tried to evict the scandalous auntie (hunter) last night, but a government conspiracy about the HDB was being exposed! {0} has been selected as the scapegoat to be the "less than honourable" public servant.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterShotWolf">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>The HDB agents (wolves) tried to evict the scandalous auntie (hunter) last night, but the HDB agent, {0}, was counter-exposed for adultery. The HDB agent had to leave in double shame.</value>
  </string>t
  <string key="SerialKillerKilledWolf">
    <value>The HDB agents (wolves) had hoped to evict someone from their flat, but were instead greeted by Pontianak!!! {0} was the the front man, and turned pale upon seeing the abomination. He decided to tell his boss he would change job the next day and move out!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DefaultKilled">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <!-- 1 - target's role -->
    <value>The middle of the night did not go by silently! A strange shout from {0} meant only one thing: the pontianak has struck again! Strangely {0} did not try to move out even earlier, but {0} had already left the HDB estate by morning. {1}.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardBlockedKiller">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>You tried to scare {0}, but the 啰哩啰嗦 (Long-winded) auntie droned on and on... even after you had long drifted away.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultConvertHunter">
    <!-- 0 - Youngest Cultist's name -->
    <!-- 1 - target's name -->
    <value>The cult sends {0} to try to recruit {1}, but TNP reported of the MLM the next morning and {0} left due to shame.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultConvertSerialKiller">
    <!-- 0 - Youngest Cultist's name -->
    <!-- 1 - target's name -->
    <value>The cult sends {0} to try to recruit {1}, but the Pontianak scared {0}! {0} dropped his pig's head, ran for his sanity, and moved out the next morning!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardKiller">
    <value>You tried to defend the ghost (you really think that was a good idea?), but the Pontianak opened the door! Finally you were at a loss of words, and quickly went to pack your belongings, leaving this haunted HDB block!!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotFuckKiller">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>You tried to sell laksa to {0}, but a Pontianak greeted you at the door. Dropping your bowl, you hurriedly flee with your giant cauldron. PONTIANAK IS TRUE!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotFuckKillerPublic">
    <value>The estate notices a white makcik with laksa all over her. Apparently she visited the Pontianak last night. {0} will leave the estate by morning.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGToMason">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>The imitator {0} has now become a gossip auntie, just like you!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGTransformToMason">
    <!-- 0 - dead mason's name -->
    <!-- 1 - mason collegues's name -->
    <value>{0} has disappeared from the estate, and you copy all her gossipy behaviour. Your new gossip auntie friend(s) (if any) is/are: {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGToCult">
    <!-- 0 - new cultist's name -->
    <value>The imitator {0} has learnt how to spray O$P$ and pretend to be a proper financial institute, joining the ranks of the MLM, just like you!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGTransformToCult">
    <!-- 0 - role's name -->
    <!-- 1 - teammates's name -->
    <value>{0} has disappeared from the estate, and you pick up a can of red paint and illegal wads of cash after raiding his flat. Your fellow MLM (if any) are: {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGToWolf">
    <!-- 0 - DG's name -->
    <value>The imitator {0} has now got a university degree in Marketting, just like you!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGTransformToWolf">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <!-- 1 - teammates's name -->
    <value>{0} has left, and you ransacked his flat for all his books on HDB doctrine after getting a job at Careers@Gov. Your fellow agents (if any) are: {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SerialKillerWins" isgif="true">
    <value>The only person left standing is the PONTIANAK! THE GHOST ROAMS FREE!</value>
    <value>No more humans?! THE PONTIANAK IS THE LAST ONE FLOATING!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskKill">
    <value>Who do you want to scare?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="LoverDied">
    <!-- 0 - dead's name -->
    <!-- 1 - lover's name -->
    <!-- 2 - roles -->
    <value>With {0} vacating the flat, {1} "rushes over and falls", crying that they're no longer eligible for a new BTO flat 💔. Having already fallen out with their parents, {1} has also decided to pack their bags and leave the HDB estate (and be homeless). {2}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskDoppelganger">
    <value>Who do you want to copy if they ever vacate their flat?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskCupid1">
    <value>Who do you want to force a marriage on? Choose the first player</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskCupid2">
    <value>Who do you want to force a marriage on? Choose the second player</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Hunter">
    <value>the Tape-recording Auntie (the Hunter) 🎯</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Cupid">
    <value>the Matchmaker (the Cupid) 🏹</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SerialKiller">
    <value>the PONTIANAK! (the Serial Killer) 🔪</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Doppelgänger">
    <value>the Imitator (the Doppelgänger) 🎭</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CupidChosen">
    <!-- 0 - lover's name -->
    <value>The curse of the forced marriage! Now you must buy a BTO with {0} or else the parents will eventually nag you to madness! If your other "loved" one disappears, you would rather flee the HDB block 💔, but if both of you make it to the end, you have the entire block to yourself!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NewWCRoleModel">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>You have become the Intern. You watch {0}, in the hope that he or she does not fall to the HDB agents! However, you will be quick to turn your internship contract permanent if he or she gets evicted!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="LoversWin">
    <value>Everyone else is dead except the forced couple! They now have the whole block to themselves to cultivate their love; maybe they'll eventually truly love each other!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HunterKilledVisiter">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <!-- 1 - role -->
    <value>At the playground below, multiple copies of TNP featured a scandal on {0}. Looks like they tried to talk to the tape-recording auntie last night! {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultAttempt">
    <value>A MLM tried to sell you a pyramid scheme with a pig's head, but you knew better not to believe in such snake oil. After all, trusting in the ah long (loanshark) is tantamount to giving up your life!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AlreadyOnWaitList">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>You are already on the wait list for the next BTO on {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AddedToWaitList">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>You have been added to the wait list for the next BTO on {0}. I will PM you when the next game is starting.\nWhile waiting, why not browse the store? https://teespring.com/stores/werewolf-for-telegram</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NotifyNewGame">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>A new BTO round is starting in {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SerialKillerWinsOverpower">
    <!-- 0 - SK's name -->
    <!-- 1 - target's name -->
    <value>Morning comes, and the remaining two residents walk/float to the nearby fishmonger. {0} takes a look at {1}, goes "Peek-a-boo" and {1} fled from the estate at lightning speed.</value>
    <value>Morning comes, and the remaining two residents were sighted at the void deck. {1} realises that {0} isn't even human, and disappears at lightning speed!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NoWinner" isgif="true">
    <value>The HDB block is strangely empty... while it's perfect for an en-bloc, no one can carry it out.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SKHunterEnd">
    <!-- 0 - SK's name -->
    <!-- 1 - Hunter's name -->
    <value>As the sun rises, {0} and {1} walk out to the nearby fishmonger. {0} tries to scare {1}, only for {1} to upload less than flattering videos of the Pontianak onto EDMW. The housing estate is damned, and no one is left, what a joke of the block.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleModelChosen">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <value>You failed to make a choice, so the Father, Son and the Holy Goh has chosen for you: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Won">
    <value>Won</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Lost">
    <value>Lost</value>
  </string>
  <string key="IdleCount">
    <!-- 0 - player's name -->
    <!-- 1 - idle count -->
    <value>Player {0} has abandoned his neighbours by not voting {1} times in the past 24 hours.</value>
  </string>
  <!--New strings 7th of July-->
  <!--If you are translating werewolf in a non-standard mode (eg. Mafia, Pokémon and similar) please put the role and the emoji in front of the string.
  For example in Mafia, AboutMason would be:
  Caporegime 👷\nYou are a caporegime blah blah
  -->a
  <string key="AboutVG">
    <value>Villager? What do you think we are, some happy-go-lucky people?\n \nThis is Singapore! You mean sad HDB resident! (Villager) 👱! While you don't really know what your neighbours are up to, you uphold the BRO CODE: don't paotou (whistle-blow) your neighbours! However, there has been talk of the HDB clamping down on "illegal business" and the MLM spreading its wings! You don't want to have no neighbours left, do you, so stop the HDB agents from evicting your neighbours!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutSeer">
    <value>Shhhh! What I do is confidential and highly illegal! *runs a port scanner*\n \nThe Hacktivist (Seer) 👳 is known to pwn networks. Your job of identifying all who threaten your neighbours' illegal activities is so highly-valued that the HDB agents will certainly see you as a prized asset to evict first.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutWw">
    <value>Werewolves? Are you really sure? *takes out a dossier of sales papers*\n \nThe HDB Agent (Werewolf) 🐺  is just as brutal, though. They call it "cleansing the HDB block" of all illegal activity, when they are probably just breaking all the bro codes in the HDB block. \nThe rumor is, a Coward will surrender on first sight of the HDB agents.\nBut HDB agents are not invincible; epic litterbugs and drunkands make them much slower at getting to the heart of all these illegal activities, for they must call the Town Council down to clean up!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutHarlot">
    <value>Sex? Sorry! I sell other delicious delicacies instead! \n \nThe makcik (Malay for auntie) (Harlot) 💋 that everyone loves!! \nYou sell laksa from your home illegally. The residents are more than happy to pay $2.50 for your laksa bowl, but if you try to sell it to the HDB agent, the law will ensnare you! \nIf the HDB agent visits you while you are not at home, no one will know of your large industrial laksa cauldron, and nothing will happen to you.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutDrunk">
    <value>Tiger, Heineken or Guinness... *orders 3 crates of beer* \n \nThe Drunkard (Drunk) 🍻 drinks thrice daily (especially when watching the Barclays Premier League), leaves a trail of alcohol and never cleans up. He is often caught drinking at Bedok Reservoir after 10.30 pm to drown his sorrows with his bad football bets, which is illegal! But the HDB agents must follow your trail, tiring them out for a night if they decide to evict you. Please don't accidentally fall into the reservoir!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutCursed">
    <value>Curses, there are none, but cowardice plenty. \n \nYou are the Coward (Cursed) 😾. You have watched how the HDB agents have moved in ever so swiftly each night, looked around and evicted your less-than-obedient neighbours. Thankfully you have consulted a lawyer from Lee and Lee to argue your way into joining the ranks of the HDB agents should they ever come visiting...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutTraitor">
    <value>Jealousy has often resulted in the worst betrayals of the bro code...\n \nI heard we have a Jealous Resident (Traitor) 🖕 in our block. He cannot cook like the makcik, smuggle like the shady NSF or hack like the hacktivist. Going for SkillsFuture did nothing to help him. While there are HDB agents still around he hopes to leverage their enforcement to keep their businesses in check, but when they are all gone he may have to do it himself...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutGA">
    <value>In every neighbourhood there is always this auntie who can talk for days on end and never run out of saliva or ammunition...\n \nThat's the 啰哩啰嗦 (Long-Winded) Auntie (Guardian Angel) 👼 already. She learnt from the best of the best! Watching Taiwanese dramas such as 爱 (LOVE) on Channel 8 was indeed useful in sounding like a broken record! Having fine-tuned this skill against any smooth-tongued people such as the MLM or anyone from the government, the 啰哩啰嗦 auntie is in high demand, except that she cannot be in two places at one time...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutDetective">
    <value>Detective? That's in the times of Sherlock! \n \nIn times of the Smart Nation, we have the Drone Operator (Detective) 🕵 ! Mistrust of the HDB agents have led to many keeping their doors closed, but flying a drone and snooping into flats, while highly illegal, is probably the best way to find out the HDB agents within! Be careful, drones are highly visible, and there is a 40% chance the HDB agents see the drone, antenna, and the smart alec responsible for flying it!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutGunner">
    <value>Serving National Service as a full-time national serviceman (NSF) is sometimes a chore, so why not do something with it?\n \nThe Shady NSF (Gunner) 🔫 is a conscript with a very smart head. While his bunkmates prefer "bribing" doctors and acting to get away with MCs, the shady NSF exploits the system to sell valuable equipment through Tor, to supplement his otherwise meagre allowance! He even has a SAR-21 at home, only waiting for an unlucky victim who crosses his path...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutTanner">
    <value>You go onto Tinder, Bigo, Instagram, Snapchat e.t.c. in the hope to be famous, but you never have enough followers.\n \nYou are the Attention Seeker (Tanner) 👺. All you know is how to exploit social media for its worst features. If the HDB estate wants you to leave, you won't leave before using your last bits of your dataplan to post conspiracies about the estate on Hardwarezone and EDMW that ghosts exist, among other spooky features. That automatically ruins everyone's day, plunging the price of their flats! The power of social media... in the hands of merely one prickly soul...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutFool">
    <value>While there are hacktivists, there are also stupid script kiddies...\n \nOverconfidence is always in huge supply, and in the Script Kiddie (Fool)🃏 there is aplenty. Just because he has watched some self-hack videos and read articles by someone who has attended DEFCON, he thinks he can hack, when really, he's just pushing traffic onto 127.0.0.1. WHAT A FOOL!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutCult">
    <value>Ah, I know what you are thinking about... those buggers hanging pigs' heads while claiming they come from some financial institution.\n \nThere are people who are Money-Lending Members (MLM) (Cultist) 👤! Well, the residents have illegal enterprises that will never get bank loans, so perhaps it's a great income opportunity to speak to them regarding "easy credit".</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutCH">
    <value>"The rise in sex scams on WeChat hints that your illegal enterprise, perhaps, should be scamming the scammer"\n \nThe fake Corrupt Practices Investigation Bureau (CPIB) Officer (Cult Hunter) 💂 revels in scaring his fellow residents! He does not really have the tools to catch anyone with syndicates, but a pig's head is a dead giveaway. For some fun, visiting them means a MLM gets so frightened he gladly pays up! If the HDB agents ever catch you... you may well be hit by double charges!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutWC">
    <value>Where do I come from?\n \nThe orphan (Wild Child) 👶 never had a clue of his origins (maybe the rubbish chute). However, if his foster parents suddenly leave, or get evicted, he'll be all alone, and will have to find a job, especially since his fellow neighbours allowed the travesty of making his foster parents leave...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutAppS">
    <value>Ah, the apprentice? The one studying Computer Science at the National University of Singapore?\n \nThe rogue Computer Science student (Apprentice Seer) 🙇 has already managed to perform Anonymous-like defacements as part of his "education". Upon graduation, he will take over the Hacktivist and keep his fellow bros safe! He remembers his Civics and Moral Education class on "gratitude", I suppose!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutBH">
    <value>Shhhh, he's always monitoring data flows...\n \nYou see, the Network Snooper (Beholder) 👁  knows who the real hacktivist; the script kiddie never seems to be able to get past pinging 127.0.0.1.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutMason">
    <value>Beneath the bro code is a deeper code called the "three sisters".\n \nThe Gossip Aunties (Mason) 👷 are always together, sharing the latest juicy gossip about the estate. They gossip about everyone else except themselves, and hence the circle of trust is really just the gossip aunties themselves. </value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutDG">
    <value>This must be the top student!\n \nI'm talking about the Imitator (Doppelgänger) 🎭. Starting with memorising multiplication tables, he then goes on to memorising the 词语手册 and then onto organic chemistry. Now he's so good; he can essentially live someone's else's life, but that person must first disappear!\nNote: If the original resident was recruited by a MLM, they will take on their original role. All other normal rules apply: If they were the Orphan and their foster parents gone, the Imitator will sign up to be an HDB agent. Otherwise, they will inherit their foster parents.\nThe MLM cannot convince the student to think about money (but can after the Imitator switches roles). Also - the Imitator can NOT win unless they have take over a role. If at the end of the game, the Imitator is still the same, they lose (exception: forced marriage).
    </value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutCupid">
    <value>You mean arranged marriages are still a thing?! *glares at conservative parents*\n \nThe Matchmaker (Cupid) 🏹 is the witness of an arranged marriage (really, just for the BTO). On command of their parents, they will wed just so that they can help improve Singapore's TFR!\n \nNote: The spouses will know who each other are, but not be told their roles. If the spouses are the last two alive, they win, regardless of teams. If the spouses are on different teams (HDB Agent + MLM), and one team wins (HDB Agent), the lover (MLM) wins as well. TL;DR if both lovers are alive at the end, and at least one of them was on the winning team, they both win together.
    </value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutHunter">
    <value>Wanna know more about someone's dark past? Look for her! \n \nShe is the tape-recording Auntie (Hunter) 🎯. You may think she is just like any housewife, but she knows every single person's history. If the HDB agents try to evict her, she may have a counter-exposé that will humiliate one of them! If they're forced to leave the HDB flat, there is no loss in spilling the beans on someone else anyway.\n \nNote: For HDB agent evictions, the chance starts at 30%. If there is one HDB agent, the tape-recording auntie has a 30% chance to humiliate the HDB agent and survive. For each additional HDB agent, add 20% (2 HDB agents = 50%, 3 = 70%, etc). However - if there are multiple HDB agents, the HDB agents will select one of their counterparts to be the fall guy, and the auntie will still have to be evicted. \nIf the MLM tries to recruit the tape-recording auntie, they have a 50% chance to fail. If they fail, the auntie has a 50% chance to "borrow" on the contact of the CID to arrest him and his pig's head!
    </value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutSK">
    <value>Regardless of race, language or religion, there is always a ghost story or two... \n \nThe one and only PONTIANAK (serial killer) 🔪 used to be human! Since gaining supernatural status, the pontianak has decided to purify the HDB estate, by chasing everyone out! \n \nThey can win only if they are the last player with a HDB flat (exception: forced marriage). If the HDB agents try to harass you to evict you from the flat, you speak so bloody fast that the HDB agents have a four-in-five chance of losing the verbal duel and one of them gets a heart attack instead!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutPara">
    <value>O HAI DER!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="EndTime">
    <value>Game Length: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <!--New strings, July the 8th -->

  <string key="Day">
    <!--0 - Day -->
    <value>Day {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NodeShutsDown">
    <value>An error has occured, and this node has shut down :/</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SentPrivate">
    <value>I have sent you a PM</value>
  </string>
  <string key="StartPM">
    <value>Please send me a pm so I can PM you: @werewolfbot</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PMTrue">
    <value>Thanks for starting me! I can PM you now.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MustReplySmite">
    <value>You must reply to the user you want to smite</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WhatToDo">
    <value>What would you like to do?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="JoinFromGroup">
    <value>You must join a game from within a group chat!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="StartFromGroup">
    <value>You must start a game from within a group chat!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PingInfo">
    <value>Time to receive ping message: {0}\nCurrent CPU Usage: {1}%\nMessages per second: {2}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WhatLang">
    <value>What Language?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WhatVariant">
    <value>What Variant?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="LangSet">
    <value>Language set to {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GetLang">
    <value>Get which language file?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NoNodes">
    <value>There are no nodes online right now, please try again in a few seconds</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GroupCommandOnly">
    <value>You must run this command in a group</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NotGlobalAdmin">
    <value>You aren't a global admin...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NotPara">
    <value>You aren't Para!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Yes">
    <value>Yes</value>
  </string>
  <string key="No">
    <value>No</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Allow">
    <value>Allow</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Disallow">
    <value>Disallow</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Show">
    <value>Show</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Hide">
    <value>Hide</value>
  </string>
  <!-- Game Mode Choices-->
  <string key="NormalOnly">
    <value>Normal Only</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ChaosOnly">
    <value>Chaos Only</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerChoice">
    <value>Player Choice</value>
  </string>

  <!-- Show Roles on End Game -->
  <string key="ShowNone">
    <value>Don't show any</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShowLiving">
    <value>Show only living players</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShowAll">
    <value>Show all players</value>
  </string>

  <string key="Cancel">
    <value>Cancel</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowFleeQ">
    <value>Do you want to allow voluntary selling of flats once the game has started?\nNote: players can still drop out from the BTO during join phase\nCurrent: {0} fleeing</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowFleeA">
    <value>{0} fleeing after game start</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MaxPlayersQ">
    <value>How many players would like to set as the maximum?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MaxPlayersA">
    <value>Max players set to {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShowRolesDeathQ">
    <value>Show or Hide roles on death?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShowRolesDeathA">
    <value>Roles will be {0} on death.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GameModeQ">
    <value>What game mode will the group be?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GameModeA">
    <value>Game mode set to {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShowRolesEndQ">
    <value>How do you want roles to be shown at the end?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ShowRolesEndA">
    <value>Roles shown at end set to: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SetDayTimeQ">
    <value>Choose the base time (in seconds) for day time. This will still be modified based on number of players.\nMinimum time added based on players is 60 seconds. Default setting: {0}\nCurrent: {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SetDayTimeA">
    <value>Base day time set to {0} seconds</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SetNightTimeQ">
    <value>Choose the time (in seconds) for night time. Default setting: {0}\nCurrent:{1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SetNightTimeA">
    <value>Night time set to {0} seconds</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SetLynchTimeQ">
    <value>Choose the time (in seconds) for lynch voting. Default setting: {0}\nCurrent:{1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SetLynchTimeA">
    <value>Lynch voting time set to {0} seconds</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowFoolQ">
    <value>Allow script kiddie (fool) as a role option?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowFoolA">
    <value>Script Kiddie (Fool) as a role set to: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowTannerQ">
    <value>Allow attention seeker (tanner) as a role option?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowTannerA">
    <value>Attention Seeker (Tanner) as a role set to: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowCultQ">
    <value>Allow money-lending member (cult) as a role option?\nCurrent: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AllowCultA">
    <value>Money-Lending Member (Cult) as a role set to: {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ThankYou">
    <value>Thank you, have a good day :)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WhatLangGroup">
    <value>What language do you want to look for a group to play in?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HereIsList">
    <value>Here are the groups for {0}:</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Members">
    <value>Members</value>
  </string>
  <string key="StartMe">
    <value>Please start me so I can PM you.</value>
  </string>n
  <string key="PlayerNoPM">
    <value>{0} failed to start the bot, and has had his HDB loan rejected! No flat!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="LatestList">
    <value>Here is the latest list.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="UnableToGetList">
    <value>Unable to get latest list.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="YouJoined">
    <!-- 0 - Group Name -->
    <value>You have successfully joined the game in {0}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Ping2">
    <value>Time to send ping message: {0}</value>
  </string>
  
  <!-- Update 4.0-->
  <string key="RoleInfoMayor">
    <value>You are the self-declared lawyer (Mayor 🎖). Actually, you know nuts, but once you claimed you got a degree from Coursera (which really doesn't mean much), the residents think your words carry double their weight.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoPrince">
    <value>You are THE OBESE ONE (Prince 👑)!!! Probably enjoying too much of makcik’s super fattening laksa (and always choosing McDonalds for lunch and dinner), if the other residents chooses to chase you with a broomstick, they will find immense difficulty moving you, giving up simply because you are too obese. However, obesity is no excuse for the law.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoClumsyGuy">
    <value>You are the Gambling Addict (Clumsy Guy 🤕). You visit RWS so often you think even the idea of chasing a neighbour from his/her unit is fun (you even asked for odds, remember?)! Half the time you decide… let’s play roulette with your neighbours.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoSorcerer">
    <value>You are the stock market speculator (Sorcerer 🔮) who prefers to ride on the fortunes of your neighbours to earn a tidy profit for yourself. While legal, the HDB agents will still evict you because of your shadiness, so make sure you find them first to convince them of your common interests! The Hacktivist is also worth searching for; he may stall your trades and steal your trading account details!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoBlacksmith">
    <value>You are the superstitious auntie (Blacksmith ⚒) that "sio ghim chua" (burns hell notes). You may decide to select a day for burning so many hell notes (to repent for your past cruelty to your parents) that the entire HDB estate gets smoked, and the HDB agents unable to visit because they have been smoked so much that they need to call the town council to clear the ashes.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoAlphaWolf">
    <value>You are the HDB CEO (Alpha Wolf ⚡)! Your charisma as an agent is so alluring that there is a chance that your hand-picked choice to be evicted may impress you so much that you employ him to cleanse the HDB flat of the illegal doings in the HDB estate!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="RoleInfoWolfCub">
    <value>You are the HDB Scholar (Wolf Cub 🐶). You are high-flying, and so others are both envious and jealous of you. If you leave your job or lose your flat, the rest of the HDB agents will suddenly work doubly hard, knowing they may have hope to be promoted finally!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PrinceLynched">
    <value>As the village begins to chase {0} out of his house, they realise the immense difficulty of moving someone with a BMI of nearly 35 out. Instead, the residents kindly give him the namecard to Raffles Hospital, suggesting he needs it dearly.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SorcererOther">
    <value>You try to speculate on {0}'s identity, but can't quite guess who {0} is. However, that's not the HDB agent or hacktivist.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MayorReveal">
    <value>{0} steps forward and present his Coursera Certificate, declaring himself as a certified "lawyer". From now on, {0}'s votes for chasing people out will count twice.</value>
    <value>{0} quickly brandishes his recent Coursera Certificate on "Estate Law". From now on, {0}'s votes for chasing people out will count twice.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AskMayor">
    <value>Click "Reveal" whenever you are ready to reveal yourself as the Self-Declared Lawyer! Your Coursera degree has little use, but you can con the aunties anyway!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Reveal">
    <value>Reveal</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SpreadDust">
    <value>Would you like to burn your hell notes, smoking the entire estate tonight?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="BlacksmithSpreadSilver">
    <value>As the rest of the HDB block went about their daily activity, they suddenly notice {0} burning hell notes nearby! That's worse than the haze, but at least the HDB agents cannot come by to harass everyone! (HDB agents cannot evict anyone tonight.)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Mayor">
    <value>the Self-Declared Lawyer (the Mayor) 🎖</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Prince">
    <value>the Obese One (the Prince) 👑</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Sorcerer">
    <value>the Stock Market Speculator (the Sorcerer) 🔮</value>
  </string>
  <string key="ClumsyGuy">
    <value>the Gambling Addict (the Clumsy Guy) 🤕</value>
  </string>
  <string key="Blacksmith">
    <value>the Superstitious Auntie (the Blacksmith) ⚒</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AlphaWolf">
    <value>the HDB CEO (the Alpha Wolf) ⚡️</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolfCub">
    <value>the HDB Scholar (the Wolf Cub) 🐶</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerBittenWolves">
    <value>As the HDB agents evict {0}, {1} stops everyone, being the HDB CEO. {1} sees potential in {0} and provides {0} an opening in the HDB. They will be formally employed tomorrow night.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PlayerBitten">
    <value>You were nearly evicted, but the CEO saw potential in you. Instead of being evicted, you have been offered a job as HDB agent and will start work effective tomorrow!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="BittenTurned">
    <value>As night falls, you got an e-mail from HR. You gleefully open your e-mail and find your new vocation titled HDB Agent.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutMayor">
    <value>Your rather dubious "self-education" in legal matters through Coursera has probably earned you an unaccredited degree (try harder next time!), no job, but some "voice" in the estate. Because you have a degree as a self-declared lawyer (mayor 🎖), even though it's useless, as compared to the aunties, your voice counts for double its weight during the crunch time: who to chase away! (You know, just say, hey, I've a law degree, and the gossip aunties will make you sound very smart!)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutPrince">
    <value>Having grown up on makcik's laksa and playing DOTA 12 hours a day, your weight is certainly off the scales. You are THE OBESE (Prince 👑)! Friends and family have repeatedly told you to eat more veggies and exercise, but the closest you come to e-sports is playing Werewolves. Well, being obese does give you one little advantage: people cannot carry you! If you are asked to leave the HDB block, all you need to do is to say "no".</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutSorcerer">
    <value>The stock market speculator (Sorcerer 🔮) is *only* interested in money! By siding with the HDB agents, the stock market speculator believes that he might be able to gain much better than any illegal enterprise. But just who are the HDB agents and who is the hacktivist that could lay waste on his path to big bucks?</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutClumsy">
    <value>You are the Gambling Addict (Clumsy 🤕). You remember the entire layouts of RWS and MBS, and the tables with the highest rollers, but almost never remember you *had* money 💸! You sometimes even decide to take some people's flats as a gamble! (You have 50% chances to vote for someone random.)</value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutBlacksmith">
    <value>Burning hell notes, the superstitious auntie (Blacksmith ⚒). The truth is that almost everyone in the HDB block hates you whenever the Seventh Month comes round, but it seems that the HDB agents never cause trouble whenever you are out there burning hell notes. Perhaps it's all the mess you leave behind! 🤔
    </value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutAlphaWolf">
    <value>You are the HDB CEO (Alpha Wolf ⚡), the one who started it all. Public housing is public housing and should not be for all these finicky business! However, considering the attrition rate in your organisation, you seek for repentant souls who might see the error in their ways and turn over to your side. (20% chance)
    </value>
  </string>
  <string key="AboutWolfCub">
    <value>You are the HDB Scholar (Wolf Cub 🐶). Adored by the HDB CEO, you are considered so valuable that all the HDB agents either look up to you because of your smarts, or are jealous because you're a scholar that will be promoted much faster than any farmer. Once you are out of the picture, however, everyone would want to start impressing their bosses for the next fast-track career vacancy, so the HDB agents will work harder to prove themselves!</value>
  </string>
  
  <!-- new strings 06 nov-->
  <string key="DGTransformToAlpha">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <!-- 1 - teammates's name -->
    <value>{0} has left, and you found, amidst the ransacked pile, the CEO stamp! You quickly assert control over your fellow agents (if any) as HDB CEO. They are: {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DGTransformToWolfCub">
    <!-- 0 - target's name -->
    <!-- 1 - teammates's name -->
    <value>{0} has left, and you found that you are hard-pressed to live up to the expectations of a HDB Scholar. Your fellow agents (if any) are: {1}</value>
  </string>
  <string key="VillageTeam">
    <value>Team Residents</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NeutralTeam">
    <value>The ones who don't give a damn!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolfTeam">
    <value>The HDB Agents</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SerialKillerTeam">
    <value>The PONTIANAK Team!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultTeam">
    <value>The Money-Lending Members</value>
  </string>
  <string key="TannerTeam">
    <value>The Attention Seeking Team</value>
  </string>
  <string key="VillageTeamEnd">
    <value>Team Residents</value>
  </string>
  <string key="NeutralTeamEnd">
    <value>The ones who don't give a damn!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WolfTeamEnd">
    <value>The HDB Agents</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SerialKillerTeamEnd">
    <value>The PONTIANAK Team!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultTeamEnd">
    <value>The Money-Lending Members</value>
  </string>
  <string key="TannerTeamEnd">
    <value>The Attention Seeking Team</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultConvertWolf">
    <value>The money-lending members send {0} to try to convert {1}, but {0} was immediately flashed an eviction notice for such daring illegal money-lending! {0} has been evicted!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="HarlotFuckedKilledPublic"> <!-- used when Harlot visit's SK's victim, and dies -->
    <!--{0} = Harlot name, {1} = SK's victim name-->
    <value>{0} offered laksa to {1} last night, only to be met with {1} packing their bags! {1} convinced {0} of the existence of the pontianak, quickly convincing {0} to leave this HDB flat immediately!</value>
  </string>
  
  <!--New Death Strings 05 DEC-->
  <string key="ApprenticeSeerEaten">
    <value>It appears {0}'s computer science skills can no longer be put to the test. The HDB agents found his twiddling with automated DDoS scripts, evicting the Rogue Computer Science student immediately.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="BlacksmithKilled">
    <value>{0}'s superstitions have come true. She predicted last night the Pontianak would eventually find her, and she was right. The Superstitious Auntie has been scared out of her wits, and has decided to pack her bags.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultistKilled">
    <value>The Pontianak has claimed a new victim! {0} tried to go around hanging pigs' heads and spraying O$P$, only to be spooked by the Pontianak!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CupidKilled">
    <value>The Pontianak has robbed the HDB flat of "love", frightening the Matchmaking Auntie, {0}, out of her wits! No more matchmakers in the HDB flat; time for singles to wait till they are 35 before getting their own BTO!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="DrunkKilled">
    <value>Weird... {0} was enjoying his Tiger Beer when a loud scream was suddenly heard. Apparently the Pontianak has come visiting, spooked him out of his wits, and no amount of alcohol would make him forget the Pontianak! He hastily fled the HDB flat.</value>
    <value>{0} was enjoying a hearty shot of Kavalan (from the Duty Free store) when the Pontianak sobered him up. The drunkard is now leaving the HDB flat for good, scarred at how no amount of whisky can make him ever forget the psychological trauma.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GuardianAngelKilled">
    <value>{0} would normally have handled the Pontianak just fine, except that she was out of words tonight. Even as a 啰哩啰嗦 (Long-winded) auntie, {0} decided to cut the crap and just leave this scary HDB flat.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GunnerKilled">
    <value>Looks like {0} was not doing guard duty right last night! All the HDB residents had found was a trail of urine, an abandoned SAR-21 and a few bullet holes, as if the Pontianak had succeeded in spooking the shady NSF, just like the stories he had heard while in Pulau Tekong.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="MayorKilled">
    <value>Being frightened in his dreams from a Pontianak was not what {0} signed up for. Self-declared lawyers have no recourse against the... paranormal.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="PrinceKilled">
    <value>The Pontianak has struck again! {0}, the Obese, was conjured an image of horror beyond compare, sending him rolling down the stairs and leaving the HDB flat for good!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SeerKilled">
    <value>The Hacktivist, {0}, was working on the latest botnet when the Pontianak decided to pay a visit... all that was known was that there were some strange screen flickers...</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SorcererEaten">
    <value>The stock market speculator, {0}, was found to have been evicted last night. They would have made a good tag team with the HDB agents, if they had known!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="WildChildEaten">
    <value>What's with the heartlessness of the HDB agents, evicting the orphan, {0}! They could have employed {0} into their ranks!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="SerialKillerKilledCH"> <!--used when CH visits SK-->
    <value>The fakery of the Fake Corrupt Practices Investigation Bureau Officer, {0}, was exposed. Visiting an apparition last night was so traumatising he had got his just desserts for scaring people with the law. Never visit the Pontianak, especially at night!</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultConvertWolfPublic"> <!--used when Cultists convert the wolves, only if wolves stayed home-->
    <value>The HDB agents were doing some OT and admin work at home when {0}, the newest Money-Lending Member, foolishly hung a pig's head at the HDB agents' homes. The arrest and eviction that followed was faster than lightning could strike.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="CultConvertKillerPublic"> <!--used when Cultists convert the SK-->
    <value>A pig's head would have scared a human, but {0} learnt it would not scare the Pontianak. The tables have turned, and {0} cut all ties with the Money-Lending Members and quietly disappeared, in the dark of the night.</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GAGuardedKiller"> <!-- used when GA guards SK -->
    <value>The 啰哩啰嗦 (Long-winded) auntie, {0}, asked for trouble! How could she ever win an argument against a ghost? All that was left was a note outside {0}'s door that read, "I scare far more than your words ever can!"</value>
  </string>
  <string key="GAGuardedWolf"> <!-- used when GA guards a wolf -->
    <value>The 啰哩啰嗦 (Long-winded) auntie, {0}, visited the HDB agents last night. She squabbled with them, raised her voice, and was evicted for "noise pollution" and "disruption to the good order of the HDB estate".</value>
  </string>

</strings>
